Chapter 1068: Extortion

As the spaceship left the Limitless Financial Group branch, Han Xiao looked through the window as the building diminished in size before pulling back his gaze and smiling.

"I've hit at a good time. Sorokin has finally compromised…"

By his estimation, there was a seventy-percent chance of the negotiation succeeding. Even if he had the right time and place, he dared not speak with absolute certainty that Sorokin would yield to him.

Fortunately, his judgment of Sorokin's character was not wrong, and the final result was favorable to him.

If it was another Beyond Grade A with a temper, they would most likely have fought. However, Sorokin was good at enduring, and it was probably not the first time he had dealt with such matters. After weighing the benefits and costs, he immediately chose to compromise.

"Speaking of which, Sorokin is so shy about showing his strength. There must be a lot of factors within…"

Han Xiao stroked his chin as he pondered.

This guy was not like the other Beyond Grade As, who relied on their own personal power to influence their organization's development. He had almost no record worth mentioning, and his business was run through the normal and legal way.

The advanced civilizations had always been alert to any non-allied Beyond Grade A organizations. As the top financial group in the universe, the stronger their power, the more jealousy they would attract. Commercial organizations were not armed forces and had their own set of industry rules to follow. The moment they were targeted by the three Universal Civilizations, it would be hard for the financial group to maintain stable footing. If Sorokin decided to retaliate, others would know that he had been hiding his strength, and the civilizations' fear would increase.

This was only one of the reasons. Han Xiao still remembered some of the information displayed about Sorokin on his interface. This guy had probably changed his skin many times and had been living in the universe with different identities.

But no matter how many times Sorokin changed his skin, his ability would not change, so he avoided any form of conflict so as not to be recognized. Maybe he had committed some huge offense, so he deliberately kept his name incognito.

"This guy is full of mystery." Han Xiao shook his head. This was all speculation, and maybe Sorokin had another reason to do so.

No matter what those secrets were, he had squashed Sorokin this time and avenged the suppression he had suffered over the past two decades.

Shareholders would receive huge dividends from the Limitless Financial Group every year. This was no small amount, and while it was not too huge of a loss to Sorokin, Han Xiao could finally obtain some interest.

Under normal circumstances, such huge dividends would not be taken for free. Every shareholder position given by the Limitless Financial Group was coveted, and they would form another business cooperation with the Beyond Grade A organizations, mutually benefitting both parties.

But Han Xiao naturally would not allow the Limitless Financial Group to partake in the army's business channels, otherwise it would just be a gift to Sorokin. He had made up his mind to only take the money and do nothing, just like a dog in the manger, deliberately creating trouble for Sorokin.

"The Evolutionary Totem is being released to the universe, and I'll also obtain the shareholder position of the Limitless Financial Group. With these two sources of income, the abundant funds are enough to support the continued expansion of the army. The stock price of the Germinal Financial Group will also skyrocket."

Han Xiao was overjoyed. He took out his communicator to send messages to the contact points of the three Universal Civilizations.

It was only the initial step for him and Sorokin to come to a consensus. He still had to file it with the three Universal Civilizations regarding this matter for their support. Because of the Evolutionary Totems, this was not a difficult task.

After sending out the news, Han Xiao let out a deep breath.

Once the dynasty, federation, and church had all expressed their opinions, Sorokin also folded, which meant that the follow-up affairs of Black Star's Godlike Battle had almost come to an end. There was nothing left to do except to take care of Traveler and the Super Star Cluster Civilization behind him.

Traveler had already hidden himself, but Han Xiao knew which Super Star Cluster Civilization he belonged to. However, he had no plans to deal with the civilization behind the scenes at this moment.

On the one hand, the Super Star Cluster alliance was currently developing as a group and steadily expanding in the free competition zone, not creating any trouble, so there was no opportunity for him to take action. On the other hand, the three Universal Civilizations would not sit back and watch the Super Star Cluster develop in the Flickering World. Thus, they would definitely take action. Han Xiao decided to wait for the time the three Universal Civilizations launched an attack to cooperate with them, which would achieve twice the results with half the effort needed.

"Things are almost settled. The establishment of a platform for the Beyond Grade A united front should be placed on the agenda." Han Xiao rolled his eyes in deep thought.

Both Manison and Kasuyi, one director and the other the actor, did not come to urge him after the incident. No matter what they had done before, at least he owed them a favor during the Hila Rescue mission, so he still had to put in some effort to maintain a united front.

"The purpose of this platform should be to take advantage of the opportunity of the Flickering World to unify all the Beyond Grade A organizations, allowing everyone to have a communication platform, binding all Beyond Grade As together. It cannot be hidden from the eyes of the three Universal Civilizations, yet it cannot be done with too much fanfare… united front… hang on, united front‽"

Han Xiao suddenly had a eureka moment and hurriedly recited a few phrases from the socialist mantras before deriving an ingenious idea.

…

At the same time, Secret Master in the faraway Beast Ancestor stronghold received a communication application from Sorokin.

"Sorokin, what's happening?"

"Your Excellency Secret Master, I have a piece of bad news for you." Sorokin sighed.

"Speak."

"There's now a problem in our previous deal."

"What exactly happened?" Secret Master hurriedly asked.

"I promised to leave you one of the shareholder positions, but Black Star came over just now and used his current influence to threaten me. You also know, with the sale of the Evolutionary Totems, the three Universal Civilizations will surely support him. Thus, to reduce my losses, I could only agree to his request."

"You mean Black Star stole my reserved shareholder seat?" Secret Master's expression changed.

"Sigh, it's indeed like that. I can actually create a new major shareholder seat, but I need to dilute the equity of the others, which is more troublesome. It will take a lot of time to carry out some commercial operations and complete the capital increase. Otherwise, the other Beyond Grade A shareholders will not be happy." Sorokin could not take out his share, otherwise it would be painful if he lost control of the entire financial group.

"… Alright then. Let's proceed with the deal when you're done."

Secret Master was helpless. While he said he would cooperate in the future, he had actually already planned to cancel the trade in his heart.

This Sorokin was obviously too unreliable.

I'm obviously first in line here…

Secret Master had no anger toward Han Xiao snatching his lollipop. After all, in his opinion, Black Star did not know about their private transaction and did not specifically target him.

…

A couple of days later…

"Flickering World Beyond Grade A Development Union?"

In the Black Star Palace, Sylvia looked at the prototype of the plan that Han Xiao had handed over and could not help but show some surprise.

Han Xiao placed his feet on the table, raising his eyebrows as he replied, "Any problems?"

"The problem is so big that I'm speechless. The dynasty will never agree." Sylvia had an expression of helplessness. "To boldly unite all the Beyond Grade A organizations, isn't this taking the initiative to anger with the three Universal Civilizations?"

"What are you talking about? The Flickering World Beyond Grade A Development Union is a non-governmental organization that aims to deal with the contradictions between the Beyond Grade A organizations involved in the expansion of the Flickering World. It's always better to solve problems through negotiation rather than violence and jointly maintain the public security of the Flickering World. This is a good thing that will benefit the entire Star Field, and it is also an idea I developed after experiencing the previous incident. I'm worried that there might be more Beyond Grade As that will fall into my hands." Han Xiao spoke with an expression as though he totally believed in his lies.

Sylvia was speechless. She waved the document in her hands. "You do know that such bullsh*t will not get past the three Universal Civilizations, right?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao stopped his scholarly act, rolling his eyes.

"Well duh, but what else can I do? If I wish to integrate the Beyond Grade As, I'll need an excuse. Whether the three Universal Civilizations believe it or not, we still have to sugar coat it to prevent us from getting caught in an embarrassing situation."

Sylvia still had a worried expression. "To have our Black Star Army be the pioneer, won't this be too eye-catching? Especially in the eyes of the dynasty…"

"That's why this is only a draft. I'll still have to pull in more people to establish this union. Those who joined in the Meeting of the Gods with me will probably tacitly choose to join." Han Xiao shook his head.

While the Beyond Grade As had similar unions, there had never been a union of such scale, akin to the Mercenary Association, Pharmacist Association, or even the Superheroes Association. While the name of this organization was called the Development Union, in the eyes of discerning people, this would be an association that gathered all the Beyond Grade As in the known universe.

So long as most of the current Beyond Grade As joined this organization, they would be able to drive the membership rate of any new Beyond Grade As in the future. Its scope far exceeded that of The Ancient Ones to encompass all Beyond Grade As.

And if one utilized the appeal of this organization to continue to expand the range of members included, it could even evolve into a Super Association for the entire universe. Such a scale would be terrifying because such associations were generally only established by the three Universal Civilizations.

"Having such non-governmental organizations will never put the three Universal Civilizations at ease. They will inevitably ask for their own personnel to settle in. By that time…" Sylvia interjected.

"I know what you mean. 'Beyond Grade A' has a special meaning, and the three Universal Civilizations do not wish to have an association of such a nature… But because we're Beyond Grade As, they can only express their views, and they cannot go all out to prohibit it," Han Xiao countered.

He was clear that once such an organization was created, the Beyond Grade As would no longer exist as a tray of loose sand. The three Universal Civilizations would also become wary, but at this moment, this organization only served to aid communications, nothing really major. Thus, while the three Universal Civilizations would feel apprehensive, they would not take any action.

However, this might not be the case in the future. The problem of the united front was that it could not circumvent the affiliation of each Beyond Grade A's allied faction. This was the shackles created by the three Universal Civilizations, and they would not allow the Beyond Grade As to get rid of it.

Furthermore, what the Mechanic Emperor wanted to do was unite the strength of all the Beyond Grade As, whilst Han Xiao only wished to reduce the number of Beyond Grade A casualties, accumulating high levelled combat powers in the explored universe. Their goals were different, and there would be differences at some point in time. Furthermore, the Beyond Grade As were not of the same mind.

"Army Commander, you're playing with fire."

Sylvia had a worried expression. Her mind was full of the information regarding the Tragedy of the Pinnacles, and with the increasing popularity of the Black Star Army, she did not wish to see the three Universal Civilizations clear out all Beyond Grade A organizations. If that happened, the Black Star Army would inevitably enter their list.

Why did the three Universal Civilizations have an unbreakable dominance? It was precisely because when combined together, they had the ability to manipulate the entire explored universe! She had no doubt that the three Universal Civilizations would be willing to pay any price to kill off all disobedient Beyond Grade As in the universe, including their own allies.

Without the backing of a Universal Civilization, a Beyond Grade A would still be a Beyond Grade A. But in the same line, a Universal Civilization would still be one even without its Beyond Grade A allies.

"You're thinking too much. Everyone has their own scruples, and it might not reach such a stage. Right now, I'm just testing the waters." Han Xiao sighed. "The topic of Beyond Grade As is just too sensitive, so we can only take a step and observe, to see what how the Universal Civilizations react."

"Alright then… I'll go and improve on this plan."

Sylvia could only accept it. After all, Han Xiao was the boss.

She got up and opened the door, only to find that Feidin was waiting outside. The two of them passed each other.

Seeing Feidin, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He straightened and spoke with a smile. "Aren't you practicing your song at the moment? How do you have the time to visit me?"

"I found out everything. You actually want me to go and be an actor." Feidin had a resigned expression. "Couldn't you have discussed it with me beforehand?"

"It's just being a star. You're back in your old line. Furthermore, the army needs you. You can't possibly reject this." Han Xiao chuckled.

"Alright, forget about the acting part, but why am I even the main character?" Feidin was speechless. "And my role is you‽"

Feidin's role was to be Black Star in the new film.

Lucky people would still be the main characters even when acting.

"This arrangement is very appropriate. Only you are as handsome as me. This is in line with the facts. Just take a look over here. If we meet with a stranger, they might even say that we're twins!"

Feidin had no words.

Han Xiao laughed to himself. before waving his hand. "Alright, I won't joke anymore. The main reason is because no one dared act as me and bear the consequences after. You're someone close to be who used to be a star, so the director arranged it that way."

"But it's been so long since I last acted. Won't this be too weird for me?" Feidin was still hesitating.

"Haha, it will only be a hit if you're in a leading role. You're also a Calamity Grade, and a Psychic at that. How is acting difficult?" Han Xiao encouraged.

Han Xiao persuaded Feidin a while longer before sending this doubtful person off.

Shaking his head with a laugh, he took out his communicator to check on the latest news.

After swiping for a bit, he stood up in shock. A piece of internal news from the dynasty was reflected in his pupils.

The Dark Lord had resigned from his position!

Chapter 1069: Confession

"'Dark Lord' Clotti has temporarily resigned as the Guard Captain of the dynasty Ruler, and his position will be temporarily assumed by 'Quantum Demon' Judith…"

Han Xiao focused, browsing through this internal intelligence. He could not help but fall into deep thought.

The three Universal Civilizations each had a pinnacle Beyond Grade A as their Guard Captains. For the Crimson Dynasty, it was [Dark Lord] Clotti; for the Federation of Light, it was [Golden Ring] Oulou; and for the Arcane Church, it was the [God's Chosen] Wuornos. All of them were Beyond Grade As of direct relation to the civilizations.

In the dynasty's Beyond Grade A circle, the Dark Lord had a transcendent status and was also well known for not mixing and socializing. Throughout his years of contact, coupled with the memory of his previous life, Han Xiao had a good understanding of what Clotti's personality was.

This was deathly loyal to the dynasty. If there was no special reason, he would not step down as the Guard Captain.

In his past life, this incident did not occur during this particular time period, so the possibility of settling his private affairs could be ruled out. It should be because Clotti had accepted some sort of special mission.

"This should be the butterfly effect I've brought about. Maybe it is related to the Evolutionary Totem or even the Hila Rescue Mission…"

To be honest, he was a little apprehensive regarding this news.

Based on his memories, some of the Beyond Grade As that were directly related to the advanced civilizations were often loyal and dedicated, placing the needs of their civilization above those of the Beyond Grade As, and the Dark Lord was undoubtedly one of them. These people would not be part of the Beyond Grade A united front and might even turn against them.

To allow such a monster to move freely in the outside world, it was unknown what sort of changes would occur. This might hinder the construction of the Flickering World Beyond Grade A Development Union.

However, it was useless to delve too deeply. Because of Han Xiao's existence, many of the fate lines for the characters had been altered, and he could only adapt as he went on.

As for the 'Quantum Demon' Judith, who replaced Clotti, he was a Virtual Mechanic coming from the Crimson Dynasty. He was the person in charge of guarding the Heroic Soul, the main Artificial intelligence of the dynasty, and had relatively strong combat ability.

"Speaking of which, the direct line of Beyond Grade As from the dynasty really do not mix around much with the allies." Han Xiao's eyes flickered.

Within the Beyond Grade A circle in the dynasty, only the allies liked to gather together and mess around. As for those directly related to the dynasty, they mostly chose to remain isolated.

Unlike allies, those directly related to the dynasty would always have official positions. Some guarded the secondary dimensional outposts, some served as instructors, and some were fleet commanders. They were not as free as those who were allies. Only those semi-direct allies such as Kohler would be so relaxed…

Of course, it might be because the dynasty thought of him as too weak.

Just as he was thinking, countless particles surfaced in front of his eyes, coagulating to form an image of Phillip.

"Master, hum… Jotina and her party have arrived. It's time to check up on them." Phillip blinked his big eyes. This was a reminder set by Han Xiao.

"Oh, take them to the lobby of the inner ring. Also, summon Hila and the other Calamity Grade officers to meet the newcomers."

Han Xiao took up, putting on his Army Commander jacket before walking out of the room.

…

Jotina and her party followed the receptionist all the way into the lobby, and many of the army officers slowly trickled in. They were curious about their future colleagues, but without the approval of the Army Commander, none of them engaged in any conversation.

This party not only included the seven Calamity Grades that defected with Jotina but also the second wave, including Schneider. The total number reached eleven. They waited in the center of the lobby, also looking over at the officers.

Both sides stared at each other, and after a while, Han Xiao and Hila walked in.

"Greetings to Army Commander Black Star and Deputy Army Commander Hila."

Jotina and her group stood up to salute.

Han Xiao was all smiles. "Everyone is here. You're welcome to leave the shadows and join the light. After joining the Black Star Army, you'll be part of our family."

"Yes, welcome." In front of everyone, Hila did not smile, keeping her words short.

Eleven Calamity Grades could be considered a strong fighting force, enough to carve out a territory in a corner of the universe. Now that this group had joined the army, the high-level combatants belonging to the army had increased quite a bit. Furthermore, there were also elites such as Jotina and Schneider.

Han Xiao had to personally review every advanced combatant that joined the army. This was also the reason why these original officers of the Beast Ancestor had come to the Black Star Palace.

"Regarding your positions, I have yet to arrange them. If you have any requests, do tell me. I'll take them into consideration." Han Xiao smiled.

Hearing this, everyone expressed their intentions, saying that it did not matter as long as they could serve the army. Only Jotina put forth a different suggestion.

"Your Excellency Black Star, if possible, I would like to join your personal guard."

"Eh?" Han Xiao curiously looked over. "Why is that so?"

Jotina raised her head, looking straight at Han Xiao with a fiery gaze, not bothering to hide anything. "The body does not lie. I have strong feelings for you, and I hope to always accompany you around. If there's a chance, I hope that some chemistry can spark between us."

The moment she spoke, the entire room turned dead silent!

"Hmm‽" Hila eyes narrowed sharply. She was originally distracted and inattentive, but she suddenly seriously sized up Jotina from head to toe.

The officers around all thought there was something wrong with their ears. All of them adopted incredulous expressions. They did not think that this woman would be so blunt and speak out so honestly.

Even Schneider and the others were frightened, finding it unbelievable that their own elder sister would speak like this with a straight face.

F*ck me, we just joined the army, and you're already expressing the intention of mating with a Beyond Grade A in public‽

Aren't your guts too big!

Even if you really feel something for Black Star, you should proceed step by step.

To actually be so direct… indeed, only you can do so!

Han Xiao was stunned in place, not knowing whether to laugh or cry. He waved his hands.

"Alright, I'm not interested in stuff like this. I'll do my best to consider your job requirements, though. Let me first get started by getting a preliminary understanding of your strength. Walk up to me one by one and take a punch of mine so that I can judge your abilities."

He lightly skipped over this topic, and Jotina did not insist either.

The conversation returned to normal, but a weird atmosphere lingered.

Everyone constantly shot weird glances toward Han Xiao or Jotina, cautiously moving around them while staying clear of Hila, whose eyes were firmly locked onto Jotina. They were afraid of being caught in the crossfire.

A line of Calamity Grades stood in front of Han Xiao. Nanoparticles rushed out behind Han Xiao, fusing into a silvery black humanoid machinery, floating beside Han Xiao like a stand-in.

This humanoid body sent a powerful iron fist to every officer originally from the Beast Ancestor, dealing some damage.

The attributes of each Calamity Grade were displayed on the combat information interface, and Han Xiao quickly scanned everyone's abilities.

Among this group of people, the most powerful was naturally the Beyond Grade A seed, 'Claw Empress' Jotina. She was outstanding even among the Pugilists in the Calamity Grade, adept in claw arts and the pugilist arts of the Beast Ancestor. Her strength and agility were on point, and her damage output was high. She was more of an all-rounder fighter, and her combat power ranked in the forefront of the Army's Calamity Grade officers. A good gauge would be third or fourth place.

As for 'Boa Constrictor' Schneider, he was an elite Calamity Grade. Among this group, there were two of them who were quite close to each other in terms of combat power, standing out from the rest.

Out of the eleven of them, nine were Pugilists, and the other two were Espers.

Because the Beast Ancestor Organization was one where they were muscle tyrants, not adept at using their brains, no one liked to learn. There were practically no mechanics or mages there.

Han Xiao intended to let all of them become combatants, while a small portion would be filtered into the Black Star Guards. Most of them would be commanded by Herlous as senior officers for the different fleets.

After some encouragement, Han Xiao left the scene with Hila, leaving the officers to mingle with this new group of colleagues.

As the two left the hall and walked through the corridor, the army members they passed nodded and saluted. Hila did not care while Han Xiao smiled as usual.

After walking for a bit, Hila suddenly opened her mouth. "You're actually quite popular."

"Are you referring to Jotina?" Han Xiao laughed. "In any case, I'm standing at the peak of personal power, so it's normal for people to treat me like their idol. Don't you worship me as well?"

"Nonsense, when did I ever worship you?" Hila snorted and avoided his gaze.

"Well, when you were surrounded and attacked, you were the one that personally admitted you had admired me for decades. It's no use trying to deny it. I still have the recording."

"Damn, you want to fight?" Hila was so embarrassed and angrily glared at Han Xiao.

"Hehehe…"

Hila's forehead bulged with veins before she took a few deep breaths to regain her tranquility.

After being distracted by Han Xiao, she no longer felt depressed. Instead, she frowned and asked, "So, how are you going to handle Jotina? Are you really going to place her among the Black Star Guards?"

"Her ability speaks for itself, so why not? Are you afraid that a Calamity Grade can do anything to me? I'm a Beyond Grade A." Han Xiao raised an eyebrow.

"Humph." Hila turned her head away.

While she did not like the brazen Jotina, Hila would not use her position to trouble others. She was not someone who would engage in small tricks and would not interfere in Han Xiao's decisions.

Seeing that Hila was silent, Han Xiao thought for a while before suddenly saying, "Anyways, the army is expanding very quickly these days, and there will be a new batch of people every three to five days. As a result, there are many members of the army that are not familiar with each other and do not know the officers. There is a sense of distance, which will not be conducive to the unity of the army. So, I was thinking that we should hold some large-scale events to promote camaraderie."

Hila looked over. "What are you planning?"

"I'm thinking toward some internal competitions, such as a military parade or a sparring competition…"

As he spoke, Han Xiao's eyes began to gleam.

As of now, the Black Star Army already had a large number of groups and a large number of talents under its command. There were sufficient resources to host large-scale internal events, allowing members of the army to participate in such events outside of their work. This would be conducive to increasing the sense of belonging and promoting the camp culture.

Han Xiao's idea was to create a league of his own. The Pro League was an internal game for the players, but he planned to create a large-scale event organized by NPCs under the Black Star Army's name, not only for the players but for all members.

Sparring would be one of the focal points. He could separate them based on their ranks, and the elites of each rank would be selected from the competition. There would be prizes, and it would also allow the normal members to witness the officers displaying their strength.

In addition to competitions, a variety of events could also be held, such as sports or technical skills such as piloting and commanding. Even the Wayne Cards could be used as a separate leisure event.

In Han Xiao's vision, such an event could be turned into something similar to the Olympic Games for the army, held every few years as a celebration and also to showcase their strength to the outside world.

If this could be carried out, the scale would be many times larger than that of the players' Pro League, which would serve as a carnival for everyone.

Just thinking about it made Han Xiao excited.

"But holding such an event seems like it would need a lot of money…" Hila hesitated.

"Hey, what's that supposed to mean? Are we lacking money?"

Shortly from now, the sale of the Evolutionary Totems would be opened to the universe, and he would also become a shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group. At present, the Great Mechanic Han was bloated from the amount of money and could be considered to have fully entered the realm of a Rich Daddy.

If this money could be used to improve the faction cohesion and attractiveness, it would be quite profitable for him.

The more Han Xiao thought about it, the more he felt that this was something he could do. After he returned from the secondary dimension and settled the affairs of the Beyond Grade A union, he would have a lot of time to plan and hold such celebrations.

But it would be good to propose a prototype for Sylvia to perfect.

He had people to take care of his chores, so there was no pressure on him. Squeezing his own Chief Administrative Official had become a habit of Han Xiao's.

He had no other choice. Who made Sylvia so good looking and capable, making him so pleased with her work?

…

Sylvia's efficiency was high. She only took a day to perfect the draft of the Flickering World Beyond Grade A Development Union.

Han Xiao revised it before sending it to Manison to discuss the matter together. While they had conflicts of interest, they had to cooperate for this matter.

"This Development Union… the idea is not bad. While it is an excuse, it is reasonable enough to pass through the eyes of the three Universal Civilizations."

Within the encrypted channel, Manison made comments while browsing the draft.

"Oh, this is just a cover," Han Xiao explained. "On the surface, the scope of cooperation will be limited to the Flickering World. In fact, as long as this union is created, the conflicts of the Beyond Grade A in other Star Fields can also be resolved through this platform, and at the same time, the Beyond Grade A organizations can form a network of interests throughout the universe, providing each member with a place to exchange and cooperate with each other. This will achieve the goal of uniting power."

Manison pondered. "This is similar to how The Ancient Ones operate, but to achieve this, most of the Beyond Grade As will need to voluntarily accept such cooperation, linking their organizations in the interest network. But if there's no benefit, most people will be unwilling to cooperate, and then there's still the obstacle of different factions…"

Han Xiao interrupted him. "That's why we have to declare that this union is completely neutral by nature, just a loose one similar to The Ancient Ones. We have to organize it as much as possible so as to weaken any possible opposing influence from the factions. As for benefits, we will need the larger Beyond Grade A organizations to lead by example, by becoming the leader of the interest network and actively taking out cooperation shares. That way, the other Beyond Grade A organizations will be willing to join."

"Who are the confirmed initiators leading this?"

"Only you and I." Han Xiao shook his head. "In terms of influence, we can be considered behemoths in the Beyond Grade A circle, enough to serve as an example. The fact that we are willing to cooperate should attract a lot of people, but well… just two of us isn't enough. We need more leaders, preferably the pinnacle Beyond Grade As. Otherwise, we cannot hold on to the crowd."

"I understand what you mean." Manison agreed. "We'll need organizations with sufficient influence in various fields. On my side, I can try to lobby all the ancient ones, and the Protectors of the Galactic Black Market should also be brought in to take the lead. At the same time, we cannot forget about the neutral Beyond Grade As. Oh yes, there's also Sorokin who controls the Limitless Financial Group. His money is very important."

In the Beyond Grade A circle, Sorokin was recognized as a top dog with one of the highest assets. While the majority did not care much for his combat abilities, no one underestimated his power to make money.

At this time, Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

"I have a question. With so many pioneers… who will be the Chairman?"

Hearing this, Manison narrowed his eyes.

Since they wished to form a union, this problem could not be avoided. The Chairman of this union was of great significance, equivalent to the position of the leader of the martial world, the nominal chief of the Beyond Grade As.

Thus, be it strength or influence, it had to be convincing. The prerequisite was to be a pinnacle Beyond Grade A. Manison would definitely be a hot candidate, and Han Xiao was also eligible to compete for the Chairman position.

The position of Chairman came with a risk, that he would become the main target of the advanced civilizations, attracting their firepower. However, with great risks came great rewards.

Manison was staring at this position naturally out of interest, but as the main initiator of this project, Han Xiao had no reason to actively hand over the position.

After silence reigned for a while, Manison spoke slowly, avoiding this sensitive topic.

"There's only two of us now. It's too early to discuss such a matter. Let's bring in all the members before we decided on this."

"Okay."

Han Xiao nodded slightly before ending the call and letting out a sigh of relief.

Because this was a Beyond Grade A union, everyone present would be big bosses of an area. Thus, it would be impossible to make this into an area where only one person's word mattered.

Thus, persuading other Beyond Grade As to join would be tantamount to pulling supporters for himself. Only with enough Beyond Grade As supporting himself could he justify becoming the Chairman of the Flickering World Beyond Grade A Development Union.

Simply put, this was a matter of fighting for face. Just his strength was not enough.

"My network is quite extensive, but compared to Manison…"

Han Xiao shook his head.

He was confident in his relationship side, but Manison had been around for far too long, and his relationships were definitely much deeper than Han Xiao's. It would be difficult to compete.

If he wanted this position, he could only start with the benefits part. He had to let people see that whoever served as the Chairman would bring about greater benefits.

"What a difficult task. I'm afraid this will be another uphill battle…"

Chapter 1070: The Dark Lord's Target

After assessing the plan's feasibility, both of them separated into their own teams.

The pinnacle Beyond Grade As that Han Xiao was most familiar with were the three oldies of the dynasty, and the others were mostly acquaintances.

In contrast, Manison knew many more people, including those from the Federation of Light, the Arcane Church, Galactic Black Market, and even the neutral pinnacle Beyond Grade As. All of them were left to him to lobby.

Since his network was not as good as the other party's, Han Xiao did not stop Manison from doing more work. Instead, he made up his mind to compete from another direction.

Only the dynasty's side was left to Han Xiao. He sent out the proposal of the union to both Milizaus and Kant, inviting them both to participate in this grand event. As for the Dark Lord, Han Xiao did not invite him.

Thanks to the consensus reached in the Meeting of the Gods, the majority of the pinnacle Beyond Grade As readily accepted and agreed to build a Beyond Grade A platform in the form of a development union. However, a small portion of them hesitated, worried about the reactions of the three Universal Civilizations. Overall, it could still be said to have gone well.

The direct line of Beyond Grade As from the advanced civilizations was not included on the invitation list. They would not be issued any sort of invitation until the union was completely established. After all, most of these Beyond Grade As placed their own civilization above their personal interests, and while admirable, not everyone thought the same way.

Kant and Milizaus were both allies, and while agreeing to the invitation sent by Han Xiao, they raised their own concerns.

"Black Star, the relationship between you and the dynasty has just eased. If you take the lead now in forming the Beyond Grade A union, the dynasty will be dissatisfied with you again."

"There are no rulers who wish to see any unstable factors in their jurisdiction, but there's no way about it. Everyone has different positions," Han Xiao replied.

"You still have to be careful," Kant urged him again. "Manison's objective is to seek for profit. He wants to tie all the Beyond Grade As together as a bargaining chip. You're too young, don't let him use you."

These Beyond Grade As actually knew that Manison was using them, but because they could see the longer-term benefits that they could obtain, they saw no reason to reject this proposal.

"I'm aware of his intentions, but only through this can the Beyond Grade As benefit. If this can be realized, it can reduce the infighting between the Beyond Grade As caused by factions' differences." Han Xiao wished to preserve the vitality of the Beyond Grade As and intervene in the Calamity of the Supers as a chess player rather than a pawn.

"If I must say…" Kant spoke in an uncertain tone as he lowered his voice. "If the Beyond Grade A union can be fully formed, it will solve the problem of excess individual power. The moment Beyond Grade As grow to a certain extent, we will internally liquidate and kill those not from any of the factions, which is better than the three Universal Civilizations taking action in person."

Hearing this, Han Xiao could not help but glance at him.

This was a way to seize the power of liquidation from the hands of the three Universal Civilizations and use the ordinary Beyond Grade As as a price to maintain their pinnacle Beyond Grade A status.

If they continued developing normally, the union would indeed likely evolve to this final form. When the Beyond Grade As circle was strong enough and had succeeded in stabilizing their position, the union would definitely actively control the number of Beyond Grade As to prevent this circle from becoming too strong and attracting a bloodbath from the three Universal Civilizations.

The Beyond Grade A union would take the initiative to prune the branches, keeping the number of Beyond Grade As at a level that could threaten the three Universal Civilizations but not force them to take action. This way, they could decide who to kill and how many to kill, keeping the initiative. This loss was naturally much smaller than having the three Universal Civilizations take action.

It was estimated that among the pinnacle Beyond Grade As, there were many who thought in the same manner as Kant. This behavior of taking away the ladder once he climbed up to the top of the wall himself was not a fresh concept… After all, when the number of Beyond Grade As reached a certain level, the nature of their circle would gradually change as well. This posed more disadvantages than advantages to them.

While these pinnacle Beyond Grade As agreed to join the union, their ideals were all different. Han Xiao narrowed his eyes but did not say anything.

In general, there were no many problems in pulling people on board, so the action was quickly implemented. The organizations of the many leaders cooperated to mobilize materials and to select a site in the Flickering World to build the base camp for the development union.

Naturally, it would be impossible to conceal such actions from the other organizations, and the leaders themselves saw no need to conceal it. After all, the nature of their union was no secret, and the three Universal Civilizations should have already learned about it.

Of course, the news also travelled to the dynasty.

Pa!

"Black Star is taking a yard for every inch we give!"

In the Ruler's office, Bekorodi's face was contorted in anger as he smacked the table.

He pulled along several of the upper echelons from the hawk faction, berating Han Xiao in front of Urranrell.

"Just look at Black Star's recent actions. He acts with no respect for the dynasty at all! He has just eased his relations with the dynasty, and he dares to do something like this. Does he regard the opening of sales for the Evolutionary Totems as our weakness?"

Urranrell rubbed the center of her brows. "Then, what do you think I should do?"

"I feel that we should warn Black Star," Bekorodi bellowed. "If he continues to act as he wills, then the dynasty will withdraw the decree to open up the sales of the Evolutionary Totem."

However, Urranrell did not accept or reject his proposal. "If we rescind the decree, what do you think the federation and the church will do?"

"Humph, while they have coveted the Evolutionary Totem for so long, they are still clear on what is important. For this problem, both the federation and the church have to choose a stance, and they will not side with Black Star."

Bekorodi had a confident tone, quite sure of his judgment.

Urranrell knocked on the table before slowly replying, "You are right, but after the Meeting of the Gods, we anticipated this situation. Just targeting Black Star will not help as this is the general trend."

When she discovered that Black Star and the others intended to integrate the Beyond Grade As, she had already predicted that the hawk faction would attack and make things difficult.

In all fairness, Urranrell did not like seeing the Beyond Grade A union, but this issue was sensitive and involved many factors, so she could not make any hasty decisions.

As such, she could not easily withdraw the decree regarding the Evolutionary Totem sales and blame Black Star as Bekorodi suggested.

His suggestion was rejected, but Bekorodi was not angry. He had known that the Ruler would give such a response, and his goal was just to express his negative attitude. He pretended to grunt before leading everyone else away.

Only Urranrell was left in the room. She shook her head before opening the star map of the Flickering World, analyzing the situation.

Ever since the Flickering World was opened, the power patterns in the universe had started to change, and the dynasty was aware of this. First was the Super Star Cluster Alliance, and now the Beyond Grade A union. The changes were slowly surfacing.

"The price of exploration and expansion is turbulence, as every class wants to redistribute benefits…" Urranrell sighed.

Currently, the development union was still a grassroots team. Only a group of pinnacle Beyond Grade As were making the preliminary preparations. During this period, they would inevitably have to negotiate with the three Universal Civilizations, and it would take a few months for them to formally establish themselves.

This matter did not require much effort, so Han Xiao had a lot of free time and was immersed in repairing and strengthening his mechanical army.

After many failures, he had finally created an Emperor's Cape at the Gold Grade in his workshop.

This was the second Universal Treasure to be created by his hand. His [Spirit Instrument] skill unlocked the second layer, and at the same time, he obtained a new God's Trait Transformation point.

The second layer increased his basic success rate of manufacturing Gold Grade equipment, as well as research and development benefits. The increase was the same as that of the first layer, 2.5% and 1.2% respectively, but it also had a new attribute that increased the possible mutation rate of a Universe by 0.2%.

Reading through the introduction, Han Xiao discovered that this was the probability bonus for generating unique mutations in the process of making Universal Treasures. Such treasures would generally be stronger than normal Gold Grade equipment and might develop some 'unsolvable' abilities.

As for the God's Trait Transformation point, Han Xiao added it into the Mechanic path, and his [God's Trait Transformation—Machinery] unlocked the effect of its third layer.

Third Stage: [Apostle Mechanic] and below classes will have +3 to all class skills, +50% to speed of assembly line production, +10% Assembly line product quality, and -25% cost of materials. In addition, +1,500 INT, +30 Potential Points.

"The levels of my basic mechanic skills have gone up by quite a bit, and there's an increase in assembly line production skills, as well as Intelligence and potential points. It's not too bad."

Because Han Xiao had skills that could raise his Machinery Affinity based on his Intelligence, 1,500 points would bring about a 400% increase in his Machinery Affinity. The thirty free Potential Points could also be used to upgrade his Ultimate Knowledge skills by a level.

Though the effects of this third stage seemed to be a little mixed. They synergized quite well, especially the +3 to all class related skills, which brought a considerable bonus to him. After all, there were many Machinery Affinity skills in the low-level class skill list.

This time, the attribute targeted to be optimized was his Dexterity. Because of the amount of work needed, the difficulty in creating the Emperor's Cape was higher than that of the King. His points were thus optimized by 375 points, all of which were converted into free attribute points.

"I finally finished this equipment."

Han Xiao felt refreshed and put away his Emperor's Cape.

Everything that he needed to do was done. He could now make a trip to the secondary dimension.

The Flickering World Beyond Grade A Development Union was still in development, and this was no overnight event. The three Universal Civilizations would definitely oppose it, so it was a good time for him to hide from the dynasty's fatal calls. He did not even need to guess what the dynasty would say to him if the call connected.

Furthermore, Ames had already been there a long time, so he should not make her wait too long.

In the Crimson Dynasty's Constellation Corridor, within a large interstellar military fortress, a gigantic spacetime gate that was several times larger than a normal stargate stood in the center of the base. It lay in a dormant state, merely resembling an oval arch.

There was a figure hovering in front of this spacetime gate. It was 'Dark Lord' Clotti, who had removed his Guard Captain uniform and put on a special lightweight mechanical suit.

The respectful voice of the base commander came through the helmet communicator.

"Your Excellency Clotti, this mechanical suit is specially used for shuttling in the secondary dimension. It can anchor the coordinates of the main universe, and there's also a spare portable anchoring device within it. Please do not damage or discard it, else you might be lost within the stacks of secondary dimensions…"

"No need to explain further. It's not my first time going to the Secondary dimension." Clotti's tone was indifferent.

"Alright, we're about to open the portal. His Excellency Guzar, who is manning the outpost over there, will welcome you."

The moment he finished speaking, the giant spacetime gate gradually opened, and bright rays of light emerged from within the gate, quickly forming a whirlpool of light.

Quietly watching as the spacetime gate warmed up, Clotti called out the secondary dimension database list that was built into the mechanical suit. This stored the secondary dimension profiles that the dynasty had explored over the years, recording the spacetime coordinates and the energy frequencies.

The secondary dimension was very different from the main universe, so this database was equivalent to a map. Tracking devices could be used to remotely mark each location, which was equivalent to a navigation route.

Browsing through the database, Clotti quickly focused on one particular secondary dimension and marked it as a target location.

This secondary dimension was called [Evil Convergence]!

Chapter 1071: The World of Secondary Dimensions

The space of the secondary dimensions was a bizarre world composed of various planes, and its rules were different compared to the main universe. Most of them were not suitable for the survival of creatures from the main universe. Some were formed naturally, while some were created from the fantasies of high-ranking mages.

If the main universe could be described as the branches and roots of a tree, then the secondary dimensions would be the leaves and fruits, and there would be a nutrient connection with each other—energy.

Researchers in the universe had created a world view model for the secondary dimensional space, which looked similar to a picture of countless bubbles stacked. Each bubble represented a secondary dimension, and the space wall of each bubble was much weaker compared to the main universe; one could jump and shuttle around frequently.

The advanced civilizations had always been keen to explore the secondary dimensions. Not only could they obtain certain resources, they could also develop new technology through studying the phenomena of the different secondary dimensions. The three Universal Civilizations had achieved a lot of results in this area, and to a certain extent, the strength of each civilization's technology came from this area.

Thus, the three Universal Civilizations had a large number of outposts and research stations in the secondary dimension space, and they stationed different troops to protect scholars and workers. In most cases, they were dealing with the attacks of the secondary dimension creatures.

The outpost A0000 was the largest barracks of the dynasty in the secondary dimension. It was set up within a secondary dimension that was suitable for survival of creatures. The dynasty had completed the exploration of that entire secondary dimension and transformed it, hoarding all the troops here. The dynasty's army was stationed in their base camp of the secondary dimension, which also served as the gateway for the dynasty to enter the secondary dimensions.

As soon as Clotti stepped into this place, a magnificent scene greeted him.

He saw a patch of endless reddish-brown land, stretching out of his line of sight. The dynasty's base also sat there, seemingly endless, like a forest of steel.

There were no stars in the sky, only gradual color tones just like the bloody glow of the setting set. There were light rays that resembled the wind at one moment and clouds at another, flowing in the sky and scattering the fog-like scene. The sky at this place seemed to contain some kind of invisible light source, forming a Tyndall effect as it emitted a misty and dreamy path of light.

Clotti was familiar with this dreamy scene, but he had not seen it for so many years, so he could not help but stop and admire it.

At this moment, a thunderous laugh shook the air.

"Hahaha, Clotti, you finally got a holiday?"

Just as the voice fell, a bolt of turquoise lightning shot out from within the base. It stopped in front of Clotti in the blink of an eye, revealing a burly figure wearing the uniform of a Senior Dynasty General.

Seeing this man, the typically stoic Clotti could not help but smile.

"Guzar, it's been a long time."

"Haha, I didn't expect you to look for me the moment you got a vacation. You're indeed my good brother!" The burly figure laughed again.

The latter was a hybrid from the dynasty human race and the Silver race, but from his appearance, there was not much of the gracefulness that the Silver race was well known for. He had a rough and masculine appearance, with a wild beard and braids. If Han Xiao was there, he might have mistaken this guy for Zhang Fei [1. Zhang Fei is one of the major characters in the historical novel Romance of the Three Kingdoms, a general and the sworn brother of Liu Bei.].

'Peals of Thunder' Guzar was a Beyond Grade A from the direct line under the dynasty, and his Esper Ability involved the manipulation of plasma currents. He had served as the guardian of the secondary dimension for many years.

The qualifications of the two were similar, with the time difference between their enlistment only around five years. They had known each other since they were young and weak, and they had maintained a good relationship.

Clotti shook his head. "I didn't come here for a holiday. I have a mission."

"No wonder you temporarily resigned from your post." Guzar nodded and curiously asked, "Is this a direct order from the Ruler? What does she want you to do?"

"Pursue and kill a Beyond Grade A. The target is hiding in the secondary dimensions, named Traveler. He is suspected of participating in the war within the Flickering World not too long ago. Do you know about that matter?"

"Haha, I'm of course aware of this. There's no entertainment here, so I can only watch the news all the time. I heard that Black Star repelled twelve Beyond Grade As in total, including Kasuyi and Sierron. This is really amazing and makes me want to spar with him a bit. Unfortunately, I cannot even meet him personally."

Guzar's tone was laced with regret. Guarding the secondary dimension, he had no chance to leave his post.

"There'll be a chance in the future," Clotti reassured him.

Guzar did not linger in the topic, smiling as he said, "I think that this Black Star is a good kid. When you officially retire, he'll probably be the one to replace you in threatening the rest of the universe."

"It's a pity that he's not of direct lineage to the dynasty." Clotti did not agree with him or say otherwise, only changing the topic. "The secondary dimension is your territory. I will need your help in pursuing Traveler."

"No problem." A cold arc of lightning shot through Guzar's pupils. "These last few years, the rats hiding in here have been rapidly increasing. It's time to teach them a lesson."

…

Somewhere within the secondary dimension, Traveler was wrapped in magic, flying forward like a comet.

Suddenly, he paused, and a hesitant look crossed his face.

"Strange, why do I feel so restless?"

As a mage, he would never ignore his intuition, so Traveler stopped and took out a crystal ball, activating his divination spell.

Holding the crystal ball with both hands, a little bit of light floated from his palm to merge with the ball. Soon, the crystal ball rippled, showing a mirror image, similar to looking at a calm lake.

Clotti's face flashed briefly before dissipating.

"Dark Lord? What relationship does he have with me?"

Traveler's expression changed.

His role during the attack on Hila was just to pretend to go to Black Star for a spar. He did not participate directly in the battle.

In his opinion, even if the Black Star Army was suspicious of him, as long as he took refuge within the secondary dimensions, the other party would not waste energy to look for him to fight, but he did not expect the dynasty to sacrifice so much and send a huge killer weapon over to him. It felt like killing a chicken with a sledgehammer… In front of the Dark Lord, he could only admit that he was no better than a chicken.

"If I meet against the Dark Lord, I definitely won't be his match."

Traveler felt depressed. Even if he managed to master his Evil Convergence skill, he did not feel that it would be enough for him to stand against the Dark Lord. The latter was someone who had reached the pinnacle of dark energy and dark matter. Even 'Golden Ring' Oulou, who had reached a similar level to the Dark Lord, still ultimately lost to him in the secondary dimensions. Traveler did not think that he could surpass Oulou at his current level.

After thinking about it, Traveler's eyes lit up.

"I showed off the Evil Convergence, so the Dark Lord will definitely use this as a clue to pursue me. If I don't appear, they will definitely do something with the Evil Convergence dimension… It seems like I can only seek helpers to ambush the Dark Lord."

The time he had spent in the secondary dimensions was not for nothing. Not only did he develop good relations with a bunch of strong biological creatures, he had also gotten to know a bunch of Beyond Grade As who lived within the secondary dimensions…

Some of them were not even recorded within the list of known Beyond Grade As in the universe!

…

In a hidden secondary dimension, a portal suddenly appeared, and several small battleships flew out. Their outer armor showed no insignias, and the model of the battleships was top of the line, even equipped with navigation for secondary dimensions. Due to their additional components, the overall appearance looked heavy and bloated.

In the command room of the flagship, many of the operators bustled about in their positions. Everyone wore a full mechanical suit set, covering their appearance.

Standing in front at the porthole were two figures, wearing masked hoods and robes. Both had special equipment to hide their appearances, and only their height difference could be seen. One was short and stocky while the other tall and slender.

They were the leaders of this trip and belonged to the same organization. They were on a special mission.

One of the operators, who looked like the overall commander, reported to the both of them. "Your Excellency Law, Your Excellency Fay, we've already arrived at our destination. Please instruct us on our next step."

The duo were known as 'Law' and 'Fay'. Those were not their real names but codenames in their organization.

The short and stocky person was named Law. He nodded as he spoke in a deep baritone. "According to the plan, the divination shows that Black Star will enter the secondary dimensions with the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy in the near future. Activate the detection radars for all biological creatures to the maximum range and set the target life strength to the pinnacle Beyond Grade A level."

The cold and clear voice of Fay rang out as she said, "The secondary dimension is our home field, and our mission is to seize the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. Black Star has powerful combat abilities, and we need to avoid any sort of frontal conflict. The leader has allowed us to have many technological weapons that can be used to temporarily trap Black Star."

She paused for a while before adding, "If conventional methods cannot reveal him, the leader will allow us to use the Esper Ability of Destiny's Child once."

…

In Black Star Palace, Han Xiao called Ames over to the live combat training room.

"Busy guy, you finally have time for me?" Ames raised a brow, her tone joking.

"Official duties, I cannot escape from them." Han Xiao joked back before taking out a compressed orb and lobbing it over. He explained, "This is a special mechanical suit designed for survival in the secondary dimension. I built it myself. Try it out."

Buzz!

With a spark of Mechanical Force, the compressed orb transformed into a jet-black mechanical suit, covering Ames' body in a snug manner.

She moved around a bit, searching for any lag or discomfort, before clicking her tongue as she commented, "Very fitting. It seems like you know my body measurements very well. Good observation skills."

That's because I touched it before… Han Xiao coughed to hide his embarrassment.

Anyway, the nano-optimization feature exists, so no matter what sort of body shape you had, the suit would adjust to fit you. Why the fuss?

Even though he was vomiting in his heart, he did not show it in his movements, taking out the improved version of the Mysterious Energy Host.

Seeing the mechanical suits, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy excitedly called out, "Black Star, are you ready to set off?"

It could not wait to gather with its old friend once again.

Han Xiao nodded before turning to Ames to explain, "The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy is able to shuttle through the secondary dimensions. With it leading the way, we can save ourselves a lot of energy."

In the five major classes, only the mages and mechanics could stably enter and exit the world of secondary dimensions. Both of them, however, had different methods of entry.

As for the Espers, theirs was a random factor. In contrast, the dimensional shuttle capability of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was more convenient, and their search for the Holy Light Particle would also require its help.

This was not Ames' first time going to the secondary dimension. However, the ordinary procedures were troublesome, so with the help offered by Black Star and the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, things were a lot simpler. She curiously asked, "Then, where will our first stop be?"

"The dynasty has quite a few outposts in the secondary dimension, but I don't wish to disturb them. Since you also have the Void bloodline, let's go to the Void Dimension first."

Han Xiao grasped the arm of the Mysterious Energy Host, gesturing for Ames to do the same.

"Alright." Ames did not have any objections, but she did not hold onto the Mysterious Energy Host, instead choosing to latch herself on Han Xiao's shoulder.

An ordinary person would have to make thorough preparations in order to go to the secondary dimension, but both of them were Beyond Grade As, so they did not require any sort of precautions.

The next moment, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy activated its ability, and a surge of crimson energy rushed out, enveloping their bodies.

Swoosh!

A bright light flashed, and the three of them disappeared without a trace.

…

Their vision blurred, and the scenery in front of their eyes suddenly changed. They were no longer inside Black Star Palace but within the familiar Void Dimension.

"This is really fast." Ames was shocked.

"This is its innate ability. For it, returning to the secondary dimension is akin to going home, just like a fish in water," Han Xiao replied.

The Mysterious Energy Host had strong combat abilities, and at the same time, it also possessed plenty of convenient abilities and effects. It really was like a handyman.

Ames took a deep breath of void energy, feeling the excitement in her cells. She chuckled. "What are our travel plans?"

"Let's finish what we came here to do. We'll have plenty of time to explore afterward."

As Han Xiao spoke, he turned to look at the Mysterious Energy Host and asked it, "Do you know which secondary dimension the Holy Light Particle resides in?"

"I'm not sure what it's called in the main universe, but I can identify its energy fluctuations and track it down," the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy explained.

Hearing this, Han Xiao nodded. He had previously inquired about the dynasty's exploration records of secondary dimensions based on the description given by the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, but they could not find anything similar. This probably meant that the place where the Holy Light Particle could be found had not been discovered yet.

Upon thinking about it, this would make sense. If the advanced civilizations managed to locate its lair, then the Holy Light Particle would not be able to laze around. Thus, at this moment, they could only depend on the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy to guide them.

"Let's go quickly. I can't wait to teach it a lesson."

The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was eager and proactively urged the others. It could not control the host by itself and had to have Han Xiao's approval.

Hearing this, Han Xiao could not help but laugh. He estimated that the Holy Light Particle would probably be upset at this 'friend'.

Brat, you brought all these enemies over to my area‽

As he shook his head, Han Xiao was about to speak, but his expression suddenly changed.

Boom!

At this moment, an anomaly occurred as the void energy in their surroundings began to tremble.

Ames felt the same sensation, and she narrowed her eyes as she gazed off into the distance. Her tone was solemn. "Seems like something's coming!"

Chapter 1072: Milestone: [Void Conqueror]

The Void Dimension was a chaotic and misty world, with gray and blue the predominant colors. Its space was filled with thick and viscous void energy.

Suddenly, the two of them seemed as though they had been put into a blender; the surrounding void energy formed a large vortex, with Han Xiao and Ames at its center.

Han Xiao raised his wariness, getting into a battle-ready state. The next moment, a mental fluctuation burst out, sweeping past the both of them, and a solemn, archaic voice spoke in their minds.

"What sort of alien creatures are you, to dare barge into my territory‽"

Just as the voice rang out, a powerful aura burst out in their perceptions. Rays of light flickered all around as countless figures appeared out of thin air, seemingly endless. They surrounded the duo.

These creatures had strange appearances, but they all carried the characteristics of a void species and wore specially-made armor.

Sweeping a glance, Han Xiao felt a sense of familiarity.

He was no stranger to these strange-looking creatures.

There were Void Prowlers and Chaos Observers as the Reconnaissance Troops, riding Void Hunters, Void Star Pursuers, and Void Walkers. Lined up in ranks were the Void Disciples, the Void Executioners, and the Magomado Blades. The ranged troops consisting of Void Witch Spirits and Chaos Arcane Bodies were placed at the back. These were all the race options he had encountered with each promotion.

In the center of this army was the behemoth troop. There were ten huge Margola Void Beasts, covered in armor and carrying countless void creatures. There were even three Void Dragon hatchlings, of which the three strongest void creatures rode on them.

Their leader was a Void Duke, about a few hundred meters in height, his body covered in a tangible blue-violet energy. He was covered from head to toe in huge black armor and held onto the reins of the void dragon with one hand, a mysterious black longsword in the other. Void Dukes could change their forms at will, and this Void Duke was currently assuming a humanoid form.

This was a Void Army Regiment!

"It seems like we accidentally ended up in the territory of a Void Duke."

Seeing the group, Ames furrowed her brows.

She was an old visitor to the secondary dimensions, so it was not the first time she had encountered such a scene.

The Void Dimension was a naturally formed secondary dimension, and it spanned across an extremely vast area. The difference in dimensional attributes compared to the main universe had resulted in the spawning of the countless void species. In addition to naturally growing, the void species could strengthen themselves by swallowing each other, thus forming a complete chain of weak and strong. In this situation, the higher void creatures eventually segregated their territories, forming armies to fight against each other.

The Void Duke was one of the top void creatures, boasting their own powerful army. Their goal was to swallow other Void Lords or Void Dukes. Not only did they thrive on war, but using the unique features available to them, they had developed a special technology applied to the Void Dimension.

The Void creatures not only fought against each other, they were also hostile toward foreign life forms. One reason was because foreigners usually tended to kill them for materials, and secondly, the Void Corruptors could use their blood to convert the foreigners to become a new source for their troops. Thus, when encountering visitors from different dimensions, they would not be lenient.

"They treat us as prey."

As countless malevolent gazes landed on them, Han Xiao narrowed his eyes before releasing his Beyond Grade A aura. His momentum swept the area around him like a gale.

Boom!

The tyrannical aura caused the void army to stagnate.

The Void Duke's longsword slashed outward, sending a spiritual message filled with shock.

"Beyond Grade A creature of the main universe‽"

The prestige of Beyond Grade As resounded even within the secondary dimensions.

Han Xiao revealed his identity. "I'm an ally of the Crimson Dynasty, the leader of the Black Star Army. I go by Black Star."

"Black Star? Never heard of you."

Because information exchanges between the main universe and the secondary dimensions were limited, most of the void creatures were not concerned about the news from the main universe. However, the big names like the Crimson Dynasty were still known to the Void Dukes, as the reputation of the three Universal Civilizations had also spread throughout the secondary dimensions. The higher beings of the Void Dimension had considerable wisdom and knew to not provoke the three Universal Civilizations.

"Outsider, I'm the Void Duke Kirkmond. Leave my territory immediately." He pointed with his longsword, indicating their expulsion.

The Beyond Grade A life forms from the main universe were not so easy to provoke. Although the Void Dimension had successfully killed some invading Beyond Grade As before, they were all done by the strongest Void Dukes. The casualties on both sides were equally heavy, which resulted in those Void Dukes being swallowed by others instead. Kirkmond was merely a Void Duke in the middle ranks and did not want to get himself into a conflict with a Beyond Grade A for nothing.

Seeing this, Ames did not wish to blow up the matter any further and patted Han Xiao. "Let's go. There's no need to entangle with them."

Sweeping his gaze across the vigilant Void Army, Han Xiao suddenly had an idea and switched to his Void Form. The aura around his body changed completely.

Seeing this, Kirkmond jumped up in shock.

"You're also part of the Void‽"

"That's right. I'm not a creature from another dimension but one of your kind."

After Han Xiao entered the Beyond Grade A realm, he had transformed into an exclusive race, but the void bloodline he originally had did not disappear, merely merging into the exclusive race.

According to his degree of evolution, Han Xiao's Void creature ranking was high. He had reached the level of the Void Archangel, which was similar to the rank of Void Duke.

Kirkmond's attitude took a 180-degree change, filling up with envy and greed while hiding behind a fawning attitude.

When encountering a Beyond Grade A of another species, even if they killed the other party, there were no benefits to them. However, if the other party was a Beyond Grade A void creature, then he could swallow their bloodline and obtain an evolutionary boost.

However, the difficulty in killing the latter was also greatly increased. The void dimension was the home of the void creatures, and the higher one's void dimension life level, the higher their degree of control over the Void Energy. Han Xiao was akin to a fish in water there and would not be affected by the suppression of void energy.

The power system of the Void Dimension differed from the main universe. The void life forms possessed various racial talents, and through continuous evolution, they would activate their innate abilities to exert a great combat strength. This sort of strength could not be replicated by others, so it could not be classified as one of the major Super systems and only classified as a special life form.

However, the void creatures could also take the initiative to master the super system of the main universe, and their representatives were relatively well known.

"Do you know Kasuyi?" Kirkmond could not help but ask.

"We're quite familiar with each other." Han Xiao nodded.

Hearing this, Kirkmond felt proud.

Kasuyi was a celebrity within the Void Dimension, publicly recognized as one of the strongest void creatures to exist. He had raked up vast achievements while still within the void dimension, conquering a large number of Void Lords and Void Dukes and ruling a vast territory in the center of the Void Dimension. No one could contend with him then, and while he was generally more active in the main universe, his reputation within the Void Dimension still remained unmatched.

And right now, Kirkmond had encountered a new Beyond Grade A void creature who was even familiar with Kasuyi, piquing his interest. After all, Kirkmond himself did not possess the qualifications to even come into contact with Kasuyi.

"Black Star, come over to my place to be my guest." Kirkmond directly issued an invitation. There were few formalities within the Void Dimension, so they did not beat around the bush.

"Alright, I'll go and have a look." Han Xiao had similar intentions. Since he had managed to meet this Void Duke, it would be good to exchange some intelligence. Furthermore, since he planned to travel and explore this time, he was not afraid of having his time delayed.

The Void Dimension had many good things, such as the Void Maharaja that Austin had once given him, allowing his bloodline to be purified further. While Han Xiao had already reached the pinnacle Beyond Grade A realm, there might be something that could help him strengthen his void talents. There was no harm in trying his luck.

Speaking of luck, Han Xiao could not help but think about the luck halo [Caretaker of the Stars] that Ames had.

While he did not bring Feidin this time, Ames' had pretty good luck as well, which could be able to carry him forward.

"This is a guider. Follow me."

Kirkmond shook his fingers, sending out a cloud of void energy that contained the information on the coordinates over to Han Xiao.

The next moment, the surrounding void army all flickered and disappeared. In the Void Dimension, none of the inhabitants flew normally. They had all mastered the craft of Void Travel.

Seeing this, Ames shook her head in resignation. "You actually exposed your identity to the Void creature. The last time Hila and I came to the secondary dimension to train, neither of us dared to do so, or else we would not have made it back."

"Those with skills have bigger balls," Han Xiao joked.

While the secondary dimension still posed some risks to ordinary Beyond Grade As, it was not much to a pinnacle Beyond Grade A.

The duo then followed the guider and shuttled through the void, soon arriving at Kirkmond's base camp.

This was a magnificent city that was suspended in space. The entire body of the city was made out of translucent crystals, and its radiant internal energy core could be seen, surrounded by a rich layer of gray-blue void energy.

Within the Void Dimension, natural materials were scarce, so crystals were generally obtained through special techniques of refining the omnipresent Void Energy. To build a city like this, the expenses were naturally gargantuan.

This huge city had many barracks, so rather than calling it a city, it would be more accurate to call it an army camp. Han Xiao and Ames went to the main hall in the center of the city, and Kirkmond greeted the both of them.

He had shrunk his body to match Han Xiao's size. After they sat down, he impatiently asked, "Black Star, where were you born?"

He thought that Han Xiao had grown up as a native of the Void Dimension. However, Han Xiao did not hide it and explained that he was someone who had acquired a void bloodline and had always been active in the main universe.

The two of them chatted with each other, exchanging information. Han Xiao talked about the situation in the main universe, while Kirkmond talked about what the Void Dimension was like.

In his previous life, the players had a limited understanding of the secondary dimensions since they only came into contact with it in the later versions. Furthermore, many of the secondary dimension life forms did not have a habit of recording their history, so Han Xiao also lacked information about the void dimension in the current era.

After some exchanges, Han Xiao developed a general understanding of the current power balance of the void dimension. It was not ruled by a single entity but by many strong powerhouses.

The Kasuyi family dominated and occupied the entire central area but had no intention of unifying the void dimension, nor did they possess the ability. Powerful Void Dukes constantly sprang up like bamboo shoots after a downpour, fighting each other in separate areas. In addition, there were a large number of chaotic areas such as the wilderness, where chaos reigned, constantly breeding new void creatures that would freely hunt each other in the area.

After chatting for a while, Kirkmond finally came to the topic of Han Xiao's reason for going there.

"I actually have no goal. I just intend to roam a bit around the secondary dimensions. My first trip was to the Void Dimension, and I coincidentally met you." Han Xiao spread open his hands.

Hearing this, Kirkmond thought for a while before saying, "Since you have nothing to do, you can help me out."

There was no such thing as politeness or etiquette in the Void Dimension. While it was the first time they had met, Kirkmond did not bother standing on ceremony with them.

"What do you need?" Han Xiao was curious.

"I've always wanted to kill Bagdora. He's also a Void Duke, his territory similar to mine. We've already had more than a hundred battles against each other. If you're able to help, I can eradicate him, swallowing his core and taking over his army troops."

Han Xiao raised his brows. "Then, what can you repay me with?"

"I can give you half of the cores of the Void life forms left on the battlefield. In addition, if you need any specialties of the Void Dimension, I can find them for you." Kirkmond waved his hand, giving his bottom line without any attention for negotiation skills. "Furthermore, you can obtain my friendship. When you need help in the main universe, you can open a Void Path, and I will bring my army to help you fight."

Hearing that, Han Xiao was excited.

When he previously evolved into the [Void Pathfinder], he had obtained the racial talent of [Void Path], which could temporarily open a door to the Void Dimension.

He had never utilized this ability before because the summoned void life forms would not differentiate between friend or foe. However, if he could form an agreement with Kirkmond, then he would be able to use this ability to summon a void regiment to fight for him.

The same was true for Kasuyi. He could use his natural ability to call out the Void army under his command. This was where he had obtained his moniker [Void Overlord], but he seldom used this ability since his true body was too strong and did not require reinforcements.

While Han Xiao was not a summoner, this talent could also achieve the effect of a summoning.

At this moment, a notification popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

_____________________

You have triggered the mission: Void Duke's War Employment!

Mission Introduction: Void Duke Kirkmond has taken a fancy to your combat abilities, and hopes to hire you to fight for him and eradicate his enemies.

Mission Requirements: Defeat Void Duke Bagdora's Army

Reward: 12 billion experience, +3,000 Kirkmond Favorability, 1 Character Summon Card

Additional Reward: Triggers the Milestone Mission: Void Conqueror

Void Conqueror: Milestone competition conditions: Destroy eight Void Dukes and their organizations (void life forms at the same life form level are accepted). At the same time, achieve a Favorability rating of Respect (3,000 Favorability) in at least four Void Dukes' factions. Reward will be given after Milestone is completed.

Milestone Completion Reward: If you possess Void abilities, their base effects will have a slight increase, and you will obtain 500 – 2,000 Free Attribute Points. You will also obtain +1 Legendary Point, +20 Favorability on all void life forms, and +1 God's Trait Transformation Point. This will only be given if the [God's Trait Transformation] talent is activated.

_____________________

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The rewards were pretty good this time. He could even obtain a God's Trait Transformation point. After creating both Universal Treasures, he had thought that he would have to wait till he underwent another Promotion to obtain more points.

Looking at the introduction, it seemed like only those Beyond Grade As who had reached the level of God's Trait Transformation would then trigger this extra point reward. If other people accepted this mission, they would not see the last message.

Han Xiao was overjoyed.

Not only did he manage to obtain a mission, he could even get a large number of Void specialties promised by Kirkmond. This sort of business could be done. To Han Xiao, it was just going back to his old mercenary days.

"Deal, I'll help you." Han Xiao smiled. "However, now's not a good time. I still have things to do, so let's put this off until I return."

He had already decided to accept the employment, but his priority was still to obtain the Holy Light Particle. This was non-negotiable; thus, he would only come over to help Kirkmond after he was done obtaining the Holy Light Particle.

"No problem!" Kirkmond was overjoyed, immediately agreeing.

Since he had fought the other party for so many years, waiting a while longer was not a problem.

Ames was not interested in their conversation. After growing bored of listening to them, she took out the revive token to fiddle in her hand. She had also obtained this from Hila.

At this moment, Kirkmond glanced over subconsciously and suddenly froze, his gaze fixed on the revive token.

"Huh?" Ames' brows rose, and she clenched her fingers over the token. "What are you looking at?"

"Er, could you pass the thing in your hand to me for a look? I felt a very familiar aura from it." Kirkmond was not polite at all, his tone carrying a little suspicion.

Han Xiao realized something, quickly taking his own token out and asking, "I have something similar. Does it have the aura you're familiar with?"

"Yes, but it's very weak. Could you pass it over to let me scrutinize it?" Kirkmond nodded.

Han Xiao thought about it before flicking the token over.

Kirkmond's palm transformed into energy to envelop the revive token. After carefully looking at it, he replied with an uncertain tone, "I seem to have felt a similar energy fluctuation within one of the secondary dimension layers…"

Han Xiao's expression changed immediately.

This revive token contained the effect of [Death Rejection—Awakening]. Based on his inference, this was a new ability developed by Hila. Using delicate power control, she had combined Aurora's life energy with her own Power of the Dead to form an entirely new type of energy.

Hila had also mentioned that when she was attempting to form a remote connection with Aurora, she experienced some difficulty in that a secondary dimension layer kept absorbing most of the energy transmitted between both of them. Hila initially planned to do a field trip to the area, but she did not have the time to come this trip.

So, is it a coincidence that I came across the target Hila was looking for?

Han Xiao could not help but look at Ames.

Compared to Feidin, I think touching you might be better now…

Chapter 1073: Encounter

To come across a clue right after they entered the secondary dimension, this could only be attributed to luck. Most likely, it was Ames' [Caretaker of the Stars] Luck Glow that shone down on them. Could it be that the Goddess of Luck had changed her sexual orientation?

Speaking of which, since the act of rubbing Feidin for luck was called 'Touching the Willy', what then should he term the act of rubbing Ames?

Should he just go with 'Coiling Dragon[1]'?

Since his luck was good enough to run into the clues that Hila was searching for, Han Xiao had no reason to let it go. He pressed on. "Do you remember which secondary dimension that was?"

Kirkmond thought for a while before he nodded. "I have a faint impression. That secondary dimension seems to be pretty well known as well and was famous for a period of time. It was once blocked off by a certain type of power but occasionally emitted strong vitality that could actually stimulate the potential of various life forms. Later, the blockade lifted by itself, but when the curious secondary dimension life forms went over, they discovered that nothing was within it, and the entire space even lacked the energy to maintain itself. It slowly declined and shrank, and in recent years, it's been close to collapse. It may disappear at any time."

Hearing that, Han Xiao was excited.

Most secondary dimensions did not exist forever but would collapse and disappear over time, just like leaves withering and fruits rotting. The secondary dimension world was disorderly and chaotic, which would constantly give rise to new secondary dimensions. Most of them were like bubbles, small and short lived, and only a few could exist stably for a long period of time.

Advanced civilizations and mages could also create artificial secondary dimensions. However, the form of such artificial secondary dimensions was different from the naturally occurring hyper-stable plane of the void dimension.

As for the blockage of such secondary dimensions, there were several possibilities. The most likely would be that the secondary dimension was a creation of some powerful life form. In which case, it would make sense to seal it from the outside world to prevent intruders.

"If this secondary dimension was the subsidiary space of a Beyond Grade A, then the reason for its decline should be the death of the Beyond Grade A creator, causing the space to lose its energy supply, gradually shrinking and collapsing," Han Xiao guessed.

"I'm not clear on that." Kirkmond threw the revive token back to Han Xiao. "I call it the Land of Dead Silence. If you wish to go, I can send you the coordinates."

"If you could. I have some interest in that place." Han Xiao smiled.

Kirkmond casually squeezed at the void energy, burning the information of the Land of Dead Silence within before throwing it to Han Xiao. He added, "The space wall of that secondary dimension is riddled with holes, and countless space storms surge within. Be careful, the space might collapse and disappear at any time, and if you are swept away by that turbulent space, you might end up lost in the endless layers of the secondary dimensions."

Han Xiao received the energy clump and read through the information before standing up. "Noted. We'll make a move now."

This was an unexpected harvest of the trip. He had planned to take a gander after he was done with his business to help Hila search for what she wanted.

"Then, I'll wait for you to return so we can start the war." Kirkmond nodded back.

Having reached an agreement for the war employment, Han Xiao did not delay and once again summoned the Mysterious Energy Host.

"Let's go. Lead the way. We'll find your old friend."

The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy got the instruction and performed another dimensional shuttle, taking Han Xiao and Ames with him.

…

Meanwhile, Law and Fay were slowly patrolling a vast white space within one of the secondary dimension layers.

On the bridge of the flagship, a star map of the secondary dimension was suspended in the air, but its appearance was very different from the detailed 3D map the main universe had. It looked like a model of countless bubbles piled up together, and at first glance, it looked like a bunch of grapes. Every bubble represented a secondary dimension that was recorded.

Because new secondary dimensions were constantly being born, the terrain of the secondary dimension changed every moment. This map was only used as a reference, and the anchor point coordinates of the different layers were used as guiding markers.

Law and Fay stood next to the secondary dimension world model, silently observing. At this moment, a red dot suddenly lit up inside one of the bubbles, and a circle of red ripples appeared within the model.

"Cross-probing radar has discovered a target, marked as pinnacle Beyond Grade A level!"

"Our target is separated by thirteen secondary dimensions… The route simulation is complete. Expected to encounter our target after eight jumps."

"Your Excellencies, awaiting your command."

Hearing the reports from the subordinates, Law hummed in agreement before commanding, "Lock the anchor point, start the dimensional jump!"

Once the command was issued, these warships immediately activated the secondary dimension engine, turning into streams of light as they accelerated wildly. The shuttle device loaded on the battleships began to operate, oscillating at the space walls with a special frequency.

The moment the battleships' speed reached its peak, a space wall shaped like a honeycomb appeared in front of it. A crack was quickly created, and the other end was a scene of the next dimension.

The spaceships flew straight in, and everyone heard a crisp 'pop' sound, as though the shock outside caused the air within the spaceships to react.

Their vision blurred, and the next moment, they had arrived in another secondary dimension. In just a few seconds, the crack within the space wall closed and disappeared without a trace.

This was the conventional way of shuttling between secondary dimensions. The scenes of the secondary dimensions changed rapidly outside the porthole as the fleet jumped many times in succession before finally coming to a halt.

Such rapid shuttling brought a heavy load to the spacecraft, and at this time, the spaceships were all shrouded in violent space energy, distorting their very environment as though the engines were overheated.

On the star map, the fleet showed that they were finally on the same secondary dimension as the red dot, and the target was rapidly drawing closer.

Seeing this, Law quickly came to the front porthole, looking in the direction of the red dot. "Prepare to engage. Ready the Dimensional Exile Bullet."

As both of them stared out of the window, finally, a figure appeared and flew closer.

Just as he was about to initiate the attack, Law took a close look at the person and immediately changed his command.

"Wait, don't fire! This person doesn't look like Black Star. His aura is different from the one in our records."

Clotti was wearing a mechanical suit, covering his facial features, but he did not hide the energy fluctuations coming from his body.

The Energy Attribute of an Esper and a Mechanic were worlds apart, so at close range, Law discovered the significant difference in energy fluctuations.

Sensing the group in front of him, Clotti slowed down before coming to a stop in front of the fleet. He opened the wide area communication channel as he coldly spoke.

"Who are you guys? Why are you stopping me?"

"We're just a secondary dimension exploration team. We're not blocking you but rather happened to come across you." Law sent a reply back.

Observing the space energy distortion caused by the rapid jumps around the fleet, Clotti knew immediately that this group was lying, but he did not expose them. "Which organization does your exploration team belong to?"

"We're from a small civil organization and have come over to collect some specialties here. Seeing that you're shuttling through the secondary dimension alone, you must be a famous pinnacle Beyond Grade A. I wonder if we can have the honor of knowing your name," Law humbly said.

"I'm just an ordinary Beyond Grade A," Clotti blandly replied.

Law cursed in his heart.

F*ck you!

To think that a pinnacle Beyond Grade A like you is trying to pretend to be weak!

Law and Fay felt a headache coming. Both of them were Beyond Grade As, and if not for the fact that the detection radar was able to tell them their opponent's combat power, they would not be so humble.

This cross-plane life form detection radar was a device dedicated to the secondary dimensions, but its accuracy was quite lacking. The search conditions were already harsh enough, but both of them did not expect themselves to have such bad luck to run into another pinnacle Beyond Grade A.

The two of them were still unaware of Clotti's identity and did not wish to cause any problems.

"Your Excellency Beyond Grade A, if we accidentally offended you. We express our apologies. If there's nothing else, we'll take our leave first."

He did not even wait for Clotti to reply, immediately steering the fleet to turn around and move away.

Looking back, the duo discovered that Clotti did not chase them but rather stayed there and watched them leave.

"It seems like he's not planning to attack us." Law sighed.

"Most likely, he's not interested in us." Fay was secretly relieved.

"Let's get out of here." Law turned back to instruct the crew, "Mark this target, and don't bump into him again on accident. Reset the cross-plane detector, and search for another pinnacle Beyond Grade A signal."

The two of them were not interested in Clotti's identity at all. In the secondary dimensions, there were many crouching tigers and hidden dragons. The two of them were not there to cause trouble. Everything was done for their mission.

Clotti watched the fleet fly away without chasing them.

The secondary dimensions hid a lot of organizations that operated in secret, avoiding the rule of the three Universal Civilizations. They were a group of rats in the eyes of the three Universal Civilizations.

In Clotti's eyes, it was likely that this group was one of these hidden organizations. They had pursued the wrong target and ended up bumping into him instead.

The goal of his trip was Traveler, and since these guys knew how to back off, he could not be bothered to pick on them.

Glancing one last time at the direction the fleet departed, Clotti chose another direction away from them to travel, continuously shuttling.

Before long, Clotti stepped into his destination, the secondary dimension of Evil Convergence.

Looking around, the area seemed to be filled with a corrosive purplish-green energy. It moved lazily in waves, like the folds on a stomach wall. Bubbles of purple green gas occasionally popped out like flooding stomach juices, and it gave off the impression of being in the stomach of some weird creature.

From one of the inner walls of the Evil Convergence dimension then popped out a male's upper body, covered with purplish green mucus. This person was Traveler.

His skin was pale, and he exuded an evil and crazed temperament, as though he had entered a manic mode that prevented him from being rational.

The lower half of Traveler's body, which was still engulfed, continuously emitted energy rings that could be seen with the naked eye. The rings travelled through the purplish-green inner walls and were absorbed by the Evil Convergence dimension.

Clotti frowned. With his insight, it was not difficult to see that Traveler was spreading the essence of his own genes. He was technically having sex with this secondary dimension that almost seemed alive.

"Dark Lord Clotti, what a rare guest… I'm not sure why you're looking for me. Are you here to join the party? I certainly don't mind." Traveler laughed hoarsely.

Clotti remained stoic, indifferently replying, "You took part in the campaign to encircle and suppress the allies of the dynasty, committing a crime. I'm here today as your arbiter."

"So, you're here to kill me?" The corners of Traveler's mouth hooked upward in an eerie smile.

At this moment, from the inner walls of the Evil Convergence dimension emerged countless figures, forming an endless army.

The majority of them were dangerous characters from various dimensions. Among them, there were three figures exuding the aura of a Beyond Grade A, obviously helpers called forth by Traveler.

After divining that he would come across a formidable enemy, Traveler had used his contacts in the secondary dimension to set up an ambush.

"This is the Dark Lord of the main universe?" At this moment, one of the assisting Beyond Grade As stepped out with his arms folded and casually spoke. "Doesn't seem to be much, if he's that careless."

The other Beyond Grade A looked toward Traveler and solemnly said, "Remember our agreement. This time, we'll only help you drive out your enemy and not kill the Dark Lord. Otherwise, the Crimson Dynasty will pursue us."

Hearing this, Clotti realized that the three Beyond Grade As were powerhouses he had never seen before, and everything became clear at once.

It was impossible for the three Universal Civilizations to monitor the birth of every single Beyond Grade A; there would definitely be some who were unwilling to be recorded. As long as they kept concealing their identity and strength, not creating organizations or making a name for themselves, the three Universal Civilizations would not be able to discover their existence.

Quite a few of them also hid within the secondary dimension, never appearing in the main universe.

Some were neutrals that were worried about being persecuted, and there were also secret combatants belonging to other advanced civilizations, such as the Super Star Cluster Alliance. After the Tragedy of the Pinnacles, the Super Star Cluster Civilizations did not dare show their Beyond Grade As on the surface. Thus, their allies would all be sent into the secondary dimension to hide, preventing their existence from being discovered by the three Universal Civilizations.

At this moment, Traveler opened his arms wide, looking at Clotti as he laughed crazily.

"Hahaha, Dark Lord, you have immense combat strength in the main universe, but this is my home field. Can you even kill me?"

Clotti's expression remained calm, but his eyes glowed with a dark light.

He lightly lifted his arms, and dark energy gathered. He slowly said, "Since that's the case, I'll have to smash you apart with your home field."

…

Following the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, Han Xiao and Ames shuttled through various secondary dimensions one by one, seeing all kinds of bizarre sights. After a long time, they finally stopped moving.

"We're here. This is the nest of the Holy Light Particle," the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy excitedly said.

Han Xiao wandered around and saw that this was a dazzling world, with boundless land, mountains, forests, and rivers. But all of it was made out of materialized light, shiny and colorful.

The towering mountain peaks looked like blocks of shining giant gems, and the river was flowing with something resembling liquid light. Everything in this world was pure and flawless, just like a fairy tale.

"It's rather pretty. This is the first time I've come across such a secondary dimension." Ames could not help but rub her eyes in helplessness. "But it's a little piercing to the eyes."

"It is indeed." Han Xiao smirked before asking, "How do we find it?"

The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy laughed. "Haha, it's either sleeping or doesn't want to be seen. Leave it to me. It's very sensitive to my energy. So long as it senses me, it will become mad, so I can release my aura and arouse its natural reaction to take the initiative to come over.

Hearing this, Han Xiao could not help but glance at the Mysterious Energy Host in a weird manner.

What's with this tone? It sounds like you've trained it like a pet…

[1] The author wrote the actual characters for Coiling Dragon (the novel) inside, so I translated as such. Not sure if there’s supposed to be a sexual connotation to it but Coiling Dragon could also mean someone whose talent was hidden, ie Ames since Han Xiao never discovered that she was so lucky.Back

Chapter 1074: New System from the Holy Light Particle

The air was filled with light energy. In a Mage's words, the density of light element was extremely high in this place.

Han Xiao and Ames landed on a shallow land beside a river, the soil was made of colorful sand and felt just like a normal beach.

Ames squatted down, picked up a sand particle, and curiously observed this irregular-shaped solid subject. She then used a tiny bit of force on it. This sand particle cracked open and turned into fog-like light dust, slowly rising up.

Looking up, the sky was covered by a large sea of clouds, all formed by gaseous light particles. It was dreamy. There were light particles ascending from all places occasionally, and once a certain density was reached, this sea of clouds would turn into rain and pour the light dust onto the ground, forming new terrains. This process had constantly been repeating itself.

"It's beautiful," Ames complimented.

Han Xiao came to the river and lifted up a pond of liquid light particles. Looking at the gold-like liquid flowing through his fingers, he could not help but say, "This place is heavily light polluted."

"… Did you have to break the atmosphere like that?" Ames said with resignation.

"Come on, I'm just telling the truth."

Han Xiao's lips curled up. He summoned a few industrial mining devices and said casually, "This place is very unique and has high research value. I'm going to bring some materials back for experiments."

As he was speaking, he recorded the coordinates of this secondary dimension in the database so that he could come again. After some pondering, he decided to call this secondary dimension 'Nation of Light'.

After Han Xiao was done with all that, he then deployed some space stabilization anchors to prevent the Holy Light Particle from escaping. He patted the Mysterious Energy Host and said, "Okay, it's time to force the Holy Light Particle out."

The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy had been looking forward to this for a long time. As soon as he received the order, he instantly released waves of red energy into the ground without hesitation, forming an enormous expanding spider net.

When Han Xiao silently counted to 221, Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy finally reacted and said with an evil tone, "I've found it. It's sleeping as expected. Watch me wake it up!"

As soon as the sentence ended, Han Xiao and Ames felt the ground under them tremble.

The next moment, the entire space started trembling, mountains and all.

Boom!

Before the two of them could start to observe the surroundings, an enormous light fountain gushed out from under the ground, turning into a holy-looking mass of gold light. At its core was a blindingly bright sphere, as if there was another sun in the sky.

At this time, a red stream of Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was inside this white gold sphere of light. Like cold water poured into boiling oil, it triggered extremely violent reactions.

With the appearance of this mass of light, a furious and irritated energy impact expanded instantly.

"Mosanil! You attacked me again in my sleep! I'm definitely going to kill you today!"

"Narusus, doesn't my energy taste good? Did you miss it?" The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy chuckled.

Hearing this, Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

From this exchange, it sounded like this was not the first time…

Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy turned to look at Han Xiao and said with a smile, "This is the Holy Light Particle you guys talked about. It's in a bad mood after waking up. I'll leave the rest to you."

Primal Esper Ability Entities were all ancient and had their own names. 'Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy' and 'Holy Light Particle' were just the names the outside world assigned to them.

The Holy Light Particle hastily approached and finally realized the others. Seeing the Mysterious Energy Host, its rage vanished, switching right to joy.

"Hmm? You've been made into a puppet again? Hahaha, karma! You deserved it!"

"Don't be too happy. You're next." Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy smiled coldly.

The Holy Light Particle looked at Han Xiao and Ames. He then said with a displeased tone, "Humph, you're low as always, helping the enemies obtain my body, hoping to drag me down… The two of you kids from the main universe, I don't care how he tricked you, but I'm not interested in playing with you. Get the hell back to the main universe and stop bothering me."

Han Xiao did not mind. He took out a tin shaped device, tilted his head, and said, "Are you going to come in yourself, or do you want me to help you?"

Hearing this, the Holy Light Particle instantly became much brighter, giving off a tsunami-like energy shockwave as if it was giving its all. The entire space trembled slightly. With an over the top confident tone, he said, "I'm no weakling like Mosanil Are you prepared to face the consequences of trying to catch me‽"

Thirty seconds later…

"Stop stop stop, it hurts. I admit my defeat."

The Holy Light Particle had shrunk countless times and was contained in the tin like a pool of gold liquid. The containment device was buzzing with an electromagnetic field.

Han Xiao shook the device and made the Holy Light Particle stagger a few times.

"That's it?" Ames was speechless.

She had thought that the Holy Light Particle was very strong and was already prepared to fight. To her absolute surprise, after one slap from Han Xiao, the Holy Light Particle was already done for. It was way too weak.

Han Xiao, of course, was not surprised. In the face of a peak Beyond Grade A, Primal Esper Ability Entities would not be able to do much. He only found the fact that the Holy Light Particle was so confident strange.

Seeing his old friend get beaten up, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was now the one gloating. He moved beside the containment device and chuckled. "Welcome, with you as my company, I won't be lonely anymore."

"Mosanil! I'll murder you sooner or later!" The Holy Light Particle was in despair.

Han Xiao tapped on the glass of the containment device and interrupted them. "You'll have plenty of time to communicate in the future. Answer my question first. What abilities do you have?"

The Holy Light Particle said with rage, "I'm telling you, I won't give in as easily as Mosanil. Even if you torture me, I won't…"

Thirty seconds later…

The Holy Light Particle obediently lay at the bottom of the containment device, shivering while explaining his abilities.

"My most basic abilities are physique enhancement, superspeed flight, and dimension crossing. I can also give others the power of holy light. I have the ability to attack as well. My host can use me to punish evil. There are two criteria for judging what or who's evil. One is the belief of my host, and the other is the target's own conscience and understanding of their crimes. The more severe the crime, the stronger the power of the punishment will be… Also, I can purify filth, helping the target to get rid of related negative states, as well as heal to a certain extent…"

The Holy Light Particle poured everything out.

As Han Xiao nodded and listened, he also complained about the Holy Light Particle in his mind. From just his name, he thought this guy would be pure and virtuous, only to realize he changed his attitude instantly after he got beaten up. He was just as shameless as Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. Was it because they had lived too long?

In terms of punishing evil and purifying filth, the abilities of the Holy Light Particle did indeed match its 'holy' style. However, the criteria were quite emotionally dependent. Its strength would only be maximized when its host was a person of justice with strong beliefs.

Compared to all that, what Han Xiao cared more about was its ability to gift others the power of holy light. After some questioning, he was pleasantly surprised.

Holy light itself was considered a type of multi-dimensional energy. It was not rare and could be used by both high-level Mechanics and Mages. It had mind energy characteristics. However, although holy light was not rare, it was not something ordinary people could use.

The Holy Light Particle, however, could gift any intelligent species 'Holy Light Seed'. As long as the target trained hard, fertilized the seed with beliefs and determination to make it blossom, the target would have control of holy light energy, which could be further enhanced. This meant that the Holy Light Particle could provide an extra class with growth potential, allowing ordinary people to have power from nothing, and Supers could obtain this ability.

However, since the requirement was that one had to obtain 'Holy Light Seed' and the gifted energy could be retrieved by Holy Light Particle, it had limited uses and was not included in the five Super classes. It was more like a subclass.

From the Holy Light Particle, Han Xiao came to know that back when the Holy Light Particle had a host, it used a method to enhance its host's strength—it retrieved the matured Holy Light Seed from others. This was equivalent to taking the fruits of hard work from others and making all of their hard work its own.

After hearing its experience, the way Han Xiao looked at the Holy Light Particle became much friendlier.

Not bad, didn't expect you to be in the leek industry too.

Han Xiao believed in 'seeing is believing', so he told the unwilling Holy Light Particle to use this ability on him. A stream of warm gold energy flowed into his body, and a notification popped up on the interface.

You have received ability [Holy Light Seed].

[Holy Light Seed]: Passive ability. This is the base of the power of holy light. It has to be nurtured by belief. After maturing, you can awaken subclass [Holy Light Emissary]. Belief Value required 0/5000. (Belief Value can be increased through meditating, mind training, punishing criminals, and so on.)

I see… This ability has a very high strategic value. If the energy given out isn't retrieved, I can turn many ordinary people who don't have the talent to become Supers into holy light warriors. This way, the fundamental combat capability of the army will increase tremendously.

This was a surprise. Maybe he could even sell this to the players. It seemed to have quite a high potential.

However, Evans did not display this ability in his previous life, so it probably had some limits.

After some questioning, Han Xiao got the answer.

As expected, every Holy Light Seed was a tiny bit of core essence granted by the Holy Light Particle, and its core energy recovered at a very slow speed. If he used too much, he would be heavily damaged together with its host.

"I seem to have a way to make its energy recover quickly…" Han Xiao pondered.

He had some ideas, but this was not the time to test them, so he kept the containment device.

Han Xiao also told the Holy Light Particle to take back the Holy Light Seed in him. He only asked for it to test it; he did not need this subclass himself.

According to his original thoughts, he wanted to also make a host for the Holy Light Particle. However, the way he looked at it now, that might not be the best choice.

Han Xiao looked at the interface. [The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy's Arch Enemy] was already shown as complete.

He received 2.4 billion EXP and two Character Summon Cards. As expected, they were from the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and Holy Light Particle. The abilities were not too rare; they were the ability to suck the energy out of a planet's core and Holy Flame Judgement. Although the two of them were already in his hands, these two Character Summon Cards were better than nothing.

What Han Xiao was more concerned about was the newly activated milestone mission [Primal Esper Ability Collector].

[Primal Esper Ability Collector (Unactivated)]: Activation requirement—Have at least 4 Primal Esper Ability Entities. Current progress 2/4.

Effects: When you fight Espers, all your attributes will increase slightly. 12% – 20% damage reduction from Espers.

Reward: [The Third Sanctum] Ability Fragment * 1

Han Xiao was stunned.

The Third Sanctum? What on earth is this? I seem to remember that I also have the Ability Fragment of the First Sanctum? Could these be connected?

This question had been troubling him for quite some time, but he had not found any clues.

He suppressed the curiosity in his heart and looked at the effects of the milestone. It was targeted at Espers and was quite useful.

The mission requirement is to have four Primal Esper Ability Entities, which means I will need two more. That is quite difficult, mainly because they're hard to find. I'll just try my best…

As he had expected, dealing with the Holy Light Particle was a piece of cake. Once business was done, Han Xiao went sightseeing with Ames in the Nation of Light for a while, and when he had collected enough sample material, the two of them left this secondary dimension and headed for the next stop—Land of Dead Silence.

…

As lights flickered, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy brought Han Xiao and Ames to the Land of Dead Silence following the coordinates from Kirkmond.

After seeing the environment there, Han Xiao could not help but exclaim, "Wow, this place really does look quite scary."

This secondary dimension had only dark colors, the spatial wall had countless holes. Violent chaotic space streams continuously invaded and raged. The sky was filled with infinite space storms flickering in dark blue and purple. Below them was a black desolate desert. Many places were devoured by chaotic space streams and turned into the void. This land was torn into separated broken islands.

Having felt something, Han Xiao took out the revive token he had been wearing and realized it was heating up—it reacted to this place as expected.

"This means that the Land of Dead Silence really is connected to Hila…"

Han Xiao released his senses and searched the entire secondary dimension, only to find nothing special.

Just as Kirkmond said, this secondary dimension was close to dying. There was nothing there.

This time, Ames shook her head and said, "Looks like Hila will have to come here personally to notice something."

Han Xiao nodded in agreement. Hila's ability probably had some resonance with the Land of Dead Silence and might be able to activate some unique event. Although he was stronger, he clearly did not meet the requirements.

"At least we investigated the place for her, so it'll be easier for her to come next time." Han Xiao recorded the coordinates of this dimension in the database.

Just as the two of them were about to leave, a powerful life energy source suddenly appeared out of nowhere and entered the range of their senses.

The two of them looked over and saw a silhouette covered in wounds falling out of a chaotic space stream, coincidentally into the space wall hole of the Land of Dead Silence.

Ames blinked and wondered, "Hmm? This person looks somewhat familiar…"

…

At the same time…

"Your Excellencies, the radar has locked onto the target!"

Inside the spaceship command room, Law and Fay quickly looked at the map.

"This isn't the same person we met earlier, right?"

"No, he's in another secondary dimension. This is the second peak Beyond Grade A signal detected."

After making sure they were not mistaken, Law instantly ordered, "Okay, lock onto the new target and advance at full speed!"

…

In Evil Convergence…

God only knew what violent treatment the space wall received. Like a balloon, it expanded and cracked from within, causing this secondary dimension to lose all its defenses. The green evil energy everywhere that was full of life earlier looked like it had lost all energy as it was blown away by the chaotic space stream together with all the bodies here, disappearing without a trace.

This special secondary dimension that gave birth to lives had now turned into a wreckage with only silence and death. It was quickly dying.

Clotti shattered the head of the last Beyond Grade A, turned up to look at the space storm raging around him, and frowned. He was not satisfied with his performance.

"It's been too long since I've fought. I've really gotten rusty and accidentally used too much strength. He managed to escape with the chaotic space stream."

Chapter 1075: Escaping from the Tiger's Den into the Wolf's Nest

"Hahaha, I've escaped!"

A green ball of light floated in the space storm. It was Traveler, who was protecting himself with a magic shield.

At this point of time, he was no longer in the state of madness affected by Evil Convergence. Although his skin was still pale, he did not give off an evil vibe anymore. His mental state had also returned to normal, only filled with fear and frustration.

In order to ambush Clotti, Traveler had gathered the friends he had made in the secondary dimension in the past. He had thought that with a total of four Beyond Grade As, with the help of the fact that they were in the Evil Convergence secondary dimension, they would be able to force Dark Lord away at the very least.

However, reality slapped him right on his cheeks.

Clotti was way too strong. He had a Super High Risk Esper Ability to begin with, and it had evolved to a very high level. His area damage was explosive. Through simulating the phenomenon of a mini big bang with his dark energy, he thrashed the entire Evil Convergence secondary dimension and broke the space wall from within.

If he was just powerful by himself, the four of them would still have had the chance to escape. However, what gave Traveler the most despair was the fact that Clotti had not just one but many Universal Treasures!

As a peak Beyond Grade A directly under the dynasty's command and the personal guard of the Ruler, Clotti was not short on Universal Treasures. To make his mission easier, the dynasty had given him many Universal Treasures to use.

Before executing the mission, Clotti had taken five Universal Treasures from the dynasty's stash, increasing his strength by a large extent. When he went all out, he easily killed three Beyond Grade As who had yet to surpass the 52,000 Energy Rank.

Traveler was the only one who had escaped with the help of the chaotic space stream when his wife, the Evil Convergence secondary dimension, was being murdered.

Without Evil Convergence, his strength had plummeted back to the level of ordinary Beyond Grade As. His hard work over all these years had gone right down the drain. His heart was hurting so much it felt like someone was suffocating it.

However, one good thing was that the enemy could no longer track him using Evil Convergence. As long as he hid well, he would be safe.

"As long as I'm alive, it means I still have a chance."

Traveler's heart was filled with the relief of surviving a disaster.

Furthermore, there was still hope of rising again…

Traveler lowered his head and opened his palm. An irregular shaped greenish-purple fragment lay quietly in his hands like a piece of glass.

This was the core fragment of Evil Convergence. As long as he planted it in another secondary dimension with a special method, there would be a chance for it to regrow into a new Evil Convergence. Only, it would take a very long time.

"All I have to do is avoid the Crimson Dynasty's pursuit. When they give up, I'll have more than enough time to recover. Looks like I'll have to hide in the secondary dimensions for decades or maybe even a century… Fortunately, I still have a long life span."

Traveler breathed a sigh of relief, cleared the shadow of failure, and motivated himself.

Surviving a disaster meant that fortune was ahead!

At this time, inside the space storm, three cracks in the space wall suddenly appeared. It was unknown which secondary dimensions they led to.

Inside space storms, space wall cracks were the only exits, or one would be forever lost inside chaotic space streams.

"What a surprise to see exits so soon. Looks like my luck is about to change for the better." Traveler's eyes sparkled. Without hesitation, he directly chose one of the cracks and flew right in.

The next moment, the world in front of him changed into a secondary dimension filled with countless holes. Inside it were countless shattered black islands. It was dead silent.

Traveler passed through the space wall and fell into this secondary dimension. Before he could be glad about escaping death, he immediately saw a man and a woman inside the secondary dimension looking up at him. They were not wearing helmets.

When he saw their appearances, Traveler's smile turned stiff on his face, and sweat ran down his forehead.

Black Star and Dragon Emperor!

What the hell? Why are the two of them here?

I just escaped from one, now I've run into two more‽

Traveler's eyes almost popped out. Before he could think of anything else, he immediately stopped his falling body and quickly returned the way he had come from, toward the chaotic space stream above.

"Don't run!" Ames reacted instantly. She reached out and pulled. A powerful force field grabbed onto Traveler's body and pulled him to her.

Traveler was heavily injured to begin with. Furthermore, losing Evil Convergence had damaged him even more. He was in an extremely horrible state at this point and could not escape Ames' force field at all.

"I can't fall here!" Traveler ignored all consequences and used secret techniques to stimulate his exhausted mind and body. He forcefully started to generate magic energy and cast spells.

A teleportation gate started appearing beside him.

However, before he finished casting the spell, a sudden movement restricting force field interrupted his channeling.

Below him, Ames' eyes that were usually lazy turned sharp and stared at Traveler. A force field overflowed from her brows.

Buzz!

Force Field: Gaze of the Dragon!

Traveler's body was instantly fixed in midair!

Before he could respond, in the blink of an eye, Ames appeared before him using Void Travel. She raised her hand and softly pressed on his forehead.

The next second, a raging force field gushed out from Ames' palm into Traveler's body.

Force Field—Stress Tear Down!

The force field inside Traveler's body pulled him in all directions, forming countless forces that reacted with each other.

Snap!

Countless sounds of bones cracking and muscles being torn apart sounded in Traveler's body. An immense sense of agony erupted and flooded every single one of his nerves, so much so that he could not even control the contorted expression on his face.

Hong!

Flowers of blood exploded from every part of his body. He let out silent screams with his mouth opened wide as he bathed in blood.

His heavy injuries immediately got even worse.

This time, with coldness in her eyes, Ames raised one leg. A highly condensed force field formed an extremely sharp cutting force on her calf as she slashed down.

Force Field—Dragon Axe!

Swoosh!

Ames's long leg slashed down from Traveler's shoulder. Like a hot knife cutting through butter, Traveler's entire arm was cut away!

She did not give Traveler any chance to respond. Following the momentum, she stepped on Traveler's neck and dashed down, falling onto a shattered black island below, pressing the barely alive Traveler under her foot.

Only this time did Han Xiao slowly fly over and look at the fearsome expression on Ames' face with surprise.

"How come you're so violent all of a sudden? It's not like you."

Without turning around, Ames stared at the Traveler below her foot and coldly said, "When Hila was being attacked, he came to attack Black Star Palace. I did not know what was going on; only afterward did I roughly guess that he wanted to lure your Lord's Avatar out to divert your energy. However, you planned ahead and told me to stay in Black Star Palace, which prevented it from happening."

Facing Traveler, Ames did not hold back at all. Not only because Traveler was on the side of those enemies who tried to kill Hila but also because these people had forced Han Xiao to pay the price of burning his potential. From the way she looked at it, Han Xiao did not talk about it because he did not want Hila to feel bad. Ames understood Han Xiao's intentions, but she never forgot it.

In her eyes, this trip to the secondary dimension was mainly to stroll with Han Xiao, but part of it was also to look for Traveler and make him pay.

Once they met, Ames immediately went all out without hesitation.

Han Xiao tutted, looked at the heavily injured Traveler on the ground, and chuckled. "Yoho, what a lucky day it is today. I was just thinking about looking for you, but you came right to me."

Veins were exposed on Traveler's frustration- and hatred-filled face.

After finally getting out of Dark Lord's nightmare, he came right to Black Star's barrel.

He had escaped a tiger's den and entered a wolf's nest!

After such extreme fluctuations in his mood, Traveler was completely exhausted and did not even have the energy to complain about how unfair fate was to him.

Being so unlucky, he had nothing to say and could only let out a long sigh in his mind.

This means the world wants me dead!

Han Xiao looked at the wounds caused by Dark Lord on Traveler's body and asked curiously, "Who did you meet? How did you end up so heavily injured?"

Traveler kept silent and looked like he was not afraid of death. When he was not affected by Evil Convergence, he was quite sane. Since he knew he would not have the slightest chance of surviving, he was not planning to beg for mercy.

"Yo, you've got quite the backbone." Han Xiao chuckled. "However, I wonder how the Star Arc Civilization will react to your death. You don't have to deny it. Since I can accurately name the civilization you work for, I'd have enough proof for it.

The moment Han Xiao said that, the expression on Traveler's face changed drastically into disbelief as he looked at Han Xiao.

When he moved in the outside world, he had always disguised himself as a neutral Beyond Grade A who accepted hires from different civilizations, all to cover the fact that he belonged to a Super Star Cluster civilization. His true identity had always been a secret. The Star Arc Civilization was indeed the Super Star Cluster civilization he secretly worked for, and the outside world had no idea.

This way, no matter what he did, nothing would be connected to his civilization. This was also the reason he could mess around without having to worry.

However, the identity he had always been hiding was suddenly exposed by Han Xiao. He immediately lost his cool and panicked.

Subconsciously, he wanted to deny it, but having heard Han Xiao's certain tone and seeing his expression, it was clear that this was not a trick. He did indeed have hard proof.

"H-how did you…"

"How did I know?"

Han Xiao finished his sentence, smirked, and said, "Sorokin told me."

Initially, he was just throwing the blame on someone else out of habit. However, Traveler's reaction surprised him.

"I knew it!" Traveler clenched his teeth. "He noticed something. The upper echelons shouldn't have worked with him!"

Hmm? Sorokin really is involved in this too? Han Xiao was the one who was slightly shocked this time.

He had thought that it was the Super Star Cluster civilization that wanted to escalate the conflict between the three Universal Civilizations. He did not expect Sorokin to be related to Traveler coming to attack Black Star Palace.

Looks like I've accidentally discovered some interesting information…

On the surface, Han Xiao's expression remained the same as he smiled and said, "Since I know your identity, you'd better tell me everything from the beginning. Otherwise, you know the consequences. The Star Arc Civilization will be blamed for all of this. I, however, might be able to help you with that."

If Traveler was all alone, he would be able to face death without any worries. However, according to the information Han Xiao had from his previous life, Traveler was absolutely loyal to the Star Arc Civilization. Now that what he cared about most was exposed, Han Xiao had control of his weakness.

Furthermore, Traveler hated Sorokin deeply for telling this to Black Star and was worried he might tell even more people. Hence, he told the truth about the agreement he had with Sorokin.

This was not just compromising. He was also trying to use this to direct Black Star's hate toward Sorokin. He was hoping this would indirectly lead to Han Xiao killing Sorokin.

Traveler explained everything truthfully from the start. Only then did Han Xiao see the full picture of this incident. He caressed his chin and said with a deep voice, "Sorokin… so you're the one who convinced the Super Star Cluster Alliance. Plus, you're on the opposite side of the united Beyond Grade A battlefront…"

Connecting the information Traveler gave with the limited information he had from his previous life, Han Xiao roughly understood Sorokin's true intentions.

All that about maintaining balance of the universe and Beyond Grade As knowing when to be satisfied, he was just hiding his own ambition.

There were two paths to higher power. One was to become stronger and step into the higher territory; the other was to reduce the number of competitors. Sorokin took the latter approach. From the way Han Xiao looked at it, this guy would love for the universe to have fewer than ten Beyond Grade As. He basically wanted to have all the power alone.

The fewer high-level combatants, the less resistance he would face, which led to him wanting to reduce the numbers of Beyond Grade As. Hence, he used factions' differences to trigger conflicts between Beyond Grade As.

Han Xiao had always been wary of Sorokin. Only, he never really knew his goals for sure. Now that he finally knew about Sorokin's goal, this meant that this powerful foe who was hiding in the dark plotting conspiracies was exposed, and he would be able to make more comprehensive preparations against him. Having thought of that, he was in a much better mood.

Putting all those thoughts behind him, Han Xiao pointed at Traveler's wounds and asked, "What about your wounds? Who's chasing you?"

Traveler glared at Han Xiao with sorrow and rage. He clenched his teeth and said, "Dark Lord from your Crimson Dynasty!"

"Hmm? He's here too?" Han Xiao was surprised. As he recalled that Dark Lord had just quit from being the captain of the Ruler's personal guards, it occurred to him.

It seemed the Dynasty Ruler was not happy about the temporary cooperation between the federation and the church. Plus, there were the issues surrounding the Flickering World and the Evolutionary Totems. She wanted to set an example for high-level combatants. Hence, she sent Dark Lord after the enemy to send a warning to those organizations with ulterior motives… Speaking of which, to peak Beyond Grade As at Dark Lord's level, the position of personal guard captain was more of a chain than a benefit.

Hearing how Clotti easily shattered Traveler's ambush, Han Xiao could not help but praise him.

Han Xiao thought for a while and activated the King mechanical suit's communication system. He found the Crimson Dynasty's A000 Outpost Station and called in.

Unlike the main universe, the secondary dimension was not covered by the quantum network, so many areas had no signal. However, Han Xiao took a super long-range quantum base station with him everywhere he went, so this was not a problem. Clotti also wore the dynasty's specially-made mechanical suit that was equipped with a fixed directional communication device that allowed him to contact the dynasty's outpost station any time. This also prevented him from going missing. Hence, Han Xiao decided to call the dynasty's outpost station and ask them to direct the call to Clotti.

Since Traveler was Dark Lord's mission target, Han Xiao felt that he had to notify Clotti about it, or he would think Traveler had escaped and would continue to waste energy in the secondary dimensions searching for him.

After a while, the communication finally went through. Clotti's remote projection appeared in front of him. He was frowning.

"Black Star, what are you calling for?"

They were both pillars of the dynasty, but due to the differences in their positions and identities, the communication between them had been very limited. The relationship was also not close, limited to just work colleagues.

"Traveler is here with me. I've captured him…"

Han Xiao briefly explained the situation.

After Han Xiao finished, Clotti replied with very few words. "I'll go there to confirm."

"Okay." Han Xiao paused and sent the coordinates to Dark Lord.

Clotti nodded and slowly said, "By the way, when Traveler escaped, he took a core fragment of Evil Convergence. Search carefully. It should still be in his hands."

Then, his remote projection disappeared as he hung up the call, showing no intention of chatting.

"How unfriendly," Han Xiao murmured. He then turned to look at Traveler, extended his hand, and said, "Core fragment, take it out."

Traveler clenched his teeth, reluctantly took out Evil Convergence's core fragment, and handed it over to Han Xiao like giving his wife away.

Han Xiao placed it in his hand.

This was the key for Traveler to summon Evil Convergence, like the lamp core of the Shadow Lantern. With the core fragment as the medium, one could use the special energy of the respective secondary dimension.

However, now the Evil Convergence was no more, this core fragment could only be used as the tinder. However, knowing the crazed state Traveler was in when he used it, he had no plans to become the new husband of Evil Convergence.

Han Xiao kept this loot and thought about how to deal with Traveler.

According to him, the best was, of course, to seal him in Spacetime Amber. However, Dark Lord's mission was to kill him, and it did not seem like Ames would be satisfied with that result either.

Buzz!

As he was thinking, the senses of all three of them felt the appearance of a new signal.

The three of them looked over simultaneously and saw that the space wall in the distance had cracked open, and a small fleet came out of it.

Before the three of them had time to think, this fleet briefly adjusted its direction and turned right toward the three of them. It was clear that they were not there on friendly terms.

Inside the main ship command room, Law stared at the confused Han Xiao on the screen and yelled, "We're correct this time. That's Black Star! All fleets, lock onto the target. Prepare to fire!"

Chapter 1076: An Organization That Should Not Have Appeared in This Era

"Did these people just happen to pass by, or are they here for us? Who are they even?"

Han Xiao looked at this quickly approaching fleet. There were no organizations' symbols on their spaceships, so their identity was unknown. Han Xiao was confused.

Seeing that the enemies did not plan to stop, Han Xiao was prepared to fight.

However, as he was just about to attack, a crack opened at the space wall not far away again—Clotti had arrived.

The next moment, this fleet stopped moving.

"What's going on with this fleet?"

Han Xiao looked at this fleet wondering. This time, Clotti flew over, so he turned to him and greeted him.

"Your Excellency Dark Lord."

"Hmm, Black Star." Clotti nodded slightly. He then turned to look at the barely alive Traveler under Ames' foot and asked, "How did you meet him?"

"Just a coincidence…"

Han Xiao briefly explained what had happened.

After Clotti heard the story, even his eyes slightly twitched on his usually expressionless face as he softly said, "Well, that's really unfortunate."

After he thrashed the Evil Convergence, he had lost track of Traveler. He was just thinking about how he was going to continue chasing after Traveler, but to his surprise, Traveler was so unlucky he met Black Star right after.

He was not curious about why Han Xiao was there. Clotti was not concerned about other Beyond Grade As' private matters.

"I heard your mission is to kill him?" Han Xiao asked.

Clotti nodded. "Traveler is just one target. The Ruler's order is to kill if capturing isn't possible. If captured, he will be publicly executed, which will be broadcast live to the entire universe… Oh, and also interrogate who hired him."

"You have other hunting targets too?"

Clotti glanced at him and said, "Just some neutral Beyond Grade As who like to be mercenaries."

"Are they related to the attack on Hila?" Han Xiao was curious.

"Whatever the dynasty says." Clotti's tone was completely carefree.

Han Xiao was speechless. Those neutral Beyond Grade As who were marked as targets were most probably innocent in this matter, but unluckily for them, they became the dynasty's tools to set an example.

Dark Lord was indeed loyal to the dynasty; he showed no care for it at all. The difficult environment these neutral Beyond Grade As lived in could be seen clearly from this matter.

Han Xiao then thought of the Super Star Cluster civilizations and understood. The targets the dynasty had chosen were probably those who were hired by the Super Star Cluster Alliance. Using the attack on Hila as an excuse, the dynasty clearly decided to intimidate the others and cut away the Super Star Cluster Alliance's feathers.

At the same time, they might hope to imitate the Tragedy Of The Pinnacles to reduce the number of Beyond Grade As using the incident as an excuse.

Han Xiao shook his head, changed the topic, and said, "I interrogated him earlier and got the identity of who's behind this."

"Who?"

The communication between the two of them was not private; Traveler heard it too. His expression changed instantly as he stared at Han Xiao nervously, afraid he would spit out the Star Arc Civilization.

However, he saw Han Xiao give him a look.

Traveler instantly understood and hastily interrupted him.

"Sorokin! He hired me to attack Black Star Palace to divert Black Star's attention and provide indirect assistance to the federation and the church!"

"Him? Isn't he just a pure businessman?" Clotti frowned and was a little surprised. He glanced at Han Xiao and said, "Do you think that's believable?"

"I think it's quite believable. Traveler is just a neutral mercenary; he wouldn't attack me out of nowhere."

Han Xiao smiled.

The Star Arc Civilization was indeed related, but Han Xiao had signaled Traveler to hide his identity and blame everything on Sorokin. This way, the dynasty's hatred would not be diverted and would all go to Sorokin.

Anyway, Sorokin was actually involved, so there would definitely be proof.

Although the Great Mechanic Han was a soon-to-be shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group, he would not help Sorokin just for the sake of dividends. Furthermore, he only just knew that he was secretly plotting against him.

Hence, he wanted to borrow the Crimson Dynasty's power to cause some trouble for Sorokin, at least make the upper echelons be cautious about that guy.

"… I'll tell the Ruler. However, I'll still have to take Traveler back for further interrogation," Clotti said.

Han Xiao nodded, turned, and patted Ames' thigh, signaling her to raise her leg. Then, he took out the Spacetime Amber and sealed Traveler up.

While doing this, Han Xiao pointed at the fleet not far away that was trying to stay unnoticed.

"By the way, I've been meaning to ask, are they your troops?"

Hearing this, Clotti was stunned for a moment. "I thought they were your men."

He noticed that this fleet was the fleet he had just met earlier as soon as he arrived. Seeing that Han Xiao was together with this fleet, he had thought they were on the same side and that he misunderstood earlier, so he did not pay much attention.

However, from Han Xiao's perspective, he only gave the coordinates to Dark Lord, and this fleet arrived right before Dark Lord. Hence, he thought this fleet belonged to him.

Both of them had thought this fleet belonged to the other person. Only then did they realize it was a third party.

Having realized that, Clotti opened the public channel and yelled, "Who are you? Why are you following me‽"

From the way he looked at it, having met them twice, the only explanation was that they were following him.

At this time, inside the command room of the fleet, Law and Fay were both going mad.

Initially, they had locked onto Black Star and were just about to attack. However, to their absolute surprise, the first peak Beyond Grade A they marked on their radar moved at the last second and arrived in this secondary dimension.

This sudden situation messed up their plan. The two of them hastily told the fleet to stop and did not dare fire.

Seeing that Black Star was on the same side as the other peak Beyond Grade A, the two of them realized how tough the situation was. If they attacked, things would become much more difficult, and there would be a lot of uncertainties.

They only wanted to attack when Han Xiao was alone, so they wanted to make an excuse and retreat to find another opportunity.

Hearing Clotti's question, Law had no choice but to use the excuse he gave when they first met.

"Your Excellency Beyond Grade A, we didn't expect to meet you again. We only came here to explore because we detected special energy here, but we never thought it would be you again. We'll leave now."

Then, Law was just about to tell the fleet to turn around and leave, but this time, Clotti stopped them and said with a cold tone, "Never mind one time, but this is the second time, and you're still using the same excuse. Do you think I'll believe you?"

Clotti did not believe in coincidences. He had already suspected their identity earlier, but back then, his focus had been on the mission, and he did not want to get involved in meaningless trouble. Now, however, Traveler was already dealt with, so he did not plan to let this mysterious fleet go again.

"It really is a coincidence. We're just a civilian exploration team…" Law had no choice but to continue faking it.

"Then it'll be easy. Stop your ships and let us search them. If there really isn't a problem, I'll let you leave," Clotti said with a deep voice.

Hearing this, Law and Fay exchanged looks and communicated with each other telepathically.

"What should we do now? They won't let us go easily. Are we really going to let them into our ships?"

"You know that's impossible."

"Then it looks like we have no choice…"

The two of them were both in an extremely bad mood. They completely did not want to attack in this kind of situation.

However, they had already exposed themselves, and there was no way they could let them board their ships.

Law clenched his teeth and slammed the table.

"Fire!"

…

After Clotti proposed to board and investigate, this mysterious fleet suddenly stopped responding.

After waiting for a few seconds, seeing that they were still silent, Clotti said with an even more serious tone, "This is your last warning. If you do not reply within ten seconds, I will crush you!"

Han Xiao was watching Clotti communicate with this mysterious fleet. He thought that they had come for Dark Lord, so he just watched on.

Hearing Clotti's warning, Han Xiao thought about it and said, "No need to attack. I can hack into those spaceships and control them, search through their database, and find out who they are."

Clotti pondered for two seconds, nodded, and said, "Alright, then I'll trouble you too…"

Before his sentence finished, a sudden change occurred!

The few battleships suddenly fired without any warnings. Cone-shaped solid bullets shot out and headed to the few of them, dragging long paths of flame behind.

"Solid bullets?"

Although the regular weapons at his level had already become dark energy and psionic energy blasters, Han Xiao did not underestimate solid bullets. This was because since they had the ability to travel between secondary dimensions, the gunpowder inside those solid bullets would definitely not be ordinary.

Seeing this, Ames raised her hand and locked all the bullets in midair with her force field.

Seeing that the opponents had attacked, Han Xiao immediately activated Virtual Intrusion and attacked the database of these spaceships without hesitation.

However, the instant Han Xiao's data needle penetrated the spaceships' artificial intelligence, an invisible force flowed into his brain through the quantum network connection.

Boom!

A powerful shock exploded in his mind, his memory palace suddenly collapsed. Countless sheets of paper representing memories turned into tornados and spun violently.

From Han Xiao's perspective, countless memory fragments flashed past his mind, and he could not maintain his usual thoughts.

At the same time, a notification popped up on the interface.

You have been hacked by [Memory Formatting Virus—Quantum Network Type].

Your class is detected to be [Virtual Mechanic].

[Memory Formatting Virus—Quantum Network Type] has 200% damage on you.

"This is…"

Shocked, Han Xiao felt like the world was spinning.

This virus had entered his quantum soul. It was no ordinary debuff. It had messed up his mind on the virtual level, as if an ill-mannered kid had come into his house and flipped around all of his neatly arranged stuff. Han Xiao had no choice but to focus on resisting it.

Seeing his situation, Clotti's eyes became serious. Dark energy gathered as he launched an attack.

However, the next moment, the tons of [Dimensional Exile Bullet] that were fixed in midair by Ames exploded, releasing expanding chaotic space streams, and devoured Clotti's attack, transferring it to God knew where.

Not only that, but those chaotic space streams were also tearing the space wall of this Land of Dead Silence, creating more holes.

Seeing this, Ames immediately targeted her force field at those spaceships.

However, the next moment, Fay acted from within the main ship. A fog-like protective shield expanded with her in the center and guarded the fleet, blocking Ames' force field, clashing with Ames' strength. Ames was unable to instantly destroy the spaceships.

The next moment, a special disc-shaped device extended from the head of the main ship that was prepared since long ago. It looked like some kind of radar to enhance a certain waveform. It suddenly shook and released a ring of shockwave.

Buzz!

This shockwave passed through Clotti, Han Xiao, and Ames. The three of them suddenly became stiff. The energy they could manipulate any way they wanted usually suddenly started to riot, making controlling their own body much more difficult. It was as if every single cell in their body was fighting against their mind.

You have been affected by [High Level Life Form Energy Disorder Shockwave—Beyond Grade A Frequency Type].

Your total level is detected to be Lv.320.

[High Level Life Form Energy Disorder Shockwave—Beyond Grade A Frequency Type] has a 320% effect on you.

"It worked. We don't have much time!"

Law raised his arm, and his sleeves slid down, exposing an arm guard style metal device on his wrist. This was a special device made to capture Primal Esper Ability Entities. He then pointed it at the Mysterious Energy Host.

Ka-cha!

As if it had suddenly gained a ton of energy, Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy suddenly expanded and destroyed the Mysterious Energy Host from within, instantly escaping.

However, before it could move, an invisible force grabbed onto its body, and it flew uncontrollably toward the fleet.

On the other side, the spaceships were also doing something. The second wave of Dimensional Exile Bullets was shot toward the three of them. Clotti barely used his Esper Ability to form a shield around his body.

However, the chaotic space stream devoured Clotti entirely together with his shield, and he disappeared.

At this crucial moment, Han Xiao barely suppressed the virus in his mind, tried his best, and grabbed Ames' arm. He activated Void Travel and got out of the range of the Dimensional Exile Bullets.

The next moment, he raised his hand and released a restraining force field, grabbing onto Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy's body.

Hu!

Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was like a piece of cloth being pulled from two opposite directions.

Law's tone became hasty. "Black Star is recovering. We can't linger any longer, or we'll certainly die. Take as much as possible!"

Then, his hand sign changed as he activated another function of the device on his wrist, slashing off a small part of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy's body.

Like being absorbed by a black hole, this portion of energy flowed into Law's arm guard.

"Quickly, go!"

After this, the fleet shot one Dimensional Exile Bullet that exploded as soon as it left the barrel. The chaotic space stream devoured the fleet, and it disappeared without a trace.

Only after close to a minute did Ames slowly start to regain control of her body. She took a deep breath and said with a shocked tone, "What were those attacks?"

"They are all special technology invented through Primal Esper Ability Entities…"

Without exterior interference, Han Xiao had already cleared out most of the virus and rearranged his memory palace. He was looking grave.

From the very start, all this fleet used was technology, yet the three of them were forced into an extremely passive state. Han Xiao had a very heavy impression of this special technology, as it had appeared in his previous life.

Be it the Memory Formatting Virus, Dimensional Exile Bullet, or the High Level Life Form Energy Disorder Shockwave, they were all invented through studying different Primal Esper Ability Entities. They had many different uses.

Among them, the Dimensional Exile Bullet had no effects in the main universe, since the space structure of the main universe was completely different from the secondary dimensions. However, in the secondary dimensions, this was powerful technology that could be used in many ways, including splitting up the battlefield, escaping, and damaging secondary dimensions.

The Memory Formatting Virus was a technological product that affected one's mind. It came from Primal Esper Ability Entities and was improved to be used through the quantum network. It was specially targeted at Virtual Intrusions and took effect when Han Xiao was taken by surprise.

The High Level Life Form Energy Disorder Shockwave mainly targeted strong individuals. The higher the target's Energy Rank, the more effective it would be. It was basically using an enemy's own energy against them. However, Beyond Grade As had very high adaptability, so the effect of the High Level Life Form Energy Disorder Shockwave would decrease every time it was used on the same target, as the cells in their bodies had adapted to its effects.

The enemies were focused on studying Primal Esper Ability Entities, so their containment ability was more advanced. Through stimulating Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, the Mysterious Energy Host was broken, and they were able to snatch part of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy's energy.

No matter how strong Supers were, they were still life forms. Since they were life forms, there were ways to deal with them. No one could be considered invincible. Although the technology of the three Universal Civilizations differed, they all had targeted technology for high-level life forms. For example, the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was one of them. Even the peak Beyond Grade A Milizaus could not take many hits from it. As advanced civilizations developed further, there would only be more technology of that level.

In a direct battle, be it Han Xiao or Dark Lord, they would be able to easily shatter this fleet. However, the enemy were prepared for this while Han Xiao and Dark Lord were not. Through all kinds of targeted attacks and technology, they had taken them by surprise.

Even Clotti fell for it and was exiled into the chaotic space streams. It was unknown when he would return.

However, being able to restrain the movements of the three of them at once was the most they could do. They did not have enough means of attack to hurt the three of them.

"These people's target isn't Clotti. They're here for me."

Han Xiao contained the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy again. He had a tight frown on his face.

Ames caught what Han Xiao meant in between the lines and asked curiously, "You know who they are?"

"I do indeed."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

"This is a group of people who shouldn't have appeared in this era…"

Chapter 1077: Holy Accord and Primordial Ones

"Not in this era?" Ames said with a weird expression. "Why do you say that?"

Han Xiao paused and did not answer this question. He changed the topic and said softly, "This is a secret organization focused on studying and inventing Esper Ability technology. They're also a mysterious arms dealer. Their products occasionally appear on the black market, and now they've set their eyes on the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy…"

Han Xiao could not give a lot of information to Ames, so he only briefly explained it while being shocked inside.

In his previous life, the first time this organization appeared publicly was during the World Tree Civilization War. As members of the explored universe, they joined the war and fought against the World Tree Civilization's invasion, using their technology in the war.

However, it was only Version 4.0 Flickering World now, many versions before the World Tree storyline. These people should not have appeared in this era, hence his shock.

The name of this organization was 'Holy Accord'. It was extremely mysterious even in the very late versions in his previous life. Most of the people who knew about this organization were the offspring of Beyond Grade As.

Other than this Esper Ability technology, there were also many renowned Beyond Grade As in the history who were already confirmed dead who joined the World Tree war together with the Holy Accord. It was as if they had revived and come back to the universe. There were even extremely famous Primordial Ones among them.

This organization, which had a new type of technology, and those high-level combatants became powerful reinforcements to the losing side back then, causing a lot of damage to the World Tree Civilization.

The revival of these Beyond Grade As was a humongous boost to everyone's morale. However, the reason for their revival was still an enigma to the players. The advanced civilizations locked the information down, so the players had no way of finding out anything about it. Therefore, even Han Xiao did not know the truth behind it.

However, although the Holy Accord organization's first appearance was during the World Tree war, it was not the same for the Primordial Ones. During as early as the Calamity of the Supers version, there was already a batch of Primordial Ones who had awakened and become the triggers of the Calamity of the Supers.

Back then, the explanation these Primordial Ones gave to the outside world was that they faked their death during the exploration era and had been sleeping in advanced life-sustaining cabins ever since in order to avoid the bloody exploration era warfare and not die for nothing. They hoped to awaken in the future and conquer the universe in the new era.

However, something seemed to have gone wrong. The place they were sleeping in was also devoured by the flames of war. Their life-sustaining cabins floated in the universe and landed on a desolate island. At the same time, the life-sustaining cabins malfunctioned, causing them to not be able to awaken at their intended time. Hence, they had no choice but to spend countless years in that sleeping state. Although the specially made life-sustaining cabins could slow down the degradation of their body and soul, they were still slowly heading toward their demise.

Coincidentally, when they were close to their end, a research team happened to dig them out and reactivated their life-sustaining cabins. Only then did they awaken from their long sleep. After that, they spent a very long time recovering back to their peak performance.

At that time, the only thing the outside world was sure of was the revival of these Primordial Ones. As for the flaws this explanation had such as how could Beyond Grade As be restrained by these tiny life-sustaining cabins, since there were no ways to prove if that was true, the public had no choice but to believe them.

In conclusion, in the later versions in Han Xiao's previous life, there were two batches of different Primordial Ones who awakened at different timings. Once during the Calamity of the Supers, once during the World Tree war.

The first batch of Primordial Ones who awakened in the Calamity of the Supers version did not seem to be related to the Holy Accord organization. However, whether they really had nothing to do with the Holy Accord organization or not, the players in his previous life had no way of knowing. Hence, Han Xiao did not know the connection between them.

If these two events were related, the first batch of Primordial Ones who awakened during the Calamity of the Supers probably lied. They might not have returned from life-sustaining cabins.

"The Holy Accord organization…"

Han Xiao pondered over their intentions.

It was clear that this organization had existed for a while but had never interfered with the outside world. Now, they had suddenly attacked him. This meant that the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was extremely important to the Holy Accord organization, so much so that it was worth attacking someone who stood at the peak of the universe. According to the characteristics of the Holy Accord organization, could they be planning to invent some dark new technology with the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy?

If that was the case, the Holy Accord organization might have done something similar in his previous life… Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Assuming this was true, the Holy Accord organization might have worked with EsGod in his previous life by splitting up other Primal Esper Ability Entities in exchange for the resources in EsGod's hands, including the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

This meant that some of those Super High Risk Esper Abilities EsGod possessed in the later versions might have been provided by the Holy Accord organization…

It would not have mattered if Han Xiao did not know, but since he knew that the Holy Accord already existed at this time, he could not help but become deeply interested in them.

"The Holy Accord organization fled right after attacking, thinking they would not expose their identity. They couldn't have guessed that I knew their identity all along."

Han Xiao raised his brows and was in a much better mood.

Compared to this huge discovery, suffering a small loss was nothing.

"The dynasty's Clotti was taken away by the chaotic space stream. Will he be okay?" Ames asked curiously.

"Don't worry, he's just lost. With his strength and the Universal Treasures in his hands, he will be able to escape very soon."

Han Xiao did not worry about Dark Lord. No matter where Clotti ended up, he would be at the top of the food chain in that secondary dimension.

However, since the chaotic space streams could not be tracked, he had no way of fishing Clotti out. This was also the reason the Holy Accord organization used the Dimensional Exile Bullet to send themselves into the chaotic space streams.

Since the Virtual Intrusion had been interrupted by the virus, Han Xiao could not leave any markings in their spaceships. However, he would be more alert next time and clear the virus before it infected him. This kind of trap would not be very useful then.

Han Xiao looked at the containment device of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. This guy was extremely mad and kept bashing the inside wall of the container while screaming in agony.

"Ahhh! It hurts so much!"

Seeing this, Han Xiao pitied him.

In his previous life, it was also torn apart by others. He had thought that since EsGod had been dealt with, the same thing would not happen to the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy again. Surprisingly, it happened all the same, as if he was fated to be torn apart.

Furthermore, he might have been treated even worse. After all, in his previous life, EsGod simply used his abilities and never tortured him or anything. The Holy Accord organization, however, would definitely study him, which meant that the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy would feel all kinds of pain from that part of his body that was taken away.

Han Xiao pitied him even more and asked, "By the way, how did it feel earlier? Were you unable to control your body?"

"That's right. I don't know what method they used. They stimulated my core and caused me to lose control of my body before using an irresistible force to drag me over."

Han Xiao then asked, "Can you feel the location of that part of your body?"

"Of cou…" Before the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy finished, as if he was suddenly shocked, his entire body shrunk as he yelled, "Ah! My senses are blocked!"

Han Xiao raised his brows but was not surprised.

After all, they were professionals in studying the Primal Esper Ability Entities. There was no way they would leave such an obvious clue to let others chase after them.

"Hahaha!" The Holy Light Particle was rolling on the ground laughing. "Karma! The day has finally come!"

Filled with sorrow and hatred, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy said, "Black Star! Black Star! You have to help me get my body back!"

Han Xiao's mouth contorted slightly.

Why does it feel like I took away Evans' screen time?

At this time, as usual, a notification popped up on the interface.

You have triggered the mission [The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy's Request for Help]!

Mission Introduction: A mysterious organization has taken away part of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy's core energy from you. The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy hopes you can help him take it back.

Mission Requirements: Retrieve the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy's missing core energy.

Reward: 15 billion EXP, 1 Random Reward, +60 Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy Favorability, +1 Holy Light Particle Favorability, [Primal Esper Ability Entity Affinity] talent.

[Primal Esper Ability Entity Affinity]: It's easier for Primal Esper Ability Entities to accept you.

Remark: This mission might cause unknown consequences. Please accept with caution.

"A mission as expected…" Han Xiao started pondering.

The rewards of this mission were nothing extraordinary, but dealing with the Holy Accord organization seemed to be an opportunity to complete [Primal Esper Ability Collector].

If he had to find Primal Esper Ability Entities without owners, it would take God knew how long to find four. Now, however, he had met the Holy Accord organization, which professionally studied Esper Ability technology, so they definitely had some inventory. If he could snatch it, this milestone would be completed easily.

Han Xiao made his decision and responded.

"Alright then, I give you my word. However, they won't be so easy to find."

"It's fine as long as you're willing to help me." The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was overjoyed.

Black Star was not his master and only saw him as a tool, so he had no right to ask for his help. Even without a part of his body, he would still be useful. Therefore, he had actually been quite afraid Han Xiao would not agree to help him.

Han Xiao comforted the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy for a while. Then, he took out a spare Mysterious Energy Host and stuffed it in, not giving it much time to recover from its psychological wounds.

This time, Ames looked around at the raging chaotic space streams around, frowned, and said, "The chaotic space streams these people released caused heavy damage to the Land of Dead Silence. If left alone, this secondary dimension might shatter before Hila comes in the future."

Han Xiao looked around as well. The already broken space wall of the Land of Dead Silence had even more holes in it.

This secondary dimension was related to Hila, so the two of them could not leave it to shatter. Han Xiao summoned lots of space-related devices to stabilize the dimension.

The thickness of the space wall depended on the core energy of the secondary dimension. Only with enough energy would the space wall regenerate itself and continue to expand. The only thing Han Xiao could do now was guide the chaotic space streams that the Dimensional Exile Bullets created out and reduce the pollution.

This was a tough progress. The two of them spent quite some in the Land of Dead Silence before Han Xiao finally got rid of the chaotic space streams inside.

At this time, the two of them suddenly realized that the revive tokens they were wearing became hotter at an extremely quick pace.

At the same time, a golden light suddenly appeared on a shattered black island far away.

Han Xiao looked over and was slightly shocked.

An orange-gold silhouette suddenly appeared from the black desert. It looked like a spirit and had the appearance of a human female. Its clothes were exquisite. It looked charming, pretty, and rather young, but the look in its eyes gave a vibe that it was very old. It was looking at Han Xiao and Ames.

Seeing this, the two of them were both slightly surprised.

They had already scanned this entire secondary dimension when they arrived, and they were certain they did not sense any life form. Now, however, a strange silhouette had appeared out of thin air. It was clear it had avoided their detection.

Han Xiao was still on alert after the attack of the Holy Accord organization earlier. He was prepared to fight.

At this time, the revive token on the two of them shockingly started to float. This silhouetted pointed at the two revive tokens and sent a telepathic message.

"Tell me, what is the relationship between the two of you and the creator of these two coins?"

…

Inside the chaotic space streams, the Holy Accord organization's fleet was floating.

Inside the command room, Law held the containment device up and observed the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy fragment. Unsatisfied, he sighed.

"Sigh, Black Star's regenerative ability is too strong. These products given to us by the organization have very limited effects on him. Without enough time, this tiny bit of Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy is all we could get."

"Be glad. At least the minimum requirements are met and the synthetic materials are all gathered. If we were too greedy and did not retreat instantly, our spaceship might have been taken by Black Star," Fay said softly.

Although they had achieved the minimum goal of this mission, the two of them knew how close they were to being obliterated. They felt tremendous fear toward Han Xiao.

"This attack was a success, but it has made him cautious too. The next time we meet him, we won't be able to achieve what we did today. Furthermore, he'll most likely report the technology we displayed to the dynasty, which will bring some risks to the organization." Law was worried.

Fay, however, was more optimistic. "Luckily, the mission was completed. It doesn't matter if Black Star is cautious now. We won't have to deal with him in the future again. There won't be a next time."

"You're right."

After chatting for a while, Law put the containment device away. Suddenly, he thought of something and said, "By the way, I seem to recall that the information about the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy shows that it's the Holy Light Particle's arch-enemy and that their energies conflict with each other. Maybe we can invent a special sensor through this characteristic it has to find the Holy Light Particle."

"Hmm, you're right. The Holy Light Particle has been missing for many years. God knows where it's hiding. There are no clues about it at all. It's also an important synthetic material, so the organization will probably heed your suggestion and target the Holy Light Particle next."

Chapter 1078: Underworld and Heritage

Inside the Land of Dead Silence, the two of them looked at the orange-gold spirit that suddenly appeared.

Han Xiao held onto the revive token, felt its vibration, and asked curiously, "What are you?"

"I'm the consciousness entity of the Underworld. Simply put, I'm the butler of this secondary dimension. You can call me by my name, Onicelu."

Dimensional consciousness entity… I thought that even if a near shattered secondary dimension had a consciousness entity, it would have already perished… Han Xiao was surprised.

A dimensional consciousness could only be born in extremely few secondary dimensions. Having one was equivalent to the secondary dimension turning from a lifeless dimension to a type of life form. For example, the Evil Convergence.

Dimensional consciousness entities were at an even higher level. It meant that the secondary dimension had ignited the sparks of intelligence. In comparison, the Evil Convergence was merely a beast.

Dimensional consciousness entities could control all the energy in the secondary dimension. In the eyes of some, they were basically like gods. Some religions even made sculptures in the image of dimensional consciousness entities and worshipped them as gods, which was one of the mainstream religions in the main universe.

No wonder they could not sense its existence. Despite this secondary dimension being close to perishing, it was still its territory. The dimensional consciousness entity was this dimension itself. If it was not willing to appear, no one would be able to sense it.

"Then, what is the Underworld?" Han Xiao had a rough guess.

As expected, this dimensional consciousness entity that called itself Onicelu looked down at the black island below it and calmly said, "As you can see, this secondary dimension that's heading toward its end is the Underworld."

Han Xiao understood.

The Land of Dead Silence was what that Void Duke Kirkmond called it. It seemed that the Underworld was the formal name of this secondary dimension.

He raised the revive token in his hands and said, "You should have noticed us long ago since you responded to the energy inside this coin. Why have you only appeared now?"

"I just wanted to be certain of your intentions." Onicelu's telepathic message was very gentle.

As soon as Han Xiao and Ames entered the Underworld, Onicelu had noticed them. She had been silently observing them. When the two of them helped her fix the environment earlier, only then did she confirm that they had no hostile intentions, so she decided to appear.

Onicelu also had to judge whether these two guys were friends or foes with the creator of these two revive tokens. This was extremely important to her.

Han Xiao wanted to continue asking questions but was interrupted by Onicelu. "I know you have a lot of questions, but I've answered enough of your questions. Before you tell me your relationship with the creator of these two coins, I won't answer any more questions."

Hearing this, Han Xiao stayed silent and started calculating the pros and cons.

The Hila sisters being related to this secondary dimension was strange. To begin with, now that this dimension had a consciousness entity, it was an even more sensitive matter.

This was because, according to Hila, this dimension was the obstruction between her link with Aurora and had always been silently absorbing the energy they were transferring. Therefore, this consciousness entity's goal was unknown, and he did not know if he should tell the truth.

However, since there was a dimensional consciousness entity, she would certainly know all the background stories, which meant that Hila would not have to investigate it herself. The only problem was, they had to be sure that she was not lying.

As Han Xiao was pondering, Ames, who was initially just listening, suddenly spoke.

"She's my student."

Onicelu turned to look at her and said, "Can you prove it?"

Ames looked at Han Xiao and gave him an eye signal.

"Oh well, since you've already told her, I don't have to think about it anymore…" Han Xiao shook his head with resignation and displayed part of Hila's information with virtual technology.

"It really is the Power of the Dead…" Onicelu looked like she was relieved. She smiled and said, "She should have an older or younger blood-related sister who has the Vital Energy Esper Ability."

"… That's right." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled, and he nodded.

Onicelu gave the two of them a deep look, placed her palms against each other, and said with a suddenly very serious tone, "I have a request. I hope you guys can bring them here as early as possible… The Underworld needs new inheritors!"

Inheritors?

Han Xiao and Ames exchanged looks of confusion.

"What does that mean? Tell me everything you know, and I'll relay it to them, but if you don't, I'll have no choice but to suspect what your goals are and stop them from coming here," Han Xiao said with a deep voice.

The term inheritors sounded good, but the Great Mechanic Han was wary this might be a trap, and he would end up putting Hila in danger, so he had to know everything.

"Since I've decided to show up, I never planned to keep secrets from you guys."

Through telepathy, Onicelu shared some of her memories like a grandma telling the story of when she was young.

"It all started as early as the exploration era. In the long war, the first batch of Beyond Grade As was born. History calls them the Primordial Ones. Among the Primordial Ones, there were a pair of sisters whose Esper Abilities synergized with each other perfectly, but they were not related by blood. They were the 'Controller of Death' Nerkese and the 'Mother of All Things' Eros. Using their abilities, they created this Underworld dimension…

"In the beginning, the Underworld dimension was nothing but a prison used to lock up the dead souls Nerkese had collected, as well as the followers of Eros. However, as the abilities of its two creators kept growing, the Underworld dimension obtained a new function—it became a world to the dead life forms where their consciousness could live forever.

"Since you're a Mechanic, in your terms, you can understand it as turning the memories and minds of those whose body died into data and uploading it into the virtual world, achieving a form of eternal life. The Underworld dimension is like the server. It stores the souls of countless life forms. Many powerful individuals in the exploration era chose to sleep in the Underworld. Because of that, Nerkese and Eros created me to manage the Underworld, as the grave keeper.

"The two extremely talented founders didn't stop there. Nerkese's ability made souls not disappear in the Underworld, and Eros used her ability to create temporary body containers, which allowed those souls to regain life. Then, using the special energy formed by fusing their energy together, they could make the targets have the strength they had when they were alive, till the vital energy acting as their fuel finished. Furthermore, even if their body container died again, their souls could still return to the Underworld. Using this ability, the two of them created an extremely powerful army. To them, the Underworld dimension was also an enormous army camp!"

Hearing Onicelu's explanation, Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

Damn, so this is basically Edo Tensei‽

What kind of luck is this‽

Aurora had once mentioned that the Hila sisters' abilities were rather similar to two of the Primordial Ones, so Han Xiao had done some research. He knew that the Mother of All Things was not as weak as Aurora. She had a ton of followers and had some kind of summoning ability. This was the first time Han Xiao had heard about the details of their abilities.

Basically, the souls of countless strong individuals were stored in the Underworld. Through some kind of revival energy fused from vital energy and death energy, they could carry out 'Edo Tensei' and turn them into an enormous army. According to what the dimensional consciousness entity said, it seemed like the Hila sisters could become the inheritors of the Underworld.

Did this not mean that the two of them could take the inheritance of two Primordial Ones? Fortune falling from the sky‽

Spending a lot of time with Feidin indeed led to good things.

While he was being pleasantly surprised, Onicelu's tone became sorrowful.

"Sadly, after the two founders died, the Underworld death energy had lost its energy supply and started to gradually wither. All the souls fell asleep, including me."

"How did they die?"

Han Xiao was curious. The cause of death of the two of them was not recorded. It only said they disappeared.

A ton of conspiracy theories appeared in his mind, but Onicelu's response gave him a big surprise.

"They committed suicide."

Han Xiao was stunned. "What… Why?"

Onicelu sighed. "They kept developing their abilities, and one day, they had a sudden realization. They had been calling themselves the controllers of life and death all this time, but they had never experienced true death and new life. In their eyes, this was the only path that could develop their Esper Abilities to a higher territory. Hence, they decided to walk into demise to search for the true meaning of life and death…

"Before their death, they told me not to grieve, that destruction is only the beginning of new life and that this is where they belonged. On that day, I watched them leave their bodies behind and end their own lives with my own eyes."

Han Xiao was puzzled.

Excuse me, what is there to search for when you're already dead?

Could it be that these two were extremists and never thought of this at all?

Maybe, only those with this kind of mindset could be the first batch of great individuals to break the limit of Beyond Grade As. Maybe this was what it meant to be the Primordial Ones.

As if she understood what Han Xiao's expression meant, Onicelu shook her head and said softly, "I know what you're wondering. Before their consciousness completely perished, there was a short moment where they were alive, dead, and in between. At that moment, I received the last message they had left me. They said they'd found the true meaning of life and death."

"And what's that?" Han Xiao was intrigued again.

"Heritage." Onicelu's tone was soft and gentle. "They said that heritage is the true definition of eternity, forming full circles in the enormous system of life forms."

Han Xiao was a little bit speechless. Doesn't everyone know that? You guys killed yourselves just to figure that out? You probably died for nothing!

However, although he really wanted to say that, he knew that knowing something was one thing and experiencing it was another completely different thing.

On many occasions, the key to a higher territory was that kind of sudden flash of insight. This was especially true the stronger the person was.

"Their deaths did not go to waste," Onicelu said. "They'll pass down this deepest understanding to the next generation."

Han Xiao was shocked. With disbelief, he said, "Are Hila and Aurora really the reincarnations of those two Primordial Ones?"

Ames looked surprised hearing this too.

However, Onicelu shook her head.

"Reincarnations? Not at all. They died completely. Their souls perished, and their bodies were also dissolved by me to supply energy to the dimension. Other than this Underworld, they left nothing. They put all of their experience in their Esper Abilities. The Esper Abilities are what's inherited."

"I still don't understand…" Ames was lost.

"After they died, they left the seeds of the Vital Energy Esper Ability and the Death Energy Esper Ability," Onicelu explained patiently. "These are neither physical nor energy-formed objects but of a higher dimensional data form. I don't know why that happened, but I know that if I had kept those seeds, no one in the entire universe would have awoken those two Esper Abilities ever.

"Therefore, to complete the dying wish of the two founders and to save myself, I sent these seeds back to the main universe. I knew that one day in the future, they would blossom on two new lives…"

Onicelu paused, smiled, and said, "Do you guys really think it's a coincidence that there is only one pair of blood-related sisters with Vital Energy Esper Ability and Death Energy Esper Ability in the entire universe?"

Having heard of such a secret, the Great Mechanic Han felt like his fragile heart was shocked.

This meant that Hila and Aurora had no direct connections with those two Primordial Ones at all; they were only chosen by the data-form Esper Ability seeds and became the Vital Energy Esper Ability and Death Energy Esper Ability owners of this generation.

The two Primordial Ones fused their understanding into the data-form Esper Ability seeds so that those who were chosen by them would slowly receive the information and experience within. This was basically indirectly increasing the talents of their inheritors.

No wonder it was so easy for Hila to acquire new abilities and talents!

"Data form…" Han Xiao could not help but have even more speculations.

He still remembers that during one of his Racial Evolutions, there was a [Multi-Dimensional Shadow] option that seemed to be related to data forms.

Before he could think further, Onicelu spoke again softly. "That's all I know. After the two founders died, the Underworld started to gradually wither and could no longer keep itself sealed from the outside world. Its size started to shrink, its space wall started to break, and souls fell asleep one after another. I had no choice but to store them all in the dimension core to prevent them from perishing. However, I've become weaker and weaker. I fell asleep as well. When the Underworld shatters completely, these souls will disappear.

"The energy source of the Underworld is the energy of the Vital Energy Esper Ability and the Death Energy Esper Ability. Not long ago, I finally obtained some of it when I subconsciously absorbed the energy from the sisters of this generation, which barely woke me from my long sleep. Only then did I stop absorbing their energy."

Han Xiao thought about it. "Not long ago… it should be when Hila and Aurora were studying their life link. No wonder the energy they transferred was absorbed. That makes sense. This means that the Underworld dimension is actually the medium of the life link between them…"

This time, Onicelu shook her head and said calmly, "The bodies of the two Primordial Ones helped me to last a very long time, but that depleted long ago. The Underworld needs stable, long-term energy suppliers. Please bring them here as soon as possible. I don't know how much longer I can last."

As soon as she said that, Han Xiao received a notification in the interface.

You have triggered the mission [Inheritors of The Underworld].

Mission Introduction: The Underworld is the heritage of the previous owners of the Vital Energy Esper Ability and the Death Energy Esper Ability. The dimensional consciousness entity Onicelu has realized that she is getting weaker every day. She hopes that Hila and Aurora can become the new inheritors.

Mission Requirements: Help Hila and Aurora inherit the Underworld dimension.

Reward: 50 Million EXP, +20 Onicelu Favorability, 1 Character Summon Card.

Bonus Mission Requirement: Help the Underworld return to its peak state.

Bonus Reward: +40 Onicelu Favorability, [Mark of The Underworld].

Chapter 1079: Rich Reward

"A mission…"

Han Xiao glanced at the interface and had a rough idea.

According to the basic rewards, he knew that helping Hila to take over the Underworld dimension would probably not be difficult. The only tough part was the bonus requirement—god only knew how much energy it would take for the Underworld to reach its original state, but even draining Hila dry would probably not be enough.

However, since it was an inheritance from the predecessors, there was no reason to reject it.

[Mark of the Underworld] was quite tempting for Han Xiao. Its effect granted him the right to control the secondary dimension to a certain extent, similar to the Mark of Evil Convergence, which Traveler had. At the same time, it would also increase his strength to some extent.

Furthermore, he could also dray the soul of the enemies he killed into the Underworld. This was equivalent to basically getting part of Hila's power as a part-time soul collector.

Along with the Favorability reward from this mission, it seemed that this mission was saying that he did Onicelu a great favor, so she was willing to let him use her body.

When he thought of it this way, it seemed quite exciting…

Han Xiao searched his memories. In his previous life, Hila did not display any ability related to the Underworld dimension, so the Underworld had probably perished before she discovered it.

After all, the main reason Hila discovered the Underworld came from when she tried creating a life link with Aurora. Without the energy the Underworld absorbed when they transferred energy to each other, Onicelu would not have awakened.

In his previous life, however, Aurora was long gone, and Hila was alone. Without Aurora, she most likely never discovered the Underworld dimension and missed out on the inheritance.

At the same time, even if Hila did obtain the Underworld dimension, without Aurora, they would not be able to summon or Edo Tensei anyone…

In conclusion, the Germinal Organization leader was truly a great man.

All kinds of thoughts flashed past Han Xiao's mind. In the end, he nodded at Onicelu and said, "Alright, I'll bring them here very soon to meet you."

"I'm counting on you." Onicelu smiled.

Then, she disappeared and hid away. She had already said everything she needed to, and with very limited energy that she had no way of recovering, she did not want to waste any of it.

Han Xiao and Ames were the only ones left. He turned around to look at her and saw that she was pondering. It was clear that she was shocked and had yet to recover.

This was not without its reasons. Initially, the two of them only wanted to come and take a look at the place for Hila. Never did they expect to run into this chain of incidents. First, they met Traveler and beat him into a pulp, then were attacked back an unknown fleet. Clotti went missing, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy became disabled, and in the end, they met the Underworld's dimensional consciousness entity and discovered this shocking secret. There was too much information to process.

It was said that every lucky guy seemed to run into trouble most easily. Why did he never notice that Ames was talented in this area?

However, overall, Han Xiao was more pleasantly surprised than shocked. He had captured the Holy Light Particle, triggered a few new missions, and obtained some secret information. The rewards of this trip were quite rich.

Although part of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy had been snatched away, it could still use its powers. When he put it this way, it did not seem like he had lost anything at all.

As for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy's agony, Han Xiao was actually not really concerned. As a great man once said, everyone had different reasons to feel sorrowful or joyous, not to mention the difference between people and Esper Ability entities.

Dealing with the Holy Accord would take a lot of planning. The main mission now was to help Hila inherit the Underworld.

Having thought of that, Han Xiao patted Ames' shoulders and said, "Stop daydreaming. It's time to leave."

Ames regained focus and chuckled with joy.

"I never thought Hila and Aurora would meet something like this. I'm proud of my students."

"Yes yes yes, your students are amazing." Han Xiao interrupted her. "Having met something like this, we'll have to cut our schedule short. I'll have the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy take you back to Black Star Palace to bring Hila here, what do you say?"

"Of course, it's a great idea." Ames smiled.

Han Xiao nodded and ordered the Mysterious Energy Host to grab Ames. In the blink of an eye, they disappeared. The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy's ability to cross between secondary dimensions was much more convenient compared to mechanical devices. It would not take long for them to return.

He was the only one there. After some thinking, he took out his communicator and called the dynasty's secondary dimension frontline station. This time, he contacted the dynasty's person in charge who was stationed there.

After some time, the communication went through, and Guzar's face appeared before his eyes.

The moment Han Xiao saw this face, he was stunned for a second.

Zhang Fei?

Yoho, I was mistaken. That sure startled me. This is way too similar to Zhang Fei's face…

This time, Guzar's loud voice sounded with an impatient tone.

"Black Star, we suddenly lost the location of Dark Lord. Where did he go?"

"We were attacked by a mysterious fleet. He was exiled into the chaotic space streams…" Han Xiao explained the process briefly with emphasis on the technology of the Holy Accord.

"These weaklings actually troubled him? Clotti is really getting rusty," Guzar murmured with dissatisfaction.

"It happens, it happens…" Han Xiao dry coughed trying to change to the topic.

Guzar caressed his beard and mumbled, "However, their technology is indeed unique. If taken by surprise, I might end up the same way too… Hey, Black Star, do you know their identity?"

"Nope. However, if you guys want to investigate them, I suggest you start with the records of the birth of the Primal Esper Ability Entities. This organization undoubtedly has more than one Primal Esper Ability. Other than that, there's nothing else I know."

Han Xiao had very limited knowledge about the Holy Accord organization in this era. Therefore, simply mentioning its name might not only be not very effective but also bring him more trouble.

"Understood, I'll relay your information up. They dare to attack the dynasty's man. We will certainly dig them out and teach them a lesson," Guzar said with a deep voice.

Han Xiao nodded.

Getting the dynasty to chase after the Holy Accord would at least cause them some trouble.

With the power of advanced civilizations, they might really be able to notice something.

Guzar complained for a while to vent his anger before he finally calmed down. He sized Han Xiao up and could not help but give him a passionate invitation.

"Black Star, I have always wanted to meet you. Come to my place if you have the time. We'll have to know more about each other."

"There'll be chances in the future."

Han Xiao agreed with a smile while being quite contented in his heart.

The fact that a powerful Beyond Grade A actively came to him meant that his networking skills were finally reaching their peak.

The Great Mechanic Han knew who Guzar was; he was a direct Beyond Grade A of the dynasty who was stationed in the secondary dimension. Before this, he had never come into contact with him, but in his memories, this guy seemed quite strong. Sadly, he died too early in his previous life, before the World Tree version.

Speaking of which, the secondary dimensions were one of the battlefronts during the World Tree war, and the battles there were just as bloody as in the main universe. The research labs and the outposts of the three Universal Civilizations were almost all destroyed. Compared to the stable spacetime of the main universe, the strange and unpredictable secondary dimensions seemed more dangerous to many.

They then chatted for a while longer. The conversation was quite pleasant, and they both gave each other a good impression.

When Han Xiao hung up the call, the space beside him rippled again. The Mysterious Energy Host had brought Ames and Hila back.

He turned and said, "Yo, you've come. Why didn't you bring your sister?"

"There's no need to bring Aurora to such a dangerous place. If her ability is needed, I'll just tell her to transfer it to me remotely," Hila explained. She then looked around at the Underworld dimension with curiosity and doubt. "You guys really didn't trick me together, right? Is this secondary dimension the inheritance of the Primordial Ones?"

"Let her explain it to you herself."

Han Xiao snapped his fingers.

Onicelu appeared again. She first gave Han Xiao a smile that seemed to mean she was very satisfied with how efficient he was before pulling Hila aside to speak to her.

Seeing this, Han Xiao told Hila, "Alright, go chat with her. Ames and I shall leave for now. I'll leave a mechanical army here. Notify me if anything changes. Anyway, you have the King mechanical suit. Tell me if you're in danger and I'll just teleport you back."

Hila turned to look at him but hesitated for a moment before nodding. "Alright, go have fun."

Han Xiao smiled at him. He told the Mysterious Energy Host to take the two of them away.

He was not worried about Hila's safety. After all, she was a Beyond Grade A. Plus, his army was with her. She had more than enough strength to protect herself in the secondary dimensions.

Looking at the direction the two of them disappeared in, complicated emotions appeared in Hila's eyes.

There was joy and disappointment.

Of course, she was surprised to come across the opportunity of becoming stronger through the inheritance of the Primordial Ones.

However, when she thought of the fact that the promise Black Star had made to travel with her alone in the secondary dimensions might be disposed because of it. She was somewhat disappointed.

Although she never spoke of it, she actually really wanted to go out with Black Star…

…

The Void Dimension.

With a flash of red light, the two of them appeared in Kirkmond's territory in an instant.

As the official business regarding the Holy Light Particle and the Underworld dimension was complete, Han Xiao planned to complete the milestone mission, [Void Conqueror]. Therefore, remembering his promise to Kirkmond, he rushed back.

However, when the two of them looked around, they were stunned.

The void crystal floating city that was originally filled with void creatures was now empty. The void army that was stationed there had vanished.

"That's strange. Where did they go? Field training?" Ames looked around.

"Let's ask a void creature about it."

Han Xiao led Ames to Kirkmond's palace. As expected, there were indeed some void creatures with no combat capability who were left behind. They had seen their boss invite these two guests here, so they approached them.

"Where did Kirkmond go?" Han Xiao asked directly.

"Master has taken the army out to war."

"Didn't I tell him to wait until we returned? He couldn't even wait for such a short time?" Han Xiao wondered.

The void henchman said with resignation, "Kirkmond did not start the war. We were invaded by another Void Duke. Kirkmond was forced to take the fight."

"Give me the coordinates of the battlefield then." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and said softly, "It seems like we've come right on time."

…

At the same time, in a certain area of the Void Dimension, two enormous void armies were fighting.

In the middle of the battlefield, the two Void Dukes of the two sides were dueling.

One rode a young Void Dragon, holding an enormous void crystal shield and a black longsword. The other rode a Void Worm and held a greenish-copper short spear in all of its twenty or so arms.

Every clash of their weapons sent out a blue-purple void energy shockwave. A huge area around them was empty—no one dared interfere with the duel between two Void Dukes.

The one who used a sword was Kirkmond, who had a slightly lower hand in the fight. His control of void energy was not as good as the opponent, and his energy was not as strong. He was defending himself more than attacking.

The enemy he was facing was indeed his archenemy, as well as Han Xiao's mission target, Void Duke Bagdora.

Since they were both void creatures and had high resistance to void energy, long-range attacks had very limited effects. Therefore, when fighting against one of their own, most void creatures preferred close-range battles.

Clank!

More than ten short spears slashed down simultaneously. Kirkmond hastily raised his shield to block them. The clash sent out several rings of shockwaves as they competed in power.

"Can you feel my improved strength? You're no longer a match for me!" Bagdora laughed.

"You killed another Void Duke‽" Kirkmond was both shocked and enraged.

At their level, every slight increase in strength was very important. Their strength would only suddenly grow when they devoured someone at the same level as them or higher.

In all these years, none of them was clearly stronger than the other. Now, however, Bagdora was clearly stronger. The only explanation was that he had devoured the core of another Void Duke.

"Hehe, a newborn Void Duke just happened to pass by my territory. I turned him into my energy. This is fate, and fate dictates that I'll defeat you!"

Damn it! Kirkmond was jealous. Why don't I ever get this lucky?

Bagdora's short spears left afterimages behind. He seemed to be growing impatient. Kirkmond was already a very nutritious meal in his eyes, and he could not wait to eat him up.

"If I eat you, I'll be able to become one of the strongest Dukes. There's no use resisting. Become my food!"

Kirkmond could not hold much longer. His army was also showing signs of losing.

He knew that his defeat was certain is this went on, so he yelled furiously,

"Don't go over your head! I still have reinforcements!"

"So what? You think you can scare me away?"

Bagdora laughed out loud as he cut away a small part of Kirkmond's body without mercy.

"I'll eat your so-called reinforcements too. I'll take it as your gift to me!"

At this time, Han Xiao just so happened to arrive at the edge of the battlefield through hyperdrive. Hearing this, he turned to look at this Void Duke, and his brows twitched a little.

He released a public telepathic message that instantly covered the entire battlefield.

"You wanna try it?"

Chapter 1080: Are You Here to Steal My Harvest?

Along with Han Xiao, the Beyond Grade A energy he had appeared too. He became an energy source that had an extremely dangerous presence, which instantly attracted the attention of all the void creatures around.

"Ha! My help is here!"

Strength appeared in Kirkmond's body all of a sudden. While Bagdora was still shocked, he slashed his sword down Bagdora's arms, instantly cutting away many of his energy-made arms.

Bagdora hastily retreated away from Kirkmond, regenerated his arms then looked at Han Xiao with a grave expression. The confidence he had earlier was nowhere to be found.

Beyond Grade As of the main universe were not easy to mess with. This was common knowledge in the secondary dimensions. He did not expect Kirkmond to have a connection with a stranger Beyond Grade A.

"Who are you? I'm warning you. Don't interfere with the matters of the Void Dimension. I'm master Kasuyi's subordinate!"

Bagdora immediately brought up a big name. Among the names he knew from the main universe, Kasuyi's name was the most impactful.

"He's not! He's just trying to scare you!" Kirkmond exposed his lie without mercy.

"Humph, don't trust him. Kirkmond is a liar! He's definitely just using you!"

"You're the liar!" Kirkmond was enraged.

"No, you!"

Even in this situation, the two of them did not stop arguing.

Han Xiao, however, had no plan to join the argument. Electric sparks appeared in his eyes as countless machines swarmed out. Then, an enormous net formed by Mechanical Force grabbed all the machines and pulled them toward him, quickly assembling.

This huge move caused all the void creatures on the battlefield to stop fighting and look over.

A Mechanical Deity formed very quickly. Since the opponent was just a Void Duke, he did not summon a lot of machines. Therefore, this Mechanical Deity was not too large, only about ten thousand meters tall.

The most conspicuous part of it was the enormous metal cape on its back. It was not soft like cloth but was completely mechanical. It looked extremely delicate and complex.

It was the Emperor's Cape, which Han Xiao had sent into battle for the first time.

"Mechanical Deity‽" Bagdora was knowledgeable enough to know what this was. His panic was clearly expressed from his fluctuating mind frequency.

If he had a face, his fear would have clearly shown on it.

Without saying anything, Bagdora immediately turned around attempting to escape. He disappeared in an instant and entered Void Hyperdrive.

However, Kirkmond was prepared for this. Being a Void Duke as well, he had all kinds of ways to prevent Bagdora from escaping. He swung his long sword sideways and slapped the space before him. Dense Void Energy exploded, sending out shockwave-like ripples. The space of this Void Dimension was easily sealed.

The next moment, Bagdora appeared again as he was forced out from hyperdrive by Kirkmond.

"You…"

Bagdora was frustrated. However, before he could try anything else again, Han Xiao controlled his Mechanical Deity and charged toward him. He was not planning to just watch on the side.

Seeing this, Bagdora did not even try to escape anymore. He quickly sent out long-ranged attacks with Void Energy at the Mechanical Deity, hoping to stop Han Xiao from getting closer.

Without slowing down, the Mechanical Deity grabbed a corner of the Emperor's Cape and pulled it to its front.

Buzz!

An energy shield appeared on the surface of the cape. It was extremely thick and strong. Countless Void Energy attacks landed on it, only to create tiny little ripples, unable to slow down the Mechanical Deity at all.

At the same time, the Emperor's Cape also increased the mobility and speed of the Machinery Deity by a large extent. At the edges of the cape, the space could be seen bent, which drastically increased the Machinery Deity's speed.

"Don't come any closer!"

Shocked, Bagdora wanted to back away, but Kirkmond stopped him from doing so. Unable to flee, he could only watch as the Mechanical Deity moved closer.

"Take this!" Han Xiao raised the Mechanical Deity's arm and punched forward.

Highly condensed psionic energy fused with all kinds of electromagnetic and shockwave force fields formed a light blue energy shield shrouding the Mechanical Deity's fist. It was extremely destructive.

Boom!

Bagdora's defense did not have much effect. His enormous energy formed body was flattened and pressed onto the Mechanical Deity's fist. His greenish-copper short spears were all shattered into atoms, and his Void Worm died right on the spot, not leaving even ashes behind.

Some time ago, Han Xiao had obtained [Machinery Control Master] through the few Beyond Grade A captives, which drastically increased the strength of armor-type equipment when used by him. Furthermore, his melee-range combat capability was also enhanced tremendously.

The power of this punch was way too much for a Void Duke like Bagdora. He was heavily injured instantly.

Void creatures had their own level system and were not included in the combat capability measurement standard of the main universe, so there was no clear comparison. However, at Han Xiao's level, he could easily estimate it.

With the advantage of fighting in its own territory, the Void Dukes could fight back and forth with ordinary Beyond Grade As for dozens of rounds, but that was all. Only the strongest Dukes and Void Lords, Void Ancients, could compete with real Beyond Grade As. As for peak Beyond Grade As, their power exceeded the upper strength limit of void creatures.

Basically, Bagdora was about as strong as his Apostle Weapons, which were between Lv260 and Lv280, basically almost Beyond Grade As. They would easily crush Calamity Grades but would be thrashed by Beyond Grade As.

With such a large difference in strength, the only reason Bagdora was not completely obliterated was thanks to the special physique of Void Dukes; his various resistances were extremely high.

Bagdora's flattened body stayed still for an instant on the Mechanical Deity's fist before shooting out the next moment like a rocket, creating an empty path on the battlefield.

The Mechanical Deity remained on the same spot. It extended two fingers and aimed at Bagdora, who was flying further and further away. Its fingertips turned sharp and became a barrel, blinding light appeared from within.

"Evil Perish Cannon!" Han Xiao gave it a ridiculous name for fun.

Xiu!

An energy beam shot out from the fingertips of the Mechanical Deity and caught up to Bagdora instantly, penetrating his body.

Bagdora's body suddenly became stiff. He started to evaporate from within like snow on a hot day, gradually melting.

Very soon, only a gray sphere was left floating. This was what was left of Bagdora—the core essence of a Void Duke.

"This guy is finally dead!" Kirkmond was overjoyed. Through hyperdrive, he jumped over and grabbed Bagdora's core. Feeling the lingering frustration emotion in it, he could not hold back his laughter.

As their master died, Bagdora's army fell into disarray. Most of the void creatures tried to flee in different directions and were chased; the rest stayed and surrendered. The situation became one-sided.

Seeing this, Han Xiao deactivated the Mechanical Deity and tutted like he wanted more.

This Void Duke was too weak. I didn't even enjoy it enough…

This time, Kirkmond held onto Bagdora's core and returned to Han Xiao. His tone was filled with joy.

"Haha, I knew I was right to trust you. To think you killed Bagdora so easily. You must be someone very well known in the main universe!"

"Not really, not really." Han Xiao gave a humble response.

"According to our agreement, half of the core is yours. We're friends from now on. If you need help in battle, just call me. This is my energy mark; you can contact me if anything happens."

Han Xiao received energy from Kirkmond, which turned into a mark on his arm. He already had a ton of enchantment tattoos on his body and looked like a gangster, so having one more was no big deal.

Han Xiao looked at the interface.

The mission was shown to be completed, and the reward was given. He obtained 12 billion EXP and one Kirkmond's Character Summon Card, and Kirkmond's faction's Favorability reached [Respect]. The Character Summon Card's ability was Void Lock, which was a quite useful controlling ability and could be used five times.

Compared to the low difficulty, this was quite a rich reward. However, only Beyond Grade As like Han Xiao would be able to deal with this mission so easily, so it made sense.

The milestone mission for [Void Conqueror] started too. His progress was at one eighth for the Void Duke forces he destroyed and a twenty-five percent for the void faction favorability he had achieved. He should be able to activate this milestone very soon.

This time, Han Xiao smiled and said, "Any interest in expanding your territory?"

"Oh? Do you plan to continue helping me?" Kirkmond paused, not pleased but surprised, and started hesitating.

The way he looked at it, what Black Star meant was that he wanted to make him his subordinate like Kirkmond. The reason that Kirkmond did not join Kasuyi was that he did not want to work for others, and now he was troubled.

Han Xiao understood what he was thinking from his hesitation. He thought about it and said, "Don't worry, I have no plan to learn from Kasuyi. Since you're willing to fight for me, making your forces stronger is basically indirectly helping myself."

The Void Dimension was Kasuyi's territory. If he came here to grow his forces, he would undoubtedly offend this void movie lord. Therefore, Han Xiao planned to help some Void Dukes in the form of hiring them as mercenaries.

As long as they agreed to be his spare tires… ahem, helpers, he would help them to take over the forces of other Void Dukes. This way, he could both complete his milestone mission and obtain more troops at the same time.

"That sounds good." Kirkmond was relieved.

Having seen Han Xiao's strength earlier, he knew that he was no match. If Han Xiao decided to force him, he would not be able to resist at all, so he felt that Black Star had no need to lie to him.

After communicating a little longer, Kirkmond went to the side to enjoy the essence of Bagdora. Ames, who only watched beside Han Xiao, suddenly shook her head and said, "You don't ever forget about increasing your forces, do you?"

"I'm used to it. After all, I'm a good faction leader…"

Then, Han Xiao gave Ames a look with unspeakable meanings.

"… What kind of look is that?" Ames's brows raised slightly.

"I'm appreciating your beauty."

"Humph, cheeky."

…

Over the next few days, Han Xiao took Ames to travel in the Void Dimension back, looking for new partners to work with and merging the forces of Void Dukes one after another. With his peak Beyond Grade A strength, the progress of the [Void Conqueror] milestone was very quick.

Such frequent movements also attracted more attention from the boss of the Void Dimension. When the news spread to Kasuyi's territory, the Void Dukes under his command reported it to him.

Somewhere in the Flickering World, Kasuyi frowned and narrowed his eyes. Looking at the kneeled void messenger in front of him, he felt alarmed.

"Black Star went to the Void Dimension and is now helping the Void Dukes there to take over the forces of their enemies?"

Could it be that Black Star had set his eyes on the forces of the Void Dimension and wanted to take over void creatures to form an organization like him?

From the way he looked at it, since Black Star had the blood of void creatures and was at the peak Beyond Grade A level, when his God's Trait Transformation reached a certain extent, it was very likely Black Star might develop new abilities related to the void.

Kasuyi was actually not interested in what Han Xiao was doing in the Void Dimension. As the Void Dimension was large enough and had more than enough energy, having one more person to share it with was completely harmless and would not affect him at all. Han Xiao would not be considered as a competitor.

However, he had a big problem with others putting their fingers on his void army. The Void Dimension was his headquarters, and all the void creatures were his own in his eyes. Black Star's actions made Kasuyi a little unhappy.

Never mind if you came to my farm to dig away some soil, but taking away my harvest is crossing the line.

The entire universe knows that the Void Dimension is my home. How can you just come to my home and cause trouble like this, Black Star? Have you ignored my existence?

Kasuyi thought about it and slowly said, "Go back and relay my decision to those Void Dukes. Tell them to get into contact with Black Star and obtain information about what his goal is. Also do the same with the other Void Dukes he helped."

The messenger received the order, shook his body, and returned to the Void Dimension, disappearing without a trace.

With Kasuyi's position, calling Han Xiao directly was the most convenient. However, that would mean that there was no room for any excuse or discussion. Hence, he hoped to take a gentler approach and ask about Han Xiao's goal through a middleman.

The so-called Beyond Grade A Association was about to be formed, and he did not want to mess with Black Star, who was leading it.

"Speaking of which, Manison seems very active recently and has been digging up his old connections. Looks like he really wants to be the one in charge…"

Kasuyi looked interested.

Kasuyi had no plan to do the same. He had never cared too much about the Beyond Grade A Association to begin with. He only saw that Beyond Grade As being in groups would become a trend in the future, so he wanted to obtain a senior position. As for the position of the president, he would not take it even if it was given to him for free. Sitting in that position meant being at the front of all issues. Anyone in that position would be heavily monitored by the advanced civilizations.

Some of the peak Beyond Grade As had the same thoughts as him; very few tried to become the president. Including Manison and Black Star, there were only four of them.

"Hmm, the association can only have one president, who also cannot be a direct member of the three Universal Civilizations, or it would go against its goal… I wonder what plans Black Star has. Although he's not as senior, as the star of the Flickering World and the key initiator of this project, his chances don't seem low…"

Chapter 1082: Return

Everyone there was standing at the top of the explored universe. They all had different forces under their command, such as armies, financial groups, and political powers.

These people did not like discussing nonsense, so the issues were solved very quickly. It did not take long for the rough structure of the association to be formed. On the surface, it was a platform to settle conflicts between Beyond Grade As, while internally, it served to unite the Beyond Grade As. The rules, regulations, and reward system all had a brief outline to be fine-tuned accordingly in the future.

At the same time, the official preparations for the organization were brought forward. These initiators started to relay the message to every Beyond Grade A to recruit members. At the same time, they had to choose a location to build the headquarters of the Beyond Grade A Association in the Flickering World, which needed the Black Star Army's help. Also, every Beyond Grade A would have to set up an agency in their territory to serve as embassies. It felt quite similar to the United Nations.

The preparations would have to take about several months. Before the official formation of the association, the management positions had to be decided. Currently, it was in the form of President, Vice President, and the Governing Council.

After their discussion, they decided to set the duration of one term for the president and vice president to be thirty years. One could only hold the position for three terms consecutively at most but would still be able to take on the position of director after stepping down. Once two terms had passed after stepping down, that person would be eligible to be re-elected for president or vice president.

The president had the most responsibilities. He had to both have appeal and the strength to take on pressure from the three Universal Civilizations. Currently, Manison had the most support, but no one would ignore Han Xiao and confirm the president before he returned.

As for the proposal Manison made to break the monopoly on Ultimate Knowledges, the opinions were currently diverted. In the past, the Ultimate Knowledges were only given by the advanced civilizations as a method to woo Beyond Grade A allies. Even if their allies learned them, they were not allowed to easily teach them to others. Han Xiao had experienced that in the past.

If the association turned the Ultimate Knowledge into one of their rewards, it would basically break the three Universal Civilizations' rules, which would cause severe responses from the three Universal Civilizations.

However, if it really worked, rights would be taken back from the advanced civilizations, and the Beyond Grade As would indeed be free from many limitations and become more independent.

This was an unavoidable step to increase the position the Beyond Grade As had in the universe so that the new Beyond Grade As in the future would not have to become allies of the advanced civilizations for Ultimate Knowledges. At the same time, the Beyond Grade A Association would be able to attract newbies much easier, which was extremely beneficial for those peak Beyond Grade As who had the full set of Ultimate Knowledges of their own class.

On this issue, what the people argued about was the timing. Some felt that this should only be carried out once the association had established a firm base, since this was basically directly confronting the three Universal Civilizations, and a new association would not be able to hold against such an intense conflict. Some felt that it should be carried out as soon as possible to regain their rights, emphasizing why this association existed in the first place.

There would be a lot of time to discuss these details. On the other hand, an excuse or opportunity for the outside world was needed to form this association. They planned to contact some Beyond Grade As to fake some conflicts with each other in the next few months and escalate the issues into physical fights. The key point of this plan was the impact it would bring. The Beyond Grade As involved would only be acting, but they would have to make sure that the conflict would damage different organizations.

Not only were they going to have a huge fight in the Flickering World, but they were also going to encourage their own organizations to cause friction in the various Star Fields, once again letting the other organizations realize how much the conflicts between Beyond Grade As could impact others. This way, the public would lean toward hoping the Beyond Grade As would stop fighting, which would set down the path to forming the association. This plan would both give the three Universal Civilizations pressure and face. Neither side wanted to expose the conflict of interests between them to the public.

After the bosses confirmed the strategy, they started executing it very soon. The Flickering World became even more boisterous than before, and the free competition zone became more chaotic. At the same time, Beyond Grade As started having conflicts with each other in various Star Fields at the same time.

Due to the appearance of this phenomenon, the three Universal Civilizations temporarily put their conflicts behind, and the upper echelons held a remote conference together to discuss how to deal with it.

…

In the completely secured conference room, the remote projections of the federation, church, and dynasty gathered.

The dynasty's Ruler Urranrell, the federation's President Bader, and the church's Pope sat in each corner of the triangular meeting table with their own upper echelons.

In usual times, the three of them fought each other in every way imaginable, but when the explored universe started to become unstable, these three sides would come together and decide the fate of this universe.

Bader looked around and said, "I don't even remember the last time the three of us hosted a meeting like this."

"Of course you don't remember. The last meeting wasn't during your term," the church's Pope said calmly.

Bader gave him a glare but had nothing to say.

The Federation of Light was indeed the one that changed their leader most often. The federation's president had already changed many times before the church's pope even changed once.

"Let's get down to business," Urranrell said expressionlessly. "The unification of the Beyond Grade As is pushed by the big picture. If our objection is too forceful, the Beyond Grade As will strongly repel it. In order to avoid the fate of becoming mere tools, there'll be more new Beyond Grade As in the future who will decide to hide their strength and live a low-profile life. In that case, our efficiency in recruiting allies will increase tremendously. At the same time, recording the total number of Beyond Grade As in the universe will become more difficult."

Bader nodded in agreement. "We have to not let the Beyond Grade As smoothly form that development union or whatnot but not use extreme methods. We'll have to work together. We can't target our own allies, so we shall target each other's. The dynasty will target my allies, I will target the church's, and the church will target the dynasty's allies. This way, we can cause some trouble to some of the Beyond Grade As, especially to those who are still undecided."

"That will only act as an obstacle and make forming the union more difficult. It won't solve the root issue," the Pope said calmly. "If the Beyond Grade As unite as one, they'll have a horrifying amount of influence on all Star Fields. They'll even be able to shake the structure of the entire galactic society."

Bader shook his head and said, "Sadly, it's not possible to clear out all the Beyond Grade As. Not considering how big a price we'll pay, we still have to make sure those extremely powerful individuals exist in this explored universe. They'll apply pressure to those Beyond Grade As who've hidden their strength and escaped to the secondary dimensions, as well as act as a form of insurance for when we explore unknown territories. We never know when we'll run into another unknown advanced civilization, and we can't give up this advantage we have."

"In the calculated model of the galactic society, this is a problem that was bound to show up sooner or later," Urranrell said with a deep voice. "It's just like how the workers formed worker's unions in the early days to protect their own interests. The situation we're facing now is similar, only the targets have changed into special individuals with great strength. Since the exploration era, we've been oppressing them way too much. This day was destined to arrive.

"Therefore, we have to make preparations on both sides. If the formation of the union can't be stopped, we'll have to try to divide them. At their management level, there'll certainly be Beyond Grade As with different opinions and interests, whom we can either bribe or woo to be our eyes and ears. We can then use them to affect the union's decision making."

The pope narrowed his eyes, looked at the two of them, and said, "Speaking of which, the Mechanic Emperor and Black Star are the main ones who initiated this. Their opinions are divided to begin with… Humph, seems like both of your people are difficult to deal with. My Kasuyi is the best as always."

"Manison is very, very ambitious," Bader said with a displeased tone. "In recent years, he's been doing a lot of things behind our backs. It's very possible he wants to be completely out of the federation's control. Frankly, we can't really control him now."

The Pope looked at Urranrell and asked, "What about the dynasty? Your Black Star loves to cause trouble too. Are you going to teach him a lesson?"

"You guys don't have to be concerned with that. We have our own plans for Black Star. The Evolutionary Totem will be sold to the public as promised. You don't have to worry about that," Urranrell said casually.

The dynasty planned on continuing to ease the tension between them and Han Xiao, so they decided to be patient and wait for Gaud to grow till they could solve the technical issue of the Evolutionary Cube. This way, they would be able to reduce Han Xiao's control over the Evolutionary Totem business.

Of course, Urranrell was not going to explain this plan to others.

Seeing this, Bader changed the topic back and said, "Other than dividing them, we'll also have to infiltrate them and not let our people be stopped outside their doors. They want to form the association, so they have to give us some high positions in return and let our people have a say in the management level of their association. Basically, they'll be open spies who'll inform us of what they're up to…"

The three of them discussed the matter for a while, made various proposals for the measures they should take, and slowly came to some agreements.

…

Time slipped by quickly while the structure of the universe gradually changed.

A few months later, in Black Star Palace…

Buzz!

With a flash of light, three people appeared in the army commander's office. It was Han Xiao, Ames, and the Mysterious Energy Host. They had returned from the secondary dimensions.

The two of their mechanical suits came off automatically. This time, a surprised voice sounded from behind.

"Hmm? You've finally decided to return?"

The two of them turned to look over. It turned out Sylvia was in the room and was lying comfortably in Han Xiao's chair. But now, she instantly jumped up like there were springs in the seat.

Seeing this, Han Xiao joked around and said, "Tsk tsk, not bad. Have you been sitting in my chair the whole time I wasn't here? What are you planning to do, take my position?"

"Of course not, I was just… just…" Sylvia's eyes spun frantically as she blushed trying to find an excuse. Stuttering, she then said, "Ahem, it's just that your chair is very comfortable to sit in."

As she was speaking, her expression suddenly froze as her eyes moved down onto Han Xiao's arm, which was wrapped around Ames' waist. Ames did not, however, reject it as Sylvia would expect. It was as if she was already used to it.

Noticing her look, Ames moved her waist slightly out of Han Xiao's hands. She then raised her hand and touched Han Xiao's cheek. "Busy man, I'm going back to the Shattered Star Ring. Jenny is probably going crazy now."

"Must be tough for you to remember her existence."

Han Xiao smiled. He wanted to grab Ames' hand on his cheeks but was a second too late after Ames had already moved it away. She blinked at him and smiled elegantly.

Then, Ames turned to look at the stunned Sylvia, smiled, and walked out of the room.

Sylvia stood in place, appalled.

These two had only gone for a tour in the secondary dimensions, and now their relationship had already become this much more intimate‽

What happened‽

"You, you guys…"

Hearing this, Han Xiao turned into a serious expression and said, "What 'you guys'? Do you know your priorities? In the days I wasn't here, how have things in the main universe been? What about Hila? What's she doing?"

Seeing Han Xiao's indisputable expression, Sylvia clenched her teeth, suppressed her boiling curiosity, and explained the changes that had occurred in the past few months.

Sometime earlier, Hila had inherited the Underworld dimension and formed a link with it, so she no longer had to stay in the Underworld to charge it. She had returned to the main universe long ago and was now in the free competition zone, continuing the exploration work.

In the recent few months, the heat of the ambush on Hila gradually cooled down. As the exploration progressed further in the free competition zone, many organizations were already going all out. Furthermore, with the 'conflicts' many Beyond Grade As had with each other, it was very boisterous.

The players' level had increased quite a bit too, and their actions gradually grew more organized. Their presence had been steadily growing in the universe. It was said that there were some small to medium organizations that were already calling the players the Cancer of the Universe, which meant things were following the path Han Xiao was familiar with, only that this nickname was not publicly recognized yet.

The dynasty had also sent a lot of messages that were all related to the development union. Since Han Xiao had hidden for a few months, he had managed to dodge the dynasty's direct questioning.

The preparation of the development union was almost complete. Recruitment was basically already done. The three Universal Civilizations had not held back on interfering with their efforts. The two sides had clashed countless times secretly. Many Beyond Grade As received oppression to various extents, which unfortunately for the three Universal Civilizations, was not very effective. Although Han Xiao did not participate directly, his influence impacted it to some extent. With his permission, the Black Star Army had provided quite a lot of help.

Meanwhile, Dark Lord had already escaped from the chaotic space streams and had publicly arrested another neutral Beyond Grade A. As a direct member of the dynasty, lingering in the Flickering World at this time attracted a lot of attention and hostility from many Beyond Grade As.

All these changes, however, did not affect the dynasty's plan to sell the Evolutionary Totems to the public. The army's logistics department had already produced a ton of Evolutionary Totems, waiting for Han Xiao to charge them. Countless organizations' preorders poured in like tsunamis.

Looking through the changes, Han Xiao thought to himself, Looks like things have been going well while I wasn't around. Manison and the other elderlies really are something… Alright, the formation of the development union is now certain. It's time I make a visit.

Chapter 1083: Exchange and Formation

The fervor for the Flickering World was shared by countless organizations. As the exploration of new Star Fields progressed, the exploration area belonging to the free competition zone got deeper and deeper into the core at a speed much faster than the three previous stages.

Planet Finn was a hub planet of the Emerald Star Cluster located at a superior position where the exterior Star System and the Star System coincided.

Initially, this was first occupied by the Modo Civilization. However, the impact of the conflict between two Beyond Grade A organizations 'coincidentally' reached this location. The Modo Civilization's troops stationed there met with 'accidents', so this planet now had no owner again.

Not long after, the Black Star Army 'happened to' occupy this planet and generously used it as the future headquarters of the Flickering World Beyond Grade A Development Union.

This desolate island was already completely different. It was filled with marks of artificial modifications. Countless Black Star Army engineering ships were constructing all kinds of buildings on the surface and satellites.

The most conspicuous landmark was a skyscraper. This was the conference building of the development union's headquarters. It was shaped like a trophy. An enormous sphere hovered on top of it like a floating fortress. There were also a lot of facilities in that sphere, including the round table conference room exclusively for the Beyond Grade As to host meetings.

At this point of time, a crucial meeting was being held inside it.

After a slight flash before his eyes, Han Xiao's remote projection appeared in the round table conference room. He looked around and saw that many seats were already occupied while more were appearing.

This was the first time Han Xiao had joined the meeting since returning. All the Beyond Grade As who were willing to join the association had been invited to this meeting, not just the ones who initiated it.

Very soon, all the seats were occupied. Manison knocked on the table to signal for everyone to stop chattering.

"Everyone, Black Star is the one who made the suggestion to form the development union. Now that he's back and all members are present, this will be our first full meeting. Some of you might not know each other, so let's start by introducing yourselves."

Even though some of the Beyond Grade As present never had been in contact with some others, they all knew who the others were. This was just a standard procedure, so everyone briefly introduced themselves.

Han Xiao looked around. Most had attended the Meeting of the Gods, but there were also some new faces, including the direct members of the three Universal Civilizations.

At the same time, some older faces did not show up, like those unlucky fellows locked in the Spacetime Amber. In total, the number of attendees was surprisingly fewer than the Meeting of the Gods.

Whenever they saw him looking over, they would all slightly nod at him as a greeting.

The direct members of the three Universal Civilizations are here too, Han Xiao thought.

The reason behind this was not difficult to guess. The development union had been in conflict with the three Universal Civilizations for a few months. Both sides ended up compromising somewhat. One of the terms agreed was having these direct members join the union. Although the association would not possibly let those people have high power, since it was called the Beyond Grade A Association, there was no reason it should reject any Beyond Grade As from joining, even if they were direct members of the three Universal Civilizations.

The initial goal of everyone there was to have a united battlefront for the Beyond Grade As and increase the position of everyone at this grade. However, skipping the steps in between was totally unrealistic. In the beginning stage, no one really planned to use all their cards, so compromising with the three Universal Civilizations was unavoidable. Anyway, this would not go against the initial goal. As long as this platform was created, a new profit network was formed, and the ability to de-escalate conflicts between Beyond Grade As was acquired, the Beyond Grade As would be able to ignore some of the conflicts that were due to their factions.

As for acquiring more power, that had to be slowly earned in the future.

Han Xiao had not come back for a few months, but he had always been paying attention to the preparation progress of the development union. He had quite a lot of intelligence about it and knew very clearly of the basic system and members of the association.

After a round of introductions, Manison looked at Han Xiao and said slowly, "Over the past few months, the preparation for the development union has been going quite well. Black Star, you've only returned recently. Do you have anything to say? You're one of the main initiators, so we'd like to hear your thoughts."

Everyone's attention instantly focused on him.

Han Xiao cleared his throat and said, "I don't have much to say. Everyone has done a good job. We've already spoken about this matter back during the Meeting of the Gods. At the end of it, it was decided that I was to be responsible for creating the communication platform, which is close to completion. As everyone knows, the top priority of the development union is to settle disputes and conflicts between Beyond Grade As. I heard that the relationships between some of you here have not been great lately, so I hope that this platform can be created as soon as possible. The entire universe is in need of a platform like this to bring peace."

"Black Star is absolutely right." Manison took over. "As you all know, there have been some obstacles on the path of creating the development union. Currently, these obstacles are already mostly cleared out. The only thing that's holding us back is the negotiation regarding the Ultimate Knowledges. We have to put this thing aside for the time being. The most crucial matter at hand is the members of the management level so that the development union can be officially formed soon."

As expected, the three Universal Civilizations did not compromise at all on the matter of Ultimate Knowledges. After a series of intense conflicts, both sides put the matter aside and decided to go for a negotiation. However, either side could give the other side what they wanted, nor could either side do anything more. Therefore, this matter would not come to a conclusion any time soon.

Due to this situation, some peak Beyond Grade As like Manison had changed their minds and decided not to let this matter delay the formation of the development union. Hence, this matter was put aside, and Ultimate Knowledge being one of the benefits of the association was not publicized. As for whether the knowledge would be taught privately was another matter.

The last thing standing before the official formation of the association was that the management position holders were yet to be decided, and the reason was that Black Star had yet to return. Now that Black Star was finally back, everyone could not wait to settle this crucial issue.

"That's right. It's time to decide who's to be the president…" A member of The Ancient Ones looked around. "Over the past few months, His Excellency Mechanic Emperor has been enduring a lot of pressure representing the development union. What he has done has been witnessed by all. I nominate Manison as the first president."

As soon as this was said, many supporters followed after. Suddenly, the entire place was discussing Manison.

In the past few months, Manison had been using the connections he had built up over the years. Not only were more than half of the peak Beyond Grade As supporting him, but he had also wooed many of the remaining Beyond Grade A members, especially members of the Ancient Ones. Most people agreed that Manison should be the president.

The other two candidates could not compete at all in the past few months. Knowing that they had no chance, they had basically quit the competition.

However, at this time, subconsciously or consciously, everyone was looking at Han Xiao. He had disappeared for a few months, and his opinion was the most unpredictable to the others.

Manison also could not help but look at Han Xiao. This was the one and only thing that might stop him from becoming the president. He had no choice but to take it seriously.

However, Han Xiao only smiled and did not speak, nor did he intend to.

Kasuyi looked back and forth between the two of them and said, "If there are no objections, let's start the vote. Who here agrees that Manison should be the first Development Union President?"

"Agree."

"Agree."

"Abstained."

"Agree."

Since there were not many people present and everyone there was important, a simple voting process was more than enough.

Everyone had voted, including Han Xiao, who abstained.

Seeing this, Manison was no longer worried. As long as Black Star did not interfere, this position was certainly going to be his.

The direct members of the three Universal Civilizations all abstained their votes. Clearly, they had an agreement. In the end, Manison easily won with an absolute number of votes.

Seeing this, Kasuyi took a deep breath and said with a deep voice, "It's decided then. His Excellency Manison 'Ancient One' Palpatine will, from now on, be the official president for the first term."

"Okay."

The muscles on Manison's face did not move at all. He maintained his poker face and did not say anything. He had no need to be humble.

Clap clap…

Those in attendance clapped a few times symbolically.

After the applause stopped, Kasuyi looked around and asked, "Now, as for the Vice-President, who…"

This time, Han Xiao suddenly smiled and said, "The formation of the association has relied a lot on the Black Star Army's forces in the Flickering World. I think that it's suitable for me to take this position. What do you guys say?"

Everyone exchanged looks and was not surprised.

With Black Star's strength and position, he would be a director at the bare minimum even without the crucial help the Black Star Army had provided. Therefore, of course, he had the right to be the vice president.

Actually, there was a reason Han Xiao did not fight with Manison. He had already decided not to compete for the position of the first president the moment he knew that the president position was term-based.

One of the reasons was that his connections were not as rich as Manison. Another was that he did not want to be the one getting the pressure during the initial stage of the association. If someone else became the president next term, he would have worked for nothing.

This was also one of the reasons Han Xiao had gone to hide in the secondary dimensions for a few months. He would not be able to become the president anyway, so he might as well let Manison and the others endure the pressure and come back later.

I'm the main initiator anyway, and the Black Star Army has provided a lot of help to the development union, so that's a big enough contribution.

Since he could still compete for the next term, Han Xiao was in no hurry. He did not want to directly compete with Manison, so he took the second-highest position as the vice president and planned to only compete for the position of president in the future.

Furthermore, even if he decided to directly compete with Manison now, he would not be able to succeed. Han Xiao never planned to compete with Manison in terms of connections but through the benefits of having him as the president, as explained by Kant and Milizaus. However, the people there still voted for Manison, which meant that they had already made their decision. Therefore, even if he had said anything earlier, these people would not have voted for him.

Although he did have some resources that he could use as chips to obtain some support, such as the Evolution Cube, there was no way he could do the same thing every term. Furthermore, much of those resources could only be used once. If he used it for this term, he might not be able to achieve the same amount of support next term.

Since he completely understood the situation, Han Xiao made the decision not to compete. He would only be able to wrestle with people on Manison's level when his connections and influence reached a higher level.

After all, he had leeks he could harvest, so he would grow much faster than everyone else. With such a unique advantage, this strategy seemed more suitable for him.

Quite a number of people had their eyes on the vice president position. Sadly, none were competent enough, and Kasuyi and the others had no interest. Since Han Xiao was the local, most people gave him face. Manison was in a good mood and supported him too. Therefore, Han Xiao became the vice president smoothly.

After getting this position, Han Xiao was relieved.

Now, this is what I call materialization of position. Getting the vice president position without spending anything is definitely much more cost effective than paying a huge price for the president position.

The director positions that came after had no suspense. They had been decided long ago and belonged to the group of peak Beyond Grade As. Other than that, there were also three 'Honorable Director' positions that had no actual power. They were given to the direct peak Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations. Of course, this was one of the conditions of the compromises.

As the positions were decided, the date of the official formation of the development union was also decided. After these things were dealt with, the meeting ended. Remote projections disappeared one after another, leaving just Manison and Han Xiao's remote projections behind.

"Congratulations, president," Han Xiao said casually.

Manison gave a rare smile and said, "Don't be discouraged. This is too early for you. The future is yours."

Han Xiao blinked with a strange expression.

Although things were going in a different direction compared to the previous life, Manison's goal should have remained unchanged, so he knew about it.

In his previous life, Manison had both pride and ambition. He wanted to make all the Beyond Grade As his shield to help him enter the next territory.

The two of them had different but similar goals. At least for a very long time, Manison would not be able to achieve his goal. He would have to wait for everyone in this grade to become stronger as time passed by.

Han Xiao put this thought away, pondered for two seconds, and asked, "About the negotiation regarding the Ultimate Knowledges, what's the price the three Universal Civilizations have asked for?"

As this issue was brought up, Manison wiped the smile off his face and said meaningfully, "A Super Star Cluster Civilization."

Han Xiao understood instantly and shook his head with resignation.

So, this is what they're planning to do, killing two birds with one stone by using the association against more important opponents and ruining the association's name.

"Will you agree?"

"I don't know. I'll have to see." Manison did not give a response. After he said that, his projection went offline, and Han Xiao was the only one in the conference room.

Han Xiao looked at Manison's empty seat and suddenly chuckled.

Mr. Director, being in this position isn't going to be that easy, you know…

…

Galaxy Calendar Year 730, July 11th. A sudden news bomb exploded in the Flickering World.

Close to a hundred Beyond Grade As made an announcement together. Due to the recent frequent conflicts between them, they had decided to form a guild-type organization to settle physical conflicts between Beyond Grade As and reduce the public damage caused by their battles.

The organization's headquarters would be located in Flickering World, on Planet Finn of the Emerald Star Cluster. Manison would be the president, Black Star would be the vice president, and there would be close to a hundred Beyond Grade A members.

The three Universal Civilizations had also publicly announced that this organization was not illegal. At the same time, they encouraged the Supers in the universe to learn from this and reduce the damage caused by their powers.

The Flickering World Beyond Grade A Development Union was officially founded on this day!

A few months after the explosive news of the ambush on Hila, countless citizens and organizations of the various Star Fields were in an uproar once again!

Chapter 1084: Association's Impact and Holy Light Host

"Have you heard? Close to a hundred Beyond Grade As have formed a new organization in the Flickering World…"

In a military bar inside one of the dynasty's closed bases, the usual boisterous atmosphere was nowhere to be found. Some held their glass up but forgot about drinking it, some caressed their glasses subconsciously, and some were smoking cigars but hardly breathed.

The only common thing they shared was that all of their eyes were on the virtual screen on the bar's wall, which was now playing a political discussion show.

The show was hosted in a studio, where one host was leading the conversation with a few guests. The matter they were discussing was related to the recent big news.

Inside the quiet bar, the only sounds were the voices of the host and the guests.

"I know, the Flickering World Beyond Grade A Development Union, right? It was formed not too long ago. They invited tons of galactic media groups and made the announcement. Now it's spread across the entire universe."

"Almost all the Beyond Grade As in the universe have joined. Tsk tsk, these guys really can't seem to be out of the spotlight."

"According to the information we have," the host said, "the purpose of this organization is to mediate the ever more frequent conflicts between Beyond Grade As. On the day of its establishment, they hosted a meeting where all the members attended. With the galactic media groups as their audience, they publicly mediated more than a dozen conflicts using peaceful negotiations, successfully solving the disputes between tens of Beyond Grade As. As it seems, this method is very effective. Those people all stopped fighting with each other. The frequent Beyond Grade As conflicts lately have been effectively reduced, and no one was unluckily impacted by those conflicts."

"It seems that this organization is really quite useful." A guest who held a high management position in a financial group complained. "The destruction Beyond Grade As can bring is too huge. Conflicts between them have always caused a humongous amount of damage to the public. Either planets were destroyed, or onlookers were accidentally killed. Now that this organization has been formed, these things can be avoided."

"Exactly. I had a friend living in the Shattered Star Ring. He went to watch the battle between Black Star and the Tyrant some decades ago, and because he got too close, he, unfortunately, got killed. There was no compensation or whatsoever after that at all"

Someone said, "I have no idea what those onlookers are thinking. Do they think it's a concert or something?"

"Have the Supers accidentally killed not enough ordinary people? This problem has existed in society for as long as Supers have. According to research, the number of ordinary people directly or indirectly killed by Supers in the entire universe every day is as high as around ten billion. Just let this horrifying number sink in. This is a huge problem that has everything to do with our daily lives."

A guest complained angrily. He was the representative of an organization that supported equal rights between ordinary people and Supers.

"Therefore, I think that the purpose of this organization is much more important than it seems on the surface. Living up to their positions at the top of the Super Grades, the Beyond Grade As have made an amazing stand and set an example for all the Supers in the universe. It's a very responsible act." The host avoided this sensitive topic with a smile. He displayed Manison and Han Xiao's virtual portraits on the screen behind and said, "The two main founders are Manison and Black Star, who have taken the position of president and vice president."

"Oh, these two are the VIPs of VIPs!" A known celebrity made an exaggerated hand gesture and said, "Not much needs to be said about Manison. He's a senior Beyond Grade A whom everyone knows about. No one finds it strange that he's been chosen as the president. However, Black Star is someone who has only risen in the last few decades, yet he surprisingly surpassed the other much more senior members and took the second-highest position."

A Slime wobbled and said, "Beyond Grade As are a group of people who heed strength above all. Not long ago, Black Star made a historical achievement by fighting twelve enemies alone, so whether he's senior enough or not doesn't limit him at all."

"Speaking of which, it seems like that conflict was the fuse that led to Black Star proposing to form the development union, and Manison is only a partner he brought in."

"No no no. From the way I see it, signs were already showing during the Meeting of the Gods. They've been planning this since long ago. Black Star is the one who contributed most to forming the association, so he became the vice president. As for the goal of the Beyond Grade As, who knows? Maybe they're planning to shuffle the deck using this opportunity during the exploration of the Flickering World."

"I've done some research. Black Star has been very active lately. Not only did he take the lead in forming the development union, but he also became a new shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group. The date when the dynasty planned to officially sell the Evolutionary Totems to the public was also brought forward. He even stepped into the entertainment industry. In the files of the Galactic Cinematic Association, the movie adapted from Black Star's true story has already been filmed. The director is the renowned Beny Travol. Maybe we'll see the rise of Black Star very soon on screen."

The host and the guests chatted.

Pa!

This time, a dynasty army officer slammed his glass on the table, curled his lips, and said with disdain, "What bullsh*t mediating. Just a group of Beyond Grade As putting up a show. Only idiots would believe what they're saying."

The people in the bar laughed.

Everyone there was a soldier of the dynasty who had a much clearer view of the matter than ordinary people and was on the dynasty's side. With this army officer starting the conversation, the others all started chattering.

"This can be basically considered as the official association of the Beyond Grade As, looks like they finally are planning to take some of their rights back from the three Universal Civilizations."

"I didn't expect Black Star to be the main founder. Tsk, outsiders really can't be trusted. To think I actually admired him for some time in the past."

"Nothing weird about it. He isn't a citizen of the dynasty, so there's no reason to demand his absolute loyalty."

"The future of the three Universal Civilizations is going to be tough from now on. They're going to have another powerful competitor."

Hearing the discussion between his comrades, Gaud shook his glass filled with amber-colored wine and silently stared at Han Xiao's portrait in the show with unknown emotions in his eyes.

"Your position is getting higher and higher, huh…"

Due to the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy being snatched away, Gaud had been paying close attention to Han Xiao. He had been watching Han Xiao continuously getting more and more resources, acquiring a higher and higher position in the universe.

The ambush on Hila some time ago had shocked him when it revealed how fast Han Xiao was growing.

Gaud stopped shaking his glass. The wine spun in it and formed a vortex. He looked down at the vortex and smirked.

"Manison has planned this long ago. Now the chance had finally come. The development union is not a bad excuse. I'll most likely join it after becoming a Beyond Grade A too. But I didn't expect you to support this idea too. Do you agree with that theory about the shared battlefront for Beyond Grade As Manison gave, or… have you discovered that too?"

In Black Star Palace…

"Looks like the first appearance of the development union is very successful…"

Han Xiao leaned back in his chair, rested his legs on the table, and looked through the news from the various media in the quantum network with a satisfied expression.

Not long ago, the development union had officially announced its creation to the outside world. As the vice president, he had also made an appearance at the ceremony.

To normal people, the development union was suddenly formed out of nowhere. The movements of close to a hundred Beyond Grade As attracted all the attention, so as soon as the news was out, the entire universe started discussing it.

The majority of the forces in the Flickering World were the most shocked by this sudden event.

There were a lot of organizations exploring the Flickering World, but to these organizations, the true situation in the free competition zone was actually split between three sides. The dynasty was one, the federation and the church shared another side, and the Super Star Cluster Alliance was the last side.

Comparatively, the rest of the organizations there were scattered. The difference was like the conflict between companies and between nations.

Originally, although there were many Beyond Grade A organizations, they all belonged to different sides. However, as they united, if they formed a profit union, another huge force would appear. The situation would turn from the conflict between three sides into four sides.

However, this was just the speculation the outside world had. Neither Manison nor Han Xiao planned to make any aggressive moves. In the negotiation with the three Universal Civilizations, they tried to ask them to deal with the Super Star Cluster Alliance. Although Han Xiao was quite tempted to use this opportunity against the Modo Civilization, for the sake of the big picture, he could only reject it.

As per their plan, the biggest purpose of the development union currently was to provide a communication platform. Its top priority was to slowly connect the resources of its members and form a profit union between Beyond Grade As. After this huge profit network was formed and its foundation was built, creating a shared battlefront would finally be meaningful. Otherwise, the development union would only be an empty shell.

"Achieving this will take a very long time, and the three Universal Civilizations will definitely try to slow it down nonstop. Therefore, before it's done, the development union won't be able to do anything else. Even if those Beyond Grade As have their own plans, they won't show it at the initial stage and will only support uniting the resources, achieving a win-win situation," Han Xiao murmured.

The Beyond Grade A Association had just been formed, so there was still a very long road ahead for both Manison and his goals. This was a long-term plan that would take decades at the minimum and could not be hurried, so there was no need for him to keep thinking about it.

What was worth mentioning was that, using money and connections, as the only exception, Sorokin was able to acquire the position as a director where everyone else was peak Beyond Grade A.

After hearing about Sorokin's acts from Traveler, he looked unaffected, but he actually secretly paid a lot of attention to this guy. As a shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group, Han Xiao did not act against Sorokin as it would only make Sorokin alarmed.

However, all things aside, Sorokin really had a knack for making money.

"This way, my goal is basically achieved. When the Calamity of the Supers erupts, I will be able to heavily interfere with it and even guide the main storyline of that version…" Han Xiao exhaled with a relaxed mood.

As the peak of personal strength, Beyond Grade As were the idols of countless Supers. Hence, Beyond Grade As uniting could guide the movement of the entire Super society to a certain extent. This was also one of the most important reasons why, when the Calamity of the Supers erupted, the influence of the Beyond Grade As quickly became stronger in the entire universe.

Temporarily putting this matter aside, Han Xiao opened the forums to look at the players' opinions.

As expected, the focus of the players was not the meaning of the development union but the names of this many Beyond Grade As.

At this moment, Aurora walked in.

Han Xiao waved at her and said, "Come here."

Aurora walked toward Han Xiao. She had suddenly been called to the office and was quite confused.

Han Xiao suddenly grabbed Aurora's forearm and pressed on it softly, all the way up to her shoulder.

Aurora's body was stiff, but she did not move away. She was both curious and anxious.

"W-what are you doing?"

Han Xiao sized her up, took his hands off her, and said, "I've noticed that your physique is very special."

"W-what do you mean?"

Pa!

Han Xiao took out the containment device of the Holy Light Particle and slapped it on the table.

"When I went to the secondary dimensions, I found a new Primal Esper Ability Entity. I'm hoping to put it inside your body. What do you think?"

After thorough consideration, he had decided to find a host for the Holy Light Particle.

He acknowledged the potential of the new power system brought by the Holy Light Seed, but it would consume its core essence. Therefore, finding a host who could heal its kidney deficiency was better than creating an Energy Host.

Hence, Aurora was the top choice.

If she turned out to be incompatible, Han Xiao would consider its host from his previous life, Evans.

"Primal Esper Ability?" Aurora curiously looked at the gold energy inside the containment device with her eyes wide open.

Unhappy, the Holy Light Particle sent a resentful telepathic message. "Hey, this is the host you've found for me? She's too young!"

"Young? She's just about ten years younger than me." Han Xiao rolled his eyes.

"What‽ A Beyond Grade A like you must be at least a few hundred years old!" The Holy Light Particle was even more enraged. "Then, isn't she a few hundred years old too? Shameless! Still acting as if she's so young!"

"… Can I strangle it?"

Aurora was speechless.

I am young! What do you mean acting!

The Holy Light Particle was still complaining. "I need a strong male host. Only then will he be able to match my power!"

Knowing his personality well, Han Xiao said, "Stop spitting nonsense. One more word and I'll give you to the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy to let him have his way with you."

The Holy Light Particle shut up instantly.

Han Xiao pressed on the containment device and a needle came out of it. Seeing this, Aurora reluctantly reached out her hand, bit her lips, and let Han Xiao plug the needle into her.

Boom!

The next moment, a strong blinding light exploded in front of Han Xiao!

Chapter 1085: Perfect Host and Bait

As the Holy Light Particle was injected into Aurora's body, it started to fuse with her cells. The Vital Energy Esper Ability inside her also started to react to it quite vigorously.

A pale-golden light shot out from every inch of Aurora's skin. She turned into a bright mini light source, as if every string of her hair had turned into light beams. She floated into the air, releasing an elegant and holy aura.

Han Xiao was paying close attention to Aurora and held the empty containment device in his hand. If he saw any signs of Aurora being damaged by the process, he would suck the Holy Light Particle out instantly.

Thankfully, the fusion process went very smoothly. When the light dissipated, Aurora finally descended to the floor. She looked like she had yet to regain focus from the state she was in earlier.

Pa!

Han Xiao snapped his fingers and said, "How are you feeling?"

"Somewhat… good?"

Aurora pressed on her heart and was uncertain.

"Since you were not hurt by it, you're now the host of the Holy Light Particle. Can you feel its power?"

"Are you talking about this?"

Aurora closed her eyes to sense it for a moment, before extending her hands with palms up. She shook them, and a cluster of gold light appeared. It had tiny dots like a group of fireflies.

She's able to use it this soon? There's usually an adjustment period after the host fuses with a Primal Esper Ability.

However, I heard that the shorter the adjustment period is, the more compatible the host is.

The Vital Energy Esper Ability and the Holy Light Particle are indeed quite compatible. Maybe some kind of chemical reaction occurred. If that's the case, I will be able to make use of the Holy Light Particle to the maximum, and my plan will be easier to execute…

Han Xiao caressed his chin.

He reached out to touch the cluster of light on top of Aurora's palm, but this cluster of light actually dodged aside. Finding this quite funny, Han Xiao smiled and said, "Ah Ho, I know you can share the senses of your host after the fusion and can hear me speaking. Stop hiding. How's this host?"

"Hmm…"

The Holy Light Particle appeared and yawned like a cat in the middle of a stretch. No longer looking down on Aurora, it immediately changed its attitude.

"It feels way too good. This is the first time I've sensed such rich life force. This is the best host I've ever had…"

"Humph, that's not what you said earlier," Aurora said unhappily.

"I was wrong. You're the best. No one else could be nearly good enough." The Holy Light Particle's light cluster circled around Aurora like a puppy.

Han Xiao curled his lips.

Tsk tsk, weren't you very tough just moments ago?

Aurora practiced for a while and was soon able to fully control it. In her senses, it was like she suddenly had an extra arm. Controlling it was a piece of cake.

"Go back and practice it more. The Primal Esper Abilities all have multiple uses. With the Holy Light Particle, you'll be able to protect yourself from more dangers," Han Xiao said.

Aurora's job was to heal since her Esper Ability lacked destructive power. Now that she was the master of the Holy Light Particle, she would acquire many new abilities such as a stronger physique, high-speed flight, dimension traveling, punishing evil, and many others.

These abilities would increase her survivability by a huge extent, especially the ability to travel between dimensions. She would be able to escape much easier in the future if she was in danger.

However, the most important ability to Han Xiao was the ability to provide Holy Light Seeds. After he tested it, to his absolute surprise, his theory was right—Aurora's Vital Energy Esper Ability could indeed replenish the energy the Holy Light Particle spent in giving out Holy Light Seeds. This meant that the new power system with the Holy Light Seed as the core could totally work.

This was extremely useful to the Black Star Army. It could both act as encouragement for the army's warriors and attract ordinary people by letting them see the hope of becoming Supers.

Han Xiao briefly explained his plan. A little shocked, Aurora said softly, "So, you're trying to spread it out…"

"Something like that. However, you're the host now, so I'll have to get your permission."

Aurora wanted to say something but did not.

She had tested the ability to give out Holy Light Seeds earlier. Although her body could endure it, it would spend quite a lot of life force. If used often, she did not know if the life force she had been naturally accumulating would be enough. She might have to experience the feeling of being sucked dry every day.

After hesitating for a while, Aurora suddenly made up her mind. She closed her eyes and said firmly, "Okay. I—I can take it!"

"Why do you look like you've just decided to sacrifice yourself?" Han Xiao squeezed her nose and said with a smile, "Don't worry, I won't make you work for free. You can retrieve those Holy Light Seeds, which will not only make up for the life force you've lost but also help your life force grow at a rate much faster than you accumulate every day."

"I'm not sure if it's good to just snatch away what others worked hard for…" Aurora rejected it slightly. This went against her principles.

"Hahaha…" Han Xiao laughed out loud and said with the tone of a rich man, "That's easy! Money can't solve everything, but it definitely can solve most things. I can hire a group of people to raise Holy Light Seeds specifically for you to harvest, which isn't different from any other jobs at its core. I'm basically paying them for their time to create value for me. As long as the salary is good enough, it'll be a totally legitimate exchange on both sides, so you don't have to feel bad about it."

"That does make sense…" Although Aurora leaned toward the lawful kind side of things, she was not stubborn. After hearing Han Xiao's explanation, she did not reject it much anymore.

Snatching away the fruit of others' labor without saying anything and telling others this was a job from the beginning were completely different things. Growing the Holy Light Seeds with meditation and other methods was just like any other job; the workers were no different from the other employees of the army.

Han Xiao chose Aurora to be the host not only because she might be able to use the Holy Light Seed ability to the maximum but also because he wanted Aurora to benefit from the fast growth provided by harvesting the Holy Light Seeds so that her level would increase faster.

Anyway, Aurora's growth had no limits, and harvesting leeks would be countless times more efficient than naturally accumulating life force. She would basically have a group of people earning EXP for her. It had a Shadow Clone-vibe to Han Xiao.

If Aurora could step into the next level, the Black Star Army having three Beyond Grade As would really become a reality.

Han Xiao already had this thought when he came across the Underworld dimension. His goal was not for Aurora to gain a stronger healing ability but access to the functions of the Underworld. 'Edo Tensei' could only be achieved if Aurora became a Beyond Grade A too.

Compared to her healing ability, Han Xiao was more interested in those powerful individuals sleeping in the Underworld. They would be a very strong force.

What a little genius I am… Han Xiao chuckled in his mind.

The only problem was the Holy Accord organization. These people seemed especially interested in Primal Esper Abilities. If they discovered that the Holy Light Particle was in Aurora, they would most likely try to take it from her.

On the other hand, this would be quite a good bait too, he would not be able to find the Holy Accord if they decided to keep hiding. The Holy Accord might not dare to attack him, but they would definitely dare to attack the Supers under his command.

As for Aurora's safety, of course, Han Xiao was not going to forget about it. He planned to give Aurora a King mechanical suit.

Not only that, he was even planning to build a few spare King suits and put the Throne on different people to ensure he could arrive at their locations anytime. He totally took the King as a teleportation device.

The King was extremely costly to build, so doing this was very luxurious. However, with the extravagantly profitable business of the Evolutionary Totems and as a shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group, he would earn an outrageous number of Enas every year. Therefore, he was not short on cash.

Han Xiao then told Aurora to go and learn to use the Holy Light Particle better and that the Holy Light Emissary plan would be carried out once she was ready.

Watching Aurora leave the room, Han Xiao could not help but think of Evans.

"How's Evans doing?"

Phillip appeared and said, "He's still getting to know his Esper Ability, hum…"

Han Xiao turned to look at the surveillance image. Ever since he sent Evans back, he had been undergoing secret training. Since Han Xiao did not give any orders, he had yet to replicate any Esper Abilities, so he was completely powerless and was still at the lowest Grade E.

"Have you found the targets I asked you to find?" Han Xiao asked.

"Immortals with compatible abilities have been selected. This is the list, hum…"

A mini bookshelf appeared beside Phillip. He searched around and picked out a deck of data. He then threw it up into the air. The flying pieces of paper turned into individual virtual screens, showing the records of different people to Han Xiao.

Han Xiao glanced at him.

Kiddo, what's with all these flashy tricks? Showing off?

While rubbing Phillip's face on the table like a toy, Han Xiao quickly read through these documents.

His New EsGod Cultivation Plan followed strict rules on what Esper Abilities to absorb. In order for Evans to have a perfect growth path, he had always been looking for Esper Abilities that were suitable for Evans in the early stage. The players in these files were all Espers under two categories—physique enhancement types and psychological enhancement types.

Since Evans was only Grade E, absorbing two Esper Abilities was the most suitable. Physique and mind were the most basic attributes, so this was the best combination. With his help, Evans did not have to take the path of killing like EsGod did. Therefore, he would not have to worry about his combat capability in the early stages and could focus on building a strong foundation.

"These two will do."

Having picked two players with the best abilities. Han Xiao told Phillip to give them the specific missions.

At this time, a notification suddenly popped up on the interface.

_____________________

[Liberate Beast Ancestor's Organization] Completed!

"Oh? The team I sent a few months ago has succeeded?" Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Before he traveled to the secondary dimensions, a group of Beast Ancestor officers led by Jotina had come to join him and made a request to liberate the Beast Ancestor's headquarters.

Back then, Han Xiao had given this mission to the people who were in the Shattered Star Ring base. Now that a few months had passed, the results of that had finally come. It seemed to be quite successful. There should very soon be a group of people coming to join him.

…

The last planet of the Beast Ancestor's headquarters was covered in flames like its ground was burning. The planet's defense measures were already all destroyed, and a ton of spaceship fragments floated in the planet's orbit.

Black Star Army battleships hovered above the planet, sucking up a huge amount of resources and countless captives using absorption beams. Most were rescued females and clueless offspring.

In the cabin of one transport ship, captives of a variety of races cowered in tiny groups, filled with fear. Groups of Black Star warriors separated them into warriors, females, and offspring.

"Don't move! Stand still!" the captain of the transport ship commanded.

To the side, wearing a black battle suit rather similar to Hila, Mia held a bag of snacks in her hand, leaned on a mechanical spear, and scanned the big group of captives before her while occasionally putting the sugar beans into her mouth.

Beast Ancestor soldier captives were absorbed into the cabin. They seemed agitated and ready to retaliate whenever. However, when they saw Mia standing near the wall, these captives all shivered and wiped that thought from their minds.

In the battle earlier, they had seen a Calamity Grade officer stationed in the headquarters get violently chopped into pieces by Mia with their very own eyes. No one dared resist in front of her.

At this time, a commotion occurred nearby. Mia turned to look over, and to her surprise, a few rescued females were arguing with the Black Star warriors and resisting their orders.

"Who the hell are you? Do you have any idea who our partner is? How dare you do this to us!"

"Let go! Stop dragging me!"

"When Master Beast Ancestor comes back, he'll crush you all!"

These people who were yelling were grouped along with the others but were still yelling and scolding, mentioning Beast Ancestor's name every other sentence.

Seeing this, Mia curled her lips and shook her head.

This time, the captain beside her sighed and said, "Pitiful, aren't they? These females who are imprisoned by Beast Ancestor are basically completely cut off from the outside world. To most, that's a dark life filled with nothing but despair, but there are also some twisted ones who somehow began to admire Beast Ancestor and became honored by their identity. Although rescuing these females is our mission, maybe many of them don't want to be saved. They only want to continue their old life."

Mia glanced at him and said, "Do your job. The mission is all I care about. I'm not interested in these things."

Have a bucket of cold water poured on him, the captain did not carry on chatting with Mia and continued to direct his subordinates.

This time, Mia's communicator rang. After she picked it up, Jotina's wild face appeared, only it was now shining with holy and motherly love.

"How are the women and young offspring? Are all of them safe?" Jotina asked immediately.

Mia smiled and replied, "Don't worry, we've rescued them all. They're all very touched."

"That's great. I'll share this good news with the army commander right now!" Jotina was overjoyed. "By the way, after you return, I'll teach you some strong moves."

Before waiting for a response, Jotina had already hastily hung up the communication.

"How impatient." Mia chuckled.

Although Jotina publicly made the request to reproduce with her direct boss and appalled everyone present, after spending some time together, the army officers had realized she was really easy to befriend, being direct and decisive in everything. After a few months, she had left a good impression on many of them.

Mia was the closest to her. Both of them were 'muscular ladies', so they had countless shared interests.

Putting the communicator away, Mia looked at the group of people in front of her, scanned past the panicked or lost expressions, and exhaled.

"Nero, your godfather is really admirable. No wonder even Her Excellency Hila is willing to follow him…"

Although Black Star eliminated Gorutan out of personal revenge, judging from the results of it, this was indeed a great deed for the entire universe. Mia admired him from the bottom of her heart.

Chapter 1086: The Definition of a Qualified Second in Command

As the silver alloy gate slowly slid open, inside was a room fully made of polymer materials. The walls and the floor were all cream-colored, reflective, and smooth.

Five enormous showcases were displayed in the middle of the room, with a Beyond Grade A sealed by the Spacetime Amber inside every one of them. All of them were in different postures, all of their expressions fixed on their faces. Other than these, there was nothing else in this room.

"This is my collection room."

As the group walked into the room, Han Xiao spoke. Behind him were the former officers of the Beast Ancestor, including Jotina.

As soon as the field team destroyed the Beast Ancestor's headquarters, Jotina led her sisters and brothers to express their appreciation to Han Xiao. Han Xiao remembered that he had promised to take them to see Gorutan, so he took them there.

This was the collection room he used to hold his five Beyond Grade A captives. There was the name of each captive on every showcase. They were the church's 'Red Devil' Tolaen; the federation's 'Lone Ranger' Jackornitz, 'Energy Soul' Womre, and Hades; and 'Beast Ancestor' Gorutan.

The five Beyond Grade A specimens displayed there were the best proof of his achievements. Just this scene alone was enough to shock everyone.

Jotina's eyes locked onto Gorutan immediately. Seeing that this man she had hated and feared all her life was locked inside the Amber, joy filled her heart.

"You deserve it!"

Jotina clenched her fists with excitement. She felt that this was the happiest day of her life. The dark times in her past seemed to have all been forgotten. The world in her eyes seemed to be colorful once again.

It was like a breeze of fresh air blew past her mind, bringing the mountains of hatred, despair, anger away with it, only leaving the refreshed feeling of hope for a new life.

She turned to look at Han Xiao. Her eyes were filled with admiration and gentleness.

In her eyes, Black Star seemed to be glowing with holiness, like he was the light that would lead her toward a new life.

Feeling Jotina's passionate sight, Han Xiao's face trembled slightly.

He did not have much contact with Jotina, but he had a very vivid impression of how direct and passionate she was.

The reward of [Liberate Beast Ancestor's Organization] had already been given. He had received a lot of Favorability, and he was guessing that Jotina's loyalty meter to him was almost going to explode.

Han Xiao coughed and said, "Some of you don't have an exact position yet. Since we just rescued a large group of Beast Ancestor's young offspring, I shall leave them to you guys to guide. Any problems?"

"Not at all!" Everyone nodded, quite happy about this arrangement.

"Take your time and look around. I have some things to attend to."

Han Xiao found an excuse to leave alone. Jotina and the others had been troubled by this hatred for many years, so he did not want to disturb them from venting it. Anyway, Phillip would be watching over them. He did not have to stay there.

After returning to his office, Han Xiao pondered about the human resource distribution of the army.

"Currently, the top-tier Calamity Grades under my command are only Hadavy, Lothaire, Feidin, and Jotina. The other ones with potential have yet to grow up. These more than a dozen Beast Ancestor officers are quite important. Together with this group of young children of Beast Ancestor, they will surely form a new faction in the army in the future…"

There were all kinds of factions in the Black Star Army, not including Han Xiao. They could be classified into a few big groups.

One was the elder faction led by Herlous, among which were smaller groups such as Sunils, Godorans, Aquamarinians, and so on. This faction represented the senior members of the army. Another was the academy faction led by Lagi and Nero, formed mostly from the graduates of the Super Academy. They were quite active. Third was the mainstream faction led by the Calamity Grades who joined later on, which was also the largest faction mainly made of official warriors and mercenaries with no backgrounds. Fourth was the political faction led by Sylvia and Reynold, mainly consisting of those who did not take part in the battles but took care of the army's other matters. They managed the army's day to day affairs, logistics, economics, and so on.

Jotina and the others would most likely form a Beast Ancestor faction after they stabilized their positions in the army.

As for Hila, since she was always alone, she had no faction. The Black Star Guards had limited influence on the various departments of the army, so they did not form a faction too. Lothaire, who was managing the Assassin's Society outside the army base, was a secret, so he was not in any factions.

These factions would have conflicted with each other privately, but with Han Xiao's existence, they all held themselves back. All big organizations had continuous internal conflicts as they expanded, but the Black Star Army was considered a new organization in terms of how long ago it had been formed, so the internal conflicts were not large, limited to internal business conflicts.

Completely getting rid of internal conflicts was impossible. Everyone had their own mindset, and there was no way to ask people to give themselves selflessly. Even pillars like Herlous had their own personal goals—for example, to obtain more benefits for his Sunil race.

Power could change one's mind. The longer the high-level officers worked for the army, the more they would want to obtain. Furthermore, those Supers who joined the Black Star Army later on came to search for a brighter future in the first place, so no matter how large the cake was, the competition would never disappear.

"It's the same for the development union. It's only just been created, so the factions have not formed yet. Once the resources are united to a certain extent, there will definitely be factions…"

He could guess that the three Universal Civilizations would try to infiltrate the Beyond Grade A Association by dividing it, as there would definitely be some who did not agree with the shared battlefront for Beyond Grade As theory. These people would be easier to woo.

Beyond Grade As were all full of pride. The root of factions being formed was the different opinions people had to begin with. The development union was fated to be full of arguments since it was created, but the upper echelons above the position of director all knew how important it was for them to unite. The stage where the association's resources were linked and united was crucial.

As the vice president, although his position was lower than Manison's on paper, it did not mean much. How much weight his words carried depended on two things—his overall strength and his influence in the association.

"The resources uniting stage is my chance. I can use my advantage to meet more members and form my own faction, slowly expanding my network to catch up to Manison. As long as there are enough people who support me, I'll be able to have as big an impact on day-to-day decision making as Manison. It will also be beneficial for me to have consecutive terms in the future too. Furthermore, if I don't do anything, I might not even be able to maintain the vice president position…"

Han Xiao pondered. He had chosen to take a step back because he wanted to slowly accumulate his advantages.

And now there was a great opportunity right in front of him. Although the three Universal Civilizations had accepted that the development union was legal, Dark Lord's mission had yet to end.

This meant that Clotti, who was an honorable director on paper, would still attack other members. This would undoubtedly damage the development union's credibility. This was an act of provocation and contempt from the Universal Civilizations, as well as a way of testing the waters.

"Since this is the case, those neutral Beyond Grade As hired by Super Star Cluster Civilizations will probably be very afraid. This looks like a good opportunity for me to cut in. If I'm able to convince the dynasty's upper echelons to stop Dark Lord's mission, not only will I be able to display how important I am as the vice president, but I will also receive favorability from those neutral Beyond Grade As…"

Having thought of this, Han Xiao told Phillip to send a message to all the neutral Beyond Grade As in the association. The message started with some formal greetings and routine questions like "Have you eaten?". He then brought up the matter regarding Dark Lord.

Although he decided to personally settle this issue, Han Xiao did not want to keep it a secret. Only spare tires would help others quietly in the dark. As for him, he would either not do it or let everyone know he was the one who did it.

Therefore, the Great Mechanic Han first planned to contact these neutral Beyond Grade As who were possible targets of Dark Lord and tell them to bring this matter up in the next meeting when everyone attended. All the Beyond Grade A members would host a meeting together once every so often. The development union made this kind of act official, which was also one of the initial reasons to form this communication platform.

"Speaking of which, Dark Lord captured Traveler, and Traveler put the blame on Sorokin, so the dynasty definitely won't let this slip easily. I wonder how they're going to punish the Limitless Financial Group."

Han Xiao chuckled.

Beep beep!

Right at that moment, his communicator rang.

The federation and the church had sent him a message one after the other. The content was the eleventh revision of the terms of bailing their allies.

Han Xiao looked through them. Compared to the initial version, the compensation the federation and the church offered was much richer.

Since he had never given any suggestions, the ones who were in charge of drafting the terms on both sides were almost going mad.

"It's been quite a few months. I've tortured them enough. Time to bring this to a conclusion."

Han Xiao tutted and changed some terms on both sides, such as swapping some resources compensations into gold-grade blueprints.

The two Universal Civilizations both had a very rich inventory of gold-grade blueprints, so the blueprints they would be willing to give out were not crucial ones. However, this was not important to Han Xiao at all as it was just a source of God's Trait Transformation Points.

As soon as the two price lists were sent, the people of the federation and the church were immediately overjoyed. With no hesitation, they sent a communication request and started an official negotiation with Han Xiao.

This time, Han Xiao did not torture them. After some negotiation, an agreement was made. He would receive three Universal Treasure Grade blueprints.

The captives he planned to return first were Tolaen and Hades, one for each side.

He did not sell the federation's allies to the church. Although this would be quite a useful move, it had its cons.

Anyway, he still had two more federation captives. What Han Xiao needed now was influence over the Universal Civilizations to improve his position in the development union, and the best way to do that was to not make any moves. As long as the captives were still in his hands, the Federation of Light would have to give him face to a certain extent, and the church would still have hope about him selling the federation's allies to them. Therefore, he was not going to let go of all the captives easily.

After confirming the agreement, Han Xiao looked at these two relieved diplomatic officials and slowly said, "I shall wait for the day of your public apologies.'

Public apologies from the federation and the church were the first terms on the compensation agreements.

"Surely, please pay attention to the news."

The two diplomatic officials bade farewell in their own traditional ways before ending the call. Their remote projections disappeared.

Han Xiao leaned back, crossed his legs, and murmured, "The federation and the church have compromised. For the time being, the dynasty will also follow through with their decision to make selling the Evolutionary Totems public to mend their relationship with me. They won't be targeting the development union on the surface. From the way it looks, the three Universal Civilizations are not going to cause any problems for quite a while…"

He knew the characteristics of the three Universal Civilizations very well, so he knew that this peace would last a few months to a year.

However, this would only be calm before the storm, as the three Universal Civilizations still had an arch enemy to deal with—the Super Star Cluster Alliance, which had been keeping a low profile and expanding in the free competition zone.

Once the three Universal Civilizations were ready, they would certainly deal the Super Star Cluster Alliance a heavy blow, and it would not be the same gentle way they dealt with the development union. They definitely would not hold back, to eliminate the unrealistic ambition of these Super Star Cluster Civilizations. It could also be said that the three Universal Civilizations were only forgiving about the Beyond Grade As because the Super Star Cluster Alliance was their top priority.

"In this brief window, I'll have to keep building my advantages."

Han Xiao looked at the interface. He had been receiving tons of EXP every single day. Although the cost of leveling up from level 320 to 340 was outrageous, in the face of his merciless leek harvesting machine, he would have enough sooner or later.

The players had become familiar with the Flickering World version, exploring while fighting one another. It was intense.

Han Xiao planned to make their game experience richer, so he wanted to host the Army Tournament that he had come up with some time ago and make it a large festival event for the faction.

The happier the players were, the more motivated they would be to contribute more EXP to him.

…

At the same time, at a certain hidden location in Black Star Palace, a player called Paradise Disco was led by two mechanical soldiers through multiple security checks and down a dark corridor.

There were no decorations in this corridor at all, only pale white lights that extended deeper ahead. At the end of the corridor was a metal wall and a turning corner. No sound could be heard other than their footsteps.

Feeling the cold and frightening atmosphere, Paradise Disco could not help but ask, "Buddy, where are we going?"

The two mechanical soldiers had no intention to reply and continued walking in synchronized steps.

"What's so secretive?" Paradise Disco opened the interface and mumbled, "What on earth is this mission anyway?"

On the mission list, a mission called [Special Experiment] was glowing.

To Paradise Disco's recollection, this mission was suddenly triggered, and he did not do anything. It asked him to follow random mechanical soldiers to the destined location to carry out a special experiment, and that was all the introduction the mission had. The reward was exorbitant. It was about the reward of seven to eight Grade B missions.

Curiosity drove him to accept the mission, and on the way to the destination, he never stopped guessing.

Did I come across the secrets of the Black Star Army?

Has the army actually been carrying out some kind of forbidden secret experiment?

Why did I trigger it?

While he was making wild guesses, the mechanical soldiers in front of him stopped, and before them was an ordinary alloy gate.

After passing the identity scan, the gate opened. Paradise Disco quickly looked in, and a white lab entered his sights.

At this time, there was another player in the room, and he looked over too. The two of them looked at each other and were both slightly stunned.

"You accepted the mission too?"

"Special Experiment, right?"

"Yes, yes, that's the one. Do you know the details?"

"No idea, I've only just arrived too."

"It's so mysterious. I love it."

The two of them chattered and exchanged information. They became even more intrigued.

Since they had come to such a secret place in the headquarters, it could be no ordinary matter.

At this time, a team of mechanical soldiers pushed two life-sustaining cabins in. Two mechanical soldiers then took out two facial devices that blocked the wearer's senses and passed them to the two players.

The leading mechanical soldier captain said, "Lie in the cabin, wear the mask, and wait for the experiment to start."

The two players exchanged looks and, suppressing their curiosity, went inside the cabins.

Paradise Disco put on the mask and instantly fell into darkness. His vision, hearing, and smell were all gone. He had no way of knowing what was happening in the outside world.

Both of his hands and legs were locked up tight; he could not move at all.

Time went by extremely slow in this state. Every second felt like years.

Paradise Disco became even more curious. He almost wanted to break the restraints a few times and see what was happening. However, the heavy failure punishment of this mission discouraged him from doing so.

Just as he was about to get impatient, a notification suddenly popped up on the interface.

Your Grade B+ Potential Esper Ability [Physique Enhancement—Bone and Muscle Inflation] has been taken away!

You have entered [Ability Frozen] state. You are not able to use any abilities related to your Esper Ability.

Duration: Infinite

"W-what‽"

Paradise Disco was shocked and appalled.

Chapter 1087: Made Friends

"Where's my Esper Ability‽"

On the interface, a ton of abilities were now gray and frozen. Even the passive attributes given by the Esper Ability were gone. Paradise Disco immediately panicked and tried to leave the cabin.

This time, a cold metal hand pressed onto his chest and held him tightly in place. It was a mechanical soldier stopping him from moving. Paradise Disco was wearing a mask that sealed off all his senses, so all he could see was darkness and nothing else. He had no choice but to give up struggling and anxiously wait for the experiment to end.

Not knowing how long had passed, Paradise Disco suddenly felt that the devices that locked him in place opened up. He instantly stood up and took off his mask. He then looked around nervously, only to realize he was at the same place he was before, and the mechanical soldiers looked like they had never moved at all.

"My Esper Ability is gone. Is yours too?" Another player taking part in the experiment was released too and spoke with shock.

"That's right. Mine is gone too."

The two of them quickly exchanged information and realized that they were both in the infinite duration [Ability Frozen] state. They were both in a state of panic.

Paradise Disco hastily asked the mechanical soldier on the side, "What have you done to us?"

Following the answer Han Xiao had set for them to give, the mechanical soldier said monotonously, "It was just an experiment. The army is developing a special device to suppress Esper Genes. It might be widely available in the future."

I knew it's an experiment involving secret weapons!

The two of them exchanged and saw the same emotion in each other's eyes. Paradise Disco quickly asked the question they both cared most about.

"Will our abilities recover?"

"Of course. In the research plan, Immortals are the best experiment targets. According to the logistics department, the Immortals only have to die and revive to refresh their body state and recover their ability. In the future, the Immortals in the army might be equipped with this kind of weapon," the mechanical soldier replied emotionlessly.

Hearing that their abilities could recover, the two of them immediately breathed a sigh of relief.

The two of them had absolutely no doubt about this explanation. After all, the 'Black Star Army Badge: Evolution' had already happened, so developing secret weapons sounded just like what the army would do.

In the players' eyes, this somewhat evil style completely aligned with the Black Star Army!

"This is the army's secret plan. You have both signed the confidentiality agreement. Remember, do not tell anyone about what happened here," the mechanical soldier said with a serious expression while returning their communication devices to them.

Paradise Disco took the communication device, looked at the player beside him, and saw suppressed joy in his eyes.

Confidentiality agreement? Hehe, that won't stop us. You think taking our communication devices away will prevent this from leaking this? Impossible, the army has no power over the forums.

As if the army will find out if we make a post about it.

The two of them were secretly excited and were already thinking about how they were going to share this secret on the forums. This was not because they wanted to get in the way of the army's interests but because their impulse to leak spoilers just could not be stopped.

Didn't you hear the mechanical soldier? He said that this kind of weapon might be widely available to the army in the future. Won't it be another type of suicidal attack like the explosion backpack and the army badge? We've come to know about it much earlier than the others. What reason do we have to not show it off?

Of course, the two of them had no idea that this was just an excuse Han Xiao had made up. He did not want to expose Evans' existence, so he made up a reason not to let the outside world have any suspicion.

He purposely let the mechanical soldiers tell the two of them because he wanted to use them to spread misleading information, making the players think that this was a research and development project of some kind of secret weapon. This way, when the players took part in it in the future, he would not have to find another excuse again.

After the mission completion notification popped up on their interfaces, the two of them took their things and were too lazy to go back the way they came from, so they asked the mechanical soldier to help to send them to the afterlife.

With a flash of white light, the two of them revived in the populated base hall and checked their status immediately.

"My ability really came back."

Paradise Disco was now finally relieved. He instantly opened up the forums and wrote down what he had just experienced. He added the title 'Shocking! The army's secret weapon turns out to be…' and posted it.

As proven by facts, there was a reason this type of intriguing title had always been popular. This post attracted the attention of some players very quickly, and people started to comment on it.

"Is this true? Why have I never seen this mission before?"

"Suppress Esper Genes? I seem to recall that Black Star once had a house of happiness that was used specifically to produce Genetic Medicines out of galactic pirates. Is it now improved?"

"If we have this kind of weapon, won't beating the other factions' Esper players be a piece of cake?"

"Come on, have some ambition and imagination. This kind of treasure might be able to allow us to even defeat NPCs, making those strong NPCs powerless and unable to resist whatever's done to them."

"Stop it. I'm already starting to imagine the adult parodies in my head…"

"Come to think of it, the secret weapons the army has been inventing seem to be becoming more and more evil. The aberration one was already bad enough, but now they're even inventing this… Are we the baddies?"

"The Deputy Army Commander is an Esper. Could it be that the Army Commander could not conquer her, so he's planning to invent this kind of equipment and use force?"

"Black Star-Hila shippers are furious!"

"We live and die with Hila!"

…

While the players were pondering and making wild guesses, a secret door of a secret training room deep in the base opened. A man wearing a black hood walked out. He took off the hood, revealing his face. It was indeed Evans.

This training room had a secret path that led directly to the earlier lab. He followed what Han Xiao told him, sneakily went over, and absorbed the Esper Abilities of the two immobilized players. Before that, he had confirmed with Han Xiao again and again that the Immortals would only lose their abilities temporarily.

"So, this is the feeling of superhuman power…"

Evans raised his right arm and clenched his fist. A small stream of energy flowed out from his cells into the muscle and bones of his arm.

Boom!

The next moment, his arm bloated visibly like air was pumped in. His bones became tougher too, and his raw strength increased a large amount.

In his hands, this Esper Ability only had Grade E power. With his pitiful amount of energy, he could not even afford to pump up his entire body. He swung his arm a few times and made sounds of the sound barrier breaking. Just this one arm's strength was close to double his original strength.

Esper Abilities all had potential grades, and usually, this grade signified the highest Grade the Esper could achieve. Although the players were not restricted by this rule, the potential grade still represented the growth speed and rarity of their Esper Abilities. The rarer, the stronger. Some players even continuously opened up new accounts and topped up real money just to get a rare Esper Ability.

Physique enhancement was a large branch in the Esper Abilities. Even Esper Abilities with the same prefix had many variations. Some ordinary physique enhancing abilities might only have Grade D or Grade C potential, but [Physique Enhancement—Bone and Muscle Inflation] had Grade B+ potential, meaning this was a rather high-quality ability among its branch.

This Esper Ability was also a semi-shapeshifting kind. Once activated, even skinny bamboos would instantly turn into muscular men.

The phycological Esper Ability that was absorbed also had grade B potential, which was still quite high.

Among the players, grade A potential was already extremely rare, so although grade B potential was one grade lower, it was plenty good enough.

According to the plan Han Xiao made, giving Evans these two high-quality abilities would not waste his slots. This combination of abilities was beneficial to increasing his basic attributes. As long as his own Grade increased, these two Esper Abilities would keep giving him bonus Strength, Dexterity, Endurance, and Psychological Resistance.

Evans loved these two abilities and could not stop using them till his energy ran out, but his eyes were still glowing.

He had been ordinary for decades. This was the first time he had enjoyed this feeling of fulfillment brought by this power. The shortcut of robbing abilities from others was extremely tempting, as if every single potential desire in his body was pushing him to take that path. Evans felt a sense of hunger coming from every cell in his body, instinctively thirsting for new abilities, like a hungry man's insatiable craving for food.

"Hmm, His Excellency Black Star said that the changes in my body will bring changes to my mindset too. This should be the change my Esper Ability has caused in me…"

Evans thought about it. His strong heart developed through hardship made him suppress this sense of hunger brought by his Esper Ability.

He was not someone who had boundless greed. Black Star had changed his life and given him a righteous path to becoming strong. All he was thinking about was studying and training hard so that he could return this favor in the future. All he wanted was not to disappoint the hope Black Star had for him.

…

The last few months had not been peaceful. First, the federation and the church cooperated to attack the Black Star Army's stronghold but were forced to retreat by Black Star. Then, the Beyond Grade A Association was formed. Therefore, the three Universal Civilizations had been at the center of galactic attention.

Today, the Federation of Light and the Arcane Church had finally made an official response regarding the attack on Hila a few months ago.

The two of them used different words but conveyed the same message, saying that the incident a few months ago was 'an act of impulse led by misunderstandings'. At the same time, they publicly apologized to the Black Star Army, expressing that they would pay for the losses as well as give extra compensation.

Actually, as early as a few months prior when the incident occurred, the black markets at various places had opened a bet on whether the Universal Civilizations would apologize to the Black Star Army. The odds were sky-high, and most galactic residents felt that even though the Universal Civilizations were wrong, they would still be firm about it. They did not think the Black Star Army would receive apologies from the federation and the church, only private compensation at most.

Therefore, after this announcement was made, most galactic residents were astonished.

In the history of the three Universal Civilizations' rule over the known universe, extremely rarely did they lower their heads against other organizations. After all, a public apology would harm their authority. However, the federation and the church shockingly had decided to do it this time, and the Black Star Army became one of the extremely few private organizations in the universe that had this honor.

The dynasty did not want to be excluded from this matter. Right after the church and the federation made their announcements, they officially opened up the Evolutionary Totem business, announcing that the product would no longer be limited and controlled, putting it onto the free market and allowing it to be bought and sold freely.

Countless civilizations had been waiting for this day. The Black Star Army's email inbox exploded. The inventory the army had built up was being depleted continuously while enormous amounts of money flowed into the army's account like a river.

Of course, the smarter people knew that the Crimson Dynasty did this to be closer to Black Star. As the three Universal Civilizations expressed their kind intentions to one person at the same time, Black Star's reputation and position grew once again, even in the Beyond Grade A circle.

Not mentioning anything else, at least Han Xiao's words carried heavier weight as a vice president in the development union.

The players now, of course, would not miss out on this kind of matter. The Flickering World panel in the forums was soon filled with discussion.

Green Dot: "Army Commander is indeed admired by all."

First Name: "Any old players that still remember 1.0? Who could have guessed that Black Star would turn out to be such an important NPC? Look at those protagonist characters in the novice planets. Which one of them turned out as successful as Black Star?"

Hesitant: "Why do I suddenly feel touched? Four versions passed so fast. It's like watching our kid grow up to be a man."

Army Commander's Big PP: "My son Black Star is destined to be the king!"

Important Things Need to Be Said Three Times: "Upstairs, you tired of living?"

The players had already been shocked when Han Xiao defeated twelve Beyond Grade As. Having witnessed such an astonishing event, they were much calmer now.

As the federation and the church carried out their terms, Han Xiao also kept his promise and released Tolaen and Hades.

…

On a sealed dock of Planet Black Gate, the officials of the federation and the church were waiting. They stood clearly apart and did not communicate with each other at all.

These groups of people were there to retrieve their own captives. For that, they had come to the Black Star Army's territory.

After waiting for a while, a Black Star fleet approached from afar and stopped at this dock.

Woosh!

The hatch of the main ship opened. A group of mechanical soldiers carried the amber specimens of Tolaen and Hades down from the spaceship. They then placed these two works of art on the ground. Han Xiao walked out after.

Seeing this, the people of the federation and the church approached quickly, gathered around Han Xiao, and greeted him respectfully.

"Your Excellency Black Star."

"Hmm." Han Xiao looked around casually, waved his hand, and said, "Since you're all here, quickly take your men away."

He signaled everyone to get back. He then blocked their view with nanoparticles. He took his time for a few minutes before breaking Tolaen and Hades out of the amber.

Pa!

Having just regained freedom, the two of them staggered and almost fell.

Seeing this, Han Xiao snorted and coldly said, "The federation and the church have bailed the two of you out. Be careful in the future. If you dare mess with me again and end up in my hands, don't blame me for picking off some parts from you."

Tolaen shivered and uncontrollably took a few steps back. Fear lingered on his face as he looked at Han Xiao with horror-filled eyes. He did not dare talk back at all.

These past few months had been hell. He felt that if it had carried on, he would have been driven mad inside the amber. He never ever wanted to experience it again; he just wanted to get as far away from Black Star as possible.

Hades, who was standing to the side, was fearful too, but he could still control his expression, just about.

Nonetheless, he was extremely sorrowful inside. He had thought that he would at the very least gain some reputation through that operation. Never did he expect to fail so miserably.

Although being defeated by Black Star could not be considered shameful, this tag would probably follow him for a very long time.

He had yet to even make a nickname for himself. Nothing he had done was worth mentioning. What should he say when someone asked him about what he was known for? Was he going to proudly say he had been locked up by Black Star before?

Seeing that the two of them stood in place and did not move, Han Xiao raised his brows and joked, "What, don't feel like leaving? Want to stay a few more months at my place?"

Hearing this, the two of them instantly shivered, quickly returned to their own welcome groups with tails tucked between their legs without saying a word, and boarded their respective spaceships.

The officials quickly took off.

Inside the church's spaceship, Tolaen was looking down.

"Six people from the church went. I'm the only one who was captured. Why am I so unlucky?"

While he was blaming himself, a few communications were picked up by the spaceship. They were from Sagman, Taylor, and Mercer, who had also taken part in the attack on Hila. Their remote projections appeared in front of him.

"Hehe, are you alright?" Sagman said with a smile.

"Not at all." Tolaen was miserable.

"Don't have to be so pessimistic. We were locked up by Black Star once too, and we've all got over it." Taylor smiled and comforted him.

"… You guys are quite generous."

"After you come back, let's find a time and place to meet up," Mercer said.

Tolaen looked at the three smiling faces in front of him, and it suddenly occurred to him.

That's it. We've all been to the prison, so we have common topics. Could this be what inmates feel like?

He had not joined the church long ago. Before that, he was a wanted man, so he could not squeeze into the Beyond Grade A circle of the church. He was like an outsider.

To his absolute surprise, after being locked up by Black Star this time, he obtained acceptance from a group of 'former inmates'.

Tolaen's mood suddenly became better.

I've finally made some friends…

Chapter 1088: Holy Accord's Pain

After releasing the two captives, Han Xiao did not leave Planet Black Gate immediately but instead summoned the person in charge of the planet and inspected the railway construction progress. He shared some experience and gave some guidance on the construction.

On the way back, Han Xiao also inspected the operations of the stargate toll booth.

The stargate commute network in the Black Star Army territory extended from the Garu Star Cluster all the way to the free competition zone, quick and convenient. It was currently one of the exceedingly few complete transport routes in the Flickering World. There were a large number of people using it every day.

Of course, any outsiders who wanted to use this route had to pay a fee. Han Xiao fully utilized the Chinese talent buried deep in his soul of 'build a road if you want to be rich'. He had set up toll booths at every stargate.

With a natural money maker like this, within a year of the Flickering World's opening, the army had already earned back the cost of building the stargates. This outrageous profit margin proved a fact—buying land was much more profitable than operating businesses.

After returning to Black Star Palace, the first part of the bail from the federation and the church came. The federation paid the most. All of the three gold blueprints came from them, and this was the first gold blueprint.

"Mechanical Deity exclusive weapon, Universal Treasure grade mechanical item, Celestial Punishment Edge."

Inside the office, Han Xiao chewed on the lava-flavor condensed nutrition bar while reading through the blueprint data from the Federation of Light.

The blueprints the federation agreed to give him were mostly weapons. This was what Han Xiao selected.

According to the information provided by the Federation of Light, this was an idea from the Saint Tyracles, those admirers of the Mechanical Deity. The federation inherited their knowledge and improved on it, fusing some of their special technology into it, and finally turned this incomplete idea into a blueprint.

On the blueprint was the complete design diagram of this weapon. It had some similarities to the Emperor's Cape. Its appearance was a long mechanical sword with complex interiors, equipped with powerful close-range combat technology. It could also turn into a giant cannon mode and release various long-range attacks. As its name suggested, it was built to destroy celestial bodies.

Like the Emperor's Cape, the Celestial Punishment Edge was also a mega machine, which the Armed Branch excelled in. Although Han Xiao was not, he would still be able to build it with the needed knowledge.

Why did these Saint Tyracles love to design close range combat weapons so much? Did all the true Mechanics have a hidden Pugilist desire inside them waiting to break free?

Complaining was one thing, but he would still undoubtedly have to build it. Han Xiao told Phillip to add the materials for the Celestial Punishment Edge to the next bulk purchase list.

After handling this matter, Han Xiao checked his inbox.

He had received replies from those neutral Beyond Grade A members of the association who were hired by Super Star Cluster Civilizations that he had messaged not too long ago. Most people were worried they might become the target of Dark Lord; only a few were not concerned.

"If there's a demand, there'll be a solution."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He chatted with those Beyond Grade As separately for a while, including 'Leader of Colossuses' Garoze, whom he had once intimidated into retreating.

These people understood what he meant instantly after he gave a subtle hint, and they clearly expressed that they were willing to support Black Star as much as they could in the development union in the future.

Most of these Beyond Grade As did not become allies of the three Universal Civilizations because they did not want to be controlled. However, this would not happen in the development union. They were just normal members of the association, so they had limited control over it. Therefore, they needed an upper echelon with power who could represent their interests and give them better privileges. This was a win-win deal.

Including Garoze, these Beyond Grade As agreed to bring up this matter in the next plenary meeting, and Han Xiao promised to operate around it to eliminate the threat they were facing.

After bringing those people to his side, Han Xiao contacted the dynasty, planning to first notify them.

He expressed his intention, and after waiting for a while, the secretary connected his communication request to Urranrell.

As the scene around him changed, Han Xiao's remote projection appeared in the Dynasty Ruler's office. Before him was Urranrell, who was sitting behind her desk.

"Your Excellency Urranrell." Han Xiao nodded respectfully as a greeting.

"Black Star." Urranrell greeted back, stared into Han Xiao's eyes, and cut to the chase. "You want me to call Clotti back?"

"Yes. The purpose of the development union is to eliminate physical conflict between Beyond Grade As. Clotti is now an Honorable Director, so if he attacks the members, it will go against the association's purpose…"

With an expressionless face, Urranrell said, "On what grounds are you making this suggestion to me today? As an ally of the dynasty or as the vice president of the development union?"

"Both," Han Xiao replied.

"Black Star, in the past few decades, how have you felt about the way the dynasty has been treating you?"

"Win-win." Han Xiao smiled.

Urranrell paused and slowly said, "I must remind you, the Evolutionary Totem business and the territory in the Flickering World, these are all benefits only our allies can enjoy. The dynasty regards you very highly. I'm sure you're aware of that."

Some things could not be said directly. The dynasty did not oppose Black Star becoming the vice president of the development union, but they did not want to see Black Star lean toward it too much. They hoped that between the positions of a dynasty ally and the vice president of the development union, Han Xiao would lean toward the former.

The Mechanic Emperor was an example they could learn from. He had made too many contributions and received too much credit. The federation had no choice but to keep rewarding him and supporting him. This had led to the Mechanic Emperor slowly getting out of control. The dynasty did not want to create another Mechanic Emperor.

As if he did not hear Urranrell's words between the lines, Han Xiao continued what he was saying. "Clotti has captured Traveler and another Beyond Grade A, reigniting others' fear of him. The mission is actually already complete. If he continues to attack others, it might be too much. Furthermore, when I was in the secondary dimensions, I helped him, or things would have turned out differently."

"Hmm… that makes sense too." Urranrell thought about his words.

Seeing this, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled, and he said, "Clotti should have reported the results of Traveler's interrogation, so you must know that Sorokin played a part in this too. Does the dynasty plan to put him on the list of targets?"

"The authenticity of his testimony has yet to be investigated. Sorokin's motive is still unknown. It's not suitable for Clotti to act." Urranrell waved her hand. "If there's enough evidence, the dynasty will deal with him."

Hearing this, Han Xiao secretly gloated.

Sorokin had always been swinging between the three Universal Civilizations, and now Traveler's testimony might cause a huge problem to the position he had maintained for a very long time.

He wondered if the dynasty would use forceful means like when they dealt with Traveler. If that was the case, the true strength Sorokin had been hiding would probably be exposed.

The two of them chatted for a while. Urranrell did not give a direct response, only saying that she would consider the proposal of stopping Dark Lord's mission. Han Xiao knew where to draw the line and bade farewell on good terms.

…

A few days later, in the Beyond Grade A Association's headquarters on Planet Finn, remote projections of close to a hundred Beyond Grade As gathered to attend the routine plenary meeting in the round table conference room.

Currently, the development union was uniting resources, so the focus of the discussion was the partnership plans between the various Beyond Grade As.

The atmosphere was heated. Everyone there was a leader in their own field. They could make big decisions on the spot, so the process was quite smooth. Everyone made their own proposals and collaborated with other members who possessed the resources they wanted. Slowly, everyone's businesses started to connect, forming an enormous profit network. To normal Beyond Grade As, this was an excellent opportunity to partner up with other large Beyond Grade A organizations and achieve mutually-beneficial agreements. With just a recommendation from others, they would receive huge profits.

After the day-to-day affairs were settled, Manison changed the topic.

"In the next meeting, the development union is going to welcome two new members, Tolaen and Hades. Due to some personal reasons, they missed the timing when the association was created. They have now gone through the necessary procedures, and they'll be attending the next meeting."

The people could not help but look at Han Xiao, who was sitting in the vice president seat. Everyone knew about the 'personal reasons', so the atmosphere in the room was quite funny.

After that, Manison looked around and slowly said, "If there's nothing else, that shall be all for this meet…"

This time, Garoze raised his hand and said, "I have a question I'd like to ask Honorable Director Clotti."

Everyone looked over. Clotti, who had been keeping silent, opened his eyes and glanced at him.

"I'd like to confirm one thing. We're all members of the association now, and we're to obey the rules and regulations. Therefore, Your Excellency Clotti, you can't attack any members, right?"

"I only listen to the dynasty's orders," Clotti said with an expressionless face, not caring at all.

The atmosphere immediately became tense. The direct members of the three Universal Civilizations, who were originally resting with their eyes closed, looked interested too.

With courage, Garoze said in a deep voice, "I hope the association will take care of this and ensure our safety. I wouldn't want His Excellency Dark Lord to suddenly have a wild idea one day and blame me and attack me for a crime I've never committed."

As soon as he said that, many neutral Beyond Grade As expressed that they agreed with him. It was clear this was planned.

"Hmm…" Manison narrowed his eyes.

The association's position was rather strange. Although these three Universal Civilizations' direct members had joined the association, it was obvious they would not listen to the association, and this proposal had brought this problem to the table.

While the request of these neutral Beyond Grade As was totally logical, it was not a decision the association currently had the power to make. He had no right to tell Clotti to stop.

However, the very purpose of the development union was to resolve conflicts between Beyond Grade As, so it had to live up to that. Manison could not possibly say that he could not do it, or it would shake the foundation of the association and make people worry about the association's ability to obey its own rules.

"I'll do my best…" Manison planned to first agree and think of a solution later.

However, before he could finish, Han Xiao suddenly interrupted him.

"Leave this problem to me. I'll deal with it."

Garoze and the others understood and all thanked Han Xiao. "Then we shall leave it to you, Your Excellency Black Star. We'll be waiting for the good news."

Clotti gave Han Xiao a meaningful look and did not speak.

Han Xiao smiled at Clotti and did not intend to speak either. Both of them knew that the one who could make this decision was not present.

Han Xiao even pretended to comfort Garoze, finishing the show.

This time, Manison figured out what was happening and gave him a meaningful look too.

Manison did not mind Han Xiao building connections and establishing his reputation. To him, Black Star was on his side. As long as he could do the job, there was no problem.

…

After about a week, Clotti received an order from the Dynasty Ruler to stop the mission. He then led the captives back, leaving the Flickering World.

This message quickly spread to all the members. In their mind, Han Xiao became much more reliable.

By actively taking responsibility for this matter and successfully dealing with it, Black Star proved his ability. Knowing that, the others would naturally come to respect him. This would work just about anywhere.

To Han Xiao, this was just a small matter that did not cost him too much. As his position became higher, his opinion became more and more influential to the dynasty's decision-making on some unimportant matters. The Dynasty Ruler gave him face, too. Making a dynasty ally sitting in the vice president seat more powerful in the association was clearly better than having the federation's Manison have full control over it.

Meanwhile, after more than half a month's time, Aurora had already fully mastered the Holy Light Particle. Without further ado, Han Xiao instantly announced the existence of the Holy Light Seed to the outside world. He emphasized the importance of the new class system granted by the Holy Light Seed. He stated that all army members would be able to acquire Holy Light Seeds after earning merits.

This new source of power made both the players and the Supers interested, but that was all it was, interest. The ordinary people had the strongest response; it was like a storm to them.

Almost everyone hoped to possess powers beyond ordinary men, and this was the best shortcut to it. As long as they awakened Super Genes, they would instantly be promoted into the Supers society and enjoy its privileges.

However, people were born different. Restricted by predetermined talent, most people were destined to be ordinary their entire lives.

Now, however, there was an opportunity to change their fate right in front of their eyes. Furthermore, it was not beyond their reach. As long as they worked for the Black Star Army and made enough contributions, they would have a certain chance of obtaining extraordinary power!

As soon as this announcement was made, countless ordinary people went haywire. The sensation it caused was even more incredible than all the things the army had done in the past added up. After all, the things the army had done were just that, but this announcement was related to the interests of everyone.

The ordinary people had their own way of living. No matter how amazing the Black Star Army was, there were only very few that were willing to work in an armed force. However, it was all different now. The Black Star Army's appeal to ordinary people instantly exceeded ninety-nine percent across all industries.

In just five short days, the number of ordinary people requesting to join the army had already exceeded the current number of members of the Black Star Army!

The number of ordinary people in the universe far exceeded the number of Supers.

…

Within a secret research base of the Holy Accord organization, a researcher placed a cooling container in front of Law and Fay, opened its cap, extended his hand into the white cold fog, and took out a device that looked like a mini radar.

"Your Excellencies, this is the detection device I've invented using the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy's characteristics. It's used to sense the Holy Light Particle."

Law clapped with encouragement. "Good job. This way, we'll be able to find the Holy Light Particle."

"The Holy Light Particle has been hidden for many years," Fay said. "It's probably sleeping in a certain secondary dimension and has no master now. This is our chance. Is the range of this device long enough?"

The researcher replied confidently, "Don't worry, this device can be used together with the cross-dimensional radar. It's definitely long enough."

"Good." Fay nodded with satisfaction.

Law hurried them. "Quickly equip it. We have to acquire the Holy Light Particle as soon as possible."

"Understood, I'll…"

Before he finished, an assistant hastily ran in holding a communicator in his hand and said, "Y-Your Excellencies, look at the news."

Law and Fay looked over and were stunned.

The image the communicator was displaying was the announcement Han Xiao had made.

"Sh*t…" Law murmured.

Not just the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy but even the Holy Light Particle got taken by Black Star‽

What kind of luck is that‽

Last time, they could only successfully attack Black Star because Black Star was not prepared and knew nothing about their weapons.

The two of them initially thought they would never cross paths with Black Star ever again, so they did not worry at all. They never expected Black Star to have another Primal Esper Ability they needed.

The two of them exchanged looks and saw the powerlessness in each other's eyes.

Another Beyond Grade A would have been fine, why did it have to be Black Star?

Black Star was alert now. The risk of carrying out the operation again would be at least ten times higher. They would be dreaming to think that doing the same thing as last time would work.

"So… are we still going for it?"

"Don't drag me down if you want to die," Fay said with a scornful tone.

"What should we do then? The Holy Light Particle is in his hands. We'll have to find a way to take it back."

"How would I know?"

The two of them were at the edge of collapsing.

What should we do‽

The researcher looked left and right before asking,

"Erm… this detection device I've invented, should I still install it?"

"What the hell do you think‽"

Chapter 1089: Black Star Cup

This is unfair! This is unfair!

Inside the exclusive training room in Black Star Palace, Mysterious Energy Host stood by the door and complained furiously to the two people in the room nonstop.

Han Xiao raised his hand and shattered a holy light shockwave from Aurora. He then scratched his ear, feeling like he was almost going deaf.

Ever since Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy found out that Han Xiao had found the Holy Light Particle a master, he instantly went mad.

Initially, he wanted to drag his old friend down so that they could happily be locked inside machines together. He did not want to feel lonely anymore. However, to his shock, although he was the one who led the way to the Holy Light Particle, the Holy Light Particle received much better treatment.

Why do you have a master by I have to be locked inside this metal‽

I want a master too!

Lately, as long as Han Xiao called him out, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy would nag nonstop around him.

"Master! Master! Master!" Han Xiao said with resignation. "Can you stop complaining?"

"No!"

A vein appeared on Han Xiao's forehead. His patience had reached the limit. "Are you forcing me to turn on silent mode for the Mysterious Energy Host? You won't even be able to speak at all then!"

Hearing this, Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy finally shut up.

Being trapped in a tool was bad enough. He could only speak because Black Star was kind enough to let it. If he was not even able to speak, he would have zero means of entertainment.

However, Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was still frustrated. After less than a minute, he uncontrollably spoke again with a soft tone like a wronged wife. "But I really want a master…"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and said, "How old are you? Can you have some pride? Are all Primal Esper Abilities as shameless as you?"

Holy Light Particle who was watching the show from the side heard that and said, "Bullsh*t, most Primal Esper Abilities have class. It's the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy who spoiled our name!"

Furious, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy yelled, "Shut up! You're not much better than me!"

"Alas, it's so comfortable to be inside my master, so much warmer than being in a metal tin," the Holy Light Particle said with a lazy tone.

Staying in Aurora's body and being nurtured by her Vital Energy was as comfortable as enjoying hot springs. No matter how the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy yelled at him, he always used this response to make the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy even more frustrated and irritated.

Listening to the two Esper Abilities fight, Han Xiao could not help but massage his temples.

These two must be the floor of virtue among the Primal Esper Abilities…

"Alright, alright, that's it for today." Han Xiao waved.

Hearing this, Aurora obediently deactivated her ability. Like a duck that got suffocated, the annoying Holy Light Particle suddenly shut up and went silent.

"Erm… uncle, how did I do?"

Aurora looked a little anxious.

She had not been a combatant in the past, so she rarely accepted combat training from Han Xiao at all. The only times she did was as Hila's support, and that was many years ago.

During the combat training, Han Xiao was not as kind and gentle as usual. He was quite strict.

Aurora did not have many opportunities to take part in direct combat, so her combat experience was limited. Therefore, she was worried she might not have done well.

"Not too bad. You need to make smarter choices…" Han Xiao called Aurora close and guided her step by step.

After Aurora learned to control the Holy Light Particle, she had the ability to take on direct battles. Although she would still not really have the chance to fight, Han Xiao still trained her personally to help her master the combat techniques of the Holy Light Particle.

While doing so, Han Xiao also tested the Holy Light Particle's special ability to 'punish evil'. This ability was completely subjective. Whether something was evil or not completely depended on the feelings of its master and the target.

The punishment effect Han Xiao received was very weak. According to the Holy Light Particle, in Aurora's heart, he was a great man, and she had never once felt he was evil. The weak damage mainly came from how Han Xiao felt about himself. He had never felt he was a righteous man.

After a bit more guidance, Han Xiao sent Aurora away, summoned Phillip, and looked at the changes that had occurred in the army after the Holy Light Seed system was announced.

Quite a few days had already passed after the Holy Light Seed announcement. The impact was enormous. Many people had applied to join from every Star Field. Therefore, the army had to, of course, filter the applicants. Also, the cost of recruiting and paying salaries to those people was not a small amount.

The good news was, most ordinary people came for the chance of acquiring extraordinary power, so their goal was clear and straightforward, meaning they were resilient to pressure.

Therefore, without any internal moral conflict, Han Xiao told Sylvia to lower the basic salary of these newcomers to cut costs. This way, the army would be able to recruit more people at a lower cost. Anyway, these people were not here for the money, so it was a great opportunity to let the army acquire a large amount of cheap labor. Furthermore, in order to gain merits, these people would definitely work hard.

What? This is oppression?

No, no, no, this is called fighting to make their dreams come true.

Showing them what they could obtain by working hard was a must-learn for leaders.

Seeing the rocketing business performance across all industries, Han Xiao nodded with satisfaction and asked about another matter.

"How's the Army Tournament plan I told Sylvia to come up with? Let me take a look."

The virtual screen before him turned into a plan drafted by Sylvia.

Han Xiao looked through it in detail. Sylvia basically followed the structure he gave. Sparring was just one of the many programs. There were also all kinds of technical, sports, and entertainment competitions. Of them, the sports and entertainment competitions were the highest in number.

Furthermore, the army members could also request certain competitions. As long as they were not nonsense, there was a chance these requests would be approved. Han Xiao had no doubts the players would request soccer and play some 'Shaolin Soccer'.

Based on the strength of army members, each Grade was classified into a group, ensuring that the participants would only meet competitors of the same Grade. At the same time, he also gave the players the freedom to choose either to join their own groups or the NPC groups.

Of course, encouragement measures could not be left out. No matter what group or program, as long as the participant's placement was high, the army would give out a grand reward. This would ensure that most army warriors would be interested in taking part.

In order to let members who did not take part or were eliminated early still participate in some way, Sylvia suggested opening up bets for all the programs and competitions.

This way, it would receive attention from the entire army. As an armed force, there were tons of gambling addicts. Even those who did not gamble normally would also be influenced by the atmosphere to place some bets.

At the same time, this would also earn back the cost of hosting the event. Sylvia even planned to sell tickets, broadcast it across the entire universe, and charge for it. She had a way of making money.

Han Xiao thought this was a good idea. He could use this opportunity to start a competition league, like the sports competitions in his previous life, building a platform where Supers could display their prowess. This might be quite popular.

In the future, perhaps other Beyond Grade A organizations could take part. Since the development union prevented physical conflicts, this might be one way for the Beyond Grade As to display their strength, by letting their subordinates earn some honor for their organizations.

"According to this plan, this is going to be a festival the entire army will take part in, which will affect business operations. However, the sense of unity brought by this kind of large faction event is quite impressive. Not only the players but the normal army members also need ways to relax outside of work," Han Xiao murmured.

To the players, the focus of the Flickering World version was to ride the tide of the era and fight each other, carrying out the first round of national wars on this grand stage. The clubs' final goal was to be placed high in the International League.

Hence, if he, an NPC, hosted an even larger competition in the early- to mid-stage of the version, it would definitely be loved by the players as a warmup for the Pro League. This way, the appeal of his faction would evolve from a powerful organization with a lot of benefits to the host of a competition in the players' eyes.

In order to take part in the Army Tournament, one naturally had to be in the army. No players from other factions would be able to take part in it. Therefore, once the players recognized the importance of the Army Tournament, the army would become a faction many players had to join like when it was the guiding faction in Version 2.0.

"This kind of large-scale faction event is not suitable to be hosted too often. Once every five to ten years should be best. Also, it needs a better name. 'Army Tournament' lacks personality."

Thinking of his pitiful talent for naming things, Han Xiao was not confident and called Phillip out.

"Give me a name."

Phillip tilted his head and said, "How about… Army Gala, hum?"

Han Xiao's face trembled. Why not just call it the Spring Festival Gala?

"Too boring, give me a cool and flashy one."

"Then… Galaxy Super Clash! Top of the Universe, Black Star Army Peak Tournament! Hum!"

What the hell? What stupid information did those players share with Phillip?

"Let's not make it too flashy…"

Phillip gave another few names. In the end, Han Xiao officially decided to call it the Black Star Cup Army Tournament, or Black Star Cup in short. Simple and easily understood, it even included his name.

Han Xiao then made some adjustments to the plan and sent it to Sylvia. He decided to make an announcement about the first Black Star Cup another day. A lot of time was required to prepare for such a large event, so he decided to announce it first to preheat it like the players' Pro League.

The scale of the Black Star Cup was so much bigger than the Pro League. The Pro League only included the players, while the entire army could take part in this. Although there were more than eight million army players, this was still a small number compared to the total members of the army.

However, most players had reached Grade B. Their importance was completely different compared to before. They could already be considered a very important force in the army.

In the universe, Grade Bs were considered the backbones of their forces. They were powerful in any non-Beyond Grade A organization. Even many Beyond Grade A organizations did not have as many Grade Bs as there were army players.

In the past few months, he had attracted a lot of attention, so he needed time to digest the influence it had brought. This was a good opportunity to direct all the attention to the army, so it was the best time to host the Black Star Cup.

Furthermore, Han Xiao had another more important goal.

The period of time when the players had the strongest desire to spend was before the Pro Leagues of every version. The players would only spend without hesitation to turn their money into strength before a large event.

Currently, the Flickering World was going from the early stage to the middle stage. Although no player had reached the maximum level yet, after accumulating for close to a year, many players had quite thick wallets.

"Some leeks… are ripe."

Han Xiao sighed.

His scythe was ready.

Chapter 1090: Announcement

In Emerald Star Cluster, on a certain planet was a desolate desert filled with strangely shaped rocks. Hundreds of shuttle-shaped, low-altitude battle carriers were fighting intensely, crisscrossing between mountains and cliffs, using them as cover.

Light beams crossed each other, landing on the cliffs around, causing landslides and rocks rolling down the slopes.

There were four different symbols on these low altitude carriers. One was the guild symbol of the Rivervale guild, and the other three were all symbols of different foreign clubs.

Rivervale was not in a good position right now. They were being attacked by three foreign clubs together. They had no choice but to flee while fighting back, or they would be surrounded.

Maple Moon was piloting one carrier. Her hands grabbed onto the sphere-shaped control devices on two sides specially made for Mechanics. Sparkling Mechanical Force connected the device to the spaceship, making the spaceship her extended body and allowing her to control it with ease. The spaceship swiftly made a turn, avoiding a round of fire while shooting a Main Cannon, which blew up one of the enemy spaceships.

However, a few visible black silhouettes flew out from the flames of the carrier's explosion. They were the players on the ship. Among them, a Mechanic player threw out compressed orbs that turned into a new carrier, and they continued the chase.

Seeing this, Maple Moon spoke in the team channel with resignation. "Sword, there are too many enemies. Our inventory will run out sooner or later if we continue like this. Should we just die? We can leave these resources."

"Hold on for just a while longer. Our allies are rushing here."

Frenzied Sword focused on dealing with the enemies. He was quite frustrated.

This planet was originally controlled by a small mining organization. Rivervale, Long Sky, and other guilds partnered with it by providing armed defense in exchange for part of the mining profit. This was a common scheme for the player guilds in the free competition zone.

However, a few middle-level officers of this mining organization were bought by a few Southeast Asian clubs. They helped them hide on this planet. When Frenzied Sword brought his men and came to collect this batch of resources as usual, the three clubs who had set up an ambush jumped out and surprised Frenzied Sword and the others.

The mode of conflict between players had been becoming more and more complicated as they learned to make use of smaller organizations more effectively. They acquired skills such as bribing and threatening the NPCs. This incident was just a small one; the bigger guilds were already involved in infiltrating, backstabbing, and many other things.

The carriers of Rivervale were being destroyed one after another; the players had no choice but to land on the ground. Maple Moon led the Mechanics to build a fortress to attack the enemies in the sky. The enemies then also sent a group of players down. The two sides started slaughtering each other on the desolate land. As Rivervale was at a numerical disadvantage, their situation was quite worrying.

After fighting for a while, a few battleships suddenly appeared deep in the starry sky and quickly approached. They were the Long Sky and the other allied guilds. Seeing this, these three foreign clubs instantly took off and returned to the spaceships that were on standby in the outer atmosphere. Before reinforcements arrived, they escaped with hyperdrive in a very well-practiced manner. It was clear they were prepared.

"Are you guys okay?"

Hao Tian and the other Long Sky members landed beside Frenzied Sword's side. They looked around at the mess around.

"Alas, they got me. We've lost quite a lot this time. Some died multiple times and lost EXP too," Frenzied Sword said with resignation. There was a limit to the number of times the players could die each day, and the punishment increased gradually after every death. The players were not afraid of death, but they had to die for a reason. Clearly, dying like this without getting anything in return was a huge loss.

"These foreign clubs have their eyes on us Chinese clubs now. They've been working together to attack us," Maple Moon complained.

"Well, it is what it is. We're making the most profit, after all, and our faction is the strongest." Sleepy Winter shrugged.

Currently, thanks to the Black Star Army, the Chinese clubs were having the best time in the free competition zone. Naturally, along with the benefits they received, they were also targeted by the foreign clubs. These clubs' plan to stir up hatred between nations failed, so they could no longer use the players in the Black Star Army. Hence, they had no choice but to do it themselves. They had been harassing the Chinese clubs frequently over the past few months, attempting to slow down their growth.

Frenzied Sword was a little worried. "It wouldn't matter if it was just during normal times, but if we get harassed even during the Pro League, it's going to be very tough for us to achieve something this season."

"If we get a champion this season too, China will have acquired the champion three times in a row. The clubs from the other countries definitely won't want to see that," Rainy Kim said calmly.

Participating in the competitions was a way to acquire fame. Fame meant traffic, and traffic meant profit. The ultimate goal of all clubs was to make profit.

The International League was the only large-scale open competition for the pro teams to increase their fame. There were no other platforms that had as large an audience.

Therefore, if the Chinese had it all, it meant that they had obstructed the others' way of making money. No clubs from the other countries were content with just participating, so some of them were causing problems for their opponents by any means necessary. They were all competitors, and when one side became too strong, the others would definitely come together to be against it. It was unavoidable.

Beep beep beep!

At this time, the communicators of everyone present suddenly rang simultaneously.

They exchanged looks of surprise and looked at their communicator. When they saw what it was, they were all slightly stunned.

"Black Star Cup?"

On the communicators was a new army announcement.

Army Announcement—The Black Star Cup Army Tournament

To the entire army, the Black Star Army has been walking the path of high-speed growth. As our business expands, so does the number of members. In order to let the members of the various departments get to know each other more, increase our unity, and select talented people from the various trades, the army has decided to host an event with the nature of a military parade. The preparation for the first season of Black Star Cup Army Tournament starts today. For details, refer to the Competition Rules and Regulations (Expand/Collapse).

All members of the army are able to take part. If you can achieve excellent results, the army will not be petty about the rewards. You're welcome to participate.

Army Commander, Black Star.

The people did not feel much by just looking at the content of the announcement. However, when they expanded the competition's rules and read the contents, their eyes became brighter and brighter as they were shocked by the scale of the Black Star Cup.

"My god, the scale of this faction event is way too big!" Maple Moon covered her mouth in shock.

"We can even request certain activities‽" Twinkle Fried Rice's eyes widened.

The players present were overjoyed just by reading the introduction. They could not wait for it.

Compared to the scale of the Black Star Cup, the International League was tiny.

Frenzied Sword and Hao Tian exchanged looks. Both of them thought of the meaning of this event beyond the surface.

"This is an amazing opportunity to increase our fame!" Frenzied Sword's tone was excited. "Events like this definitely don't lack spectators, and there are close to ten million army players as the default audience."

"That's right. Although this is an event hosted by an NPC, as long as it's popular, it'll also bring traffic. It might be an even better replacement for the International League!" Hao Tian expressed his agreement.

Hearing this, the look in everyone's eyes changed. The way they looked at this announcement was as if they were looking at a mountain of gold.

Everyone had noticed that this was probably the new platform for professional players to shine. Furthermore, it had way more activities than the International League, which would bring an extremely high amount of exposure.

Although the clubs in the other factions could not participate, which meant that the Chinese clubs had no competitors and it was not as competitive as the International League, was this not an exclusive exposure opportunity to the army players?

Also, it was now the early to middle stage of the version, so the Pro League was still far away. This was the exact time the players needed an entertainment show, and the Black Star Cup filled this void!

If it was popular enough, they were even willing to bring out as much passion as during the International League to prepare for the Black Star Cup, turning their accumulated EXP and wealth into strength.

Why do we make money? To spend it when needed of course!

Such an amazing opportunity has landed on us Chinese players again…

Thinking of this, they could feel the blood flowing in their body turn warm. They were touched.

Black Star might be a member of the Communist Party!

…

"Black Star Cup‽"

Seeing the army's public announcement, the many foreign clubs were filled with jealousy.

Every club knew that this was an excellent opportunity to gain exposure. This was exactly the stage they needed.

However, only the Black Star Army members could participate in the Black Star Cup. These clubs belonging to other factions could do nothing but watch this opportunity slip by.

The foreign clubs could still put up with the mission benefits the Black Star Army was already getting, but now such an amazing exposure opportunity had appeared, the determination of many clubs not to change factions was shaken.

Why can the Black Star Army hit our soft spots so easily‽

Should we just… give in?

…

"What is Black Star doing?'

On the other hand, some Beyond Grade As were confused about this.

To some of them, not only did events like this damage profit and affect efficiency, it would also eat into a lot of time that could be used for work.

However, after some thinking, quite a number of Beyond Grade As felt they understood Black Star's intentions.

With the development union, the chances for us to take part in battles in the future will probably decrease, which is not beneficial to maintaining our individual image. Black Star might be searching for a new way for us to display our strength to the outside world.

Quite a number of Beyond Grade As were touched.

The Vice President is thinking so far into the future. Now this is what it means to help us obtain more benefits!

Chapter 1091: Making It Clear

The day after the Black Star Cup's announcement, countless representatives of the media and financial groups came with money in their pockets, wanting to buy the rights to broadcast the event.

Inside the large conference room of the army's headquarters, Sylvia sat in the top seat. Countless remote projections of representatives sat below and chatted nonstop. The room was noisy.

"Silence."

Sylvia knocked on the table, and the entire place did indeed become silent. Everyone turned to look at her.

As the Chief Administrative Official of the army, Sylvia was also in charge of communicating with the outside. In the eyes of many organizations, she was no doubt someone who held a high position and a lot of power. Even though all the people sitting there were upper echelons of their own media and financial groups, they were still very obedient in front of Sylvia.

Sylvia looked around and said with a serious tone, "You're all here for the same purpose. About the Black Star Cup Army Tournament, the Army Commander intends to develop it into an integrated sports event for Supers. The first season will temporarily be limited only to the army itself, but in the future, people from other forces might participate too. The details are in the introduction of the rules and regulations of the competition, which I believe you have all already read.

"The army hopes to broadcast the event to the entire universe, so the broadcasting rights will be sold by areas. Planet-level broadcasting rights will not be sold alone. The lowest will be at the Star Zone level, which costs 15 million Enas. The broadcasting rights for a Star System costs 120 million Enas, and the Star Cluster broadcasting rights costs 980 million Enas. It can be paid in one go or up to five terms. This is only the initial price for reference. If any of you want to be the only one broadcasting it in the area, the sale will be done in the form of bidding."

Hearing this, a commotion began under the stage. Many people exchanged looks and saw the surprise in each other's eyes.

Given the Black Star Army's position and the popularity of this competition, this price was more than just generous. It was much lower than they expected.

Usually, there would only be two ways to sell the broadcasting rights of this kind of event. The most common one would be selling it to the media, not restricting the areas where the said media would play it in. Another would be to sell it by areas, which was usually used for large-scale broadcasting. Very few could do the latter, or the media would not allow it. Of course, the Black Star Army had the right to.

The basic unit was Star Zone, which meant that if bought, it would only be allowed to be broadcast in one Star Zone. Although the current quantum network was extremely developed and connected the entire galactic society, most viewers still had area-based preferences. It was basically like the local channel.

Indeed, the price of 15 million Enas was not low, but any media or financial group that dared to come to make deals with the army had no shortage of that much money.

If the broadcasting areas overlapped, the event would then be broadcast together unless an auction was held for the exclusive rights. If different levels of broadcasting areas were to overlap—for example, if one media bought the Star System broadcasting rights while the other brought the Star Zone broadcasting rights that included this Star System—the issue would either be left undealt with or they could request to negotiate with the army. The army would then either refund the broadcasting rights or have the two media groups work together. However, any media purchasing a large area broadcasting right, selling it themselves was absolutely forbidden.

Sylvia called out Phillip's doppelgangers, which appeared beside every representative, to record the prices they were willing to pay.

The media representatives contemplated for a while and wrote down their requests and prices.

They could all see the business potential of the Black Star Cup. Lately, the Black Star Army had done a lot of shocking things and attracted a lot of attention, especially Black Star's Godlike Battle and the Holy Light Particle incidents. The army had welcomed a lot of traffic. In fact, in every ten galactic residents, at least four would pay attention to news about the army.

Furthermore, the Black Star Cup itself was also very appealing. Although there were many Supers in the universe and battles between them were anything but rare, a competition where countless Supers of different Grades all participated together was extremely rare. Plus, there were even things like selections and drafting events, which would make things much more interesting for the audience.

Also, the competition had way too many items. Where else could anyone see such an interesting sports entertainment event with so many Supers attending?

According to the blueprint of the Black Star Cup, there was a chance this would turn into a league festival in the future that more organizations would take part in. With the Black Star Army's position, anyone copying the idea was nothing to be worried about. From a long-term perspective, this competition had a lot of growth potential. The representatives present not only wanted to sign this competition, but some even wanted to immediately sign the next few seasons too as a long-term investment.

"That's a win-win for us." Sylvia continued speaking while they were considering the prices to pay. "The army wants to make the Black Star Cup big, so we need more media groups to broadcast it and increase the event's popularity, while you guys need people to watch your channel. I'm sure I don't have to emphasize the scale of the Black Star Cup. It's a festival that…"

At this time, a financial group representative raised his hand and said, "I heard that the army is opening up bets internally. Do you accept exterior bets?"

"You guys can set up bets yourselves, but the army's pot doesn't accept bets from the outside." Sylvia waved her hand.

"And why is that? If you guys open up the bet, the commission you can earn from it will be countless times greater." Someone questioned.

"This is the highest order from the Army Commander."

Sylvia did not explain it to them. Actually, when she came to know that Han Xiao had made this decision, she was confused too. This was an opportunity to make a lot of money, and from what she knew about Han Xiao, he would not let this opportunity slip past. However, to her surprise, it was like her teacher's personality changed on this matter.

Afterward, Han Xiao explained it to her. He said that although the army was quite wealthy, the bets from the outside world were still way too large. There were risks to opening the betting to the outside world, and some fool—Sorokin—might cause problems in the dark. Comparatively, if the bets were only open to the internal members, it was basically equivalent to cycling the funds within the army. No matter who won or lost, the money was still in the hands of the army's members.

On the other hand, the people participating in the competition were their own army members, and if the army opened the bets to the outside world, the army members might have some disgruntled guesses about why it was the case. This was not beneficial to building their mindsets. If the bets were only limited to within the army, the image it gave would be much better. It would feel like a family betting with each other within the family.

Simply put…

We ain't gonna earn this dirty money!

After retrieving all the price quotes, Iapetus brought his business team along and came in for negotiations, while Sylvia left the conference room and headed for the next meeting.

Other than the selling of broadcasting rights, the army also planned to find a lot of sponsors for the Black Star Cup. The partners of the army would provide some form of sponsorship, be it for the sake of profit or face, and all of that added together was quite a large amount of money.

Sorokin had approached Han Xiao for this purpose, too.

"You want to sponsor the Black Star Cup?"

Han Xiao sized up Sorokin's remote projection.

"That's right. You're a shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group. Of course, I have to show my support for your projects." Sorokin had his signature fake smile on his face.

"How much do you plan to sponsor?"

Sorokin gave a number, smiled, and said, "This number represents my sincerity."

Han Xiao's heart skipped a beat. This amount was quite outrageous.

Your sincerity is overflowing…

"Are you sure?"

"Yes, the Black Star Cup has a lot of potential. I have very high hopes in this investment." Sorokin smiled and slowly said, "Plus, we're partners now. Due to some reasons in the past, some cracks were made in our relationship, so I'm hoping to fix our relationship…"

Han Xiao understood.

Right, so you're here to give me 'protection fees', hoping to compensate for the loss you've caused me before.

He had essentially threatened Sorokin to obtain the position of shareholder, which could not be changed. Sorokin had already accepted that, so he mainly wanted to fix their relationship. He had to say, this guy really knew when to compromise and take a step back.

Han Xiao suddenly thought of something.

This guy probably was not only there to make up for what he had done but also for Traveler.

Dark Lord had caught Traveler, and the dynasty had already announced that he would be openly executed. Han Xiao had gone to the secondary dimensions some time ago, so Sorokin might think that he had found something out. Thus, he had come to test Han Xiao.

After all, Sorokin meddled in the attack on Hila, and Traveler was one of the very few people who knew about it, so it was natural that he was worried.

"Alright then. About before, I shall hold you less responsible." Han Xiao smiled, dragged his words, and said, "About Heber…"

Sorokin's eyelid trembled. "This…"

Before he answered, Han Xiao laughed and said, "Don't worry, I'm kidding. How can I let you void your agreement with him, use the methods you used on me on him, and take away all the developments you've helped him make? He and I are so very close."

As if I'd believe you…

Sorokin adjusted his emotions and tested Han Xiao by saying, "I heard you went to the secondary dimensions recently. How was it?"

"Not bad. I went to quite a few places…"

Han Xiao chattered about everything but what he knew Sorokin really wanted to know about.

After patiently listening for a while, Sorokin realized that Han Xiao was deliberately avoiding the topic, so he had no choice but to cough and say, "I heard that Dark Lord caught Traveler in the secondary dimensions. Did you meet him?'

"Yes." Han Xiao nodded.

Sorokin was glad. Just as he was about to listen to what Han Xiao was going to say next, he suddenly realized that Han Xiao had stopped and did not seem like he was going to continue at all.

"…"

The two of them looked at each other in silence for close to half a minute.

Finally, Sorokin could not take it anymore and asked with resignation, "What happened?"

"Back then, Dark Da… ahem, Traveler almost escaped from Dark Lord, but he ran into me, so I captured him." Han Xiao tutted. "Speaking of which, that guy hardly had a backbone. I only tortured him a little bit, and he gave up the identity of who was behind all this."

Sorokin's heart tightened. "Who?"

Han Xiao glanced at him and slowly said, "He said he isn't really a neutral mercenary but a secret direct member of a Super Star Cluster civilization. He was ordered by his superiors to disrupt me when Hila was attacked."

"Direct member?" Sorokin was curious. "Of whom?"

Han Xiao said with a grave ton, "None of us expected him to actually be a member of the Modo Civilization."

"Modo…"

Sorokin pondered.

Suddenly, realizing something, he became alarmed.

Wait a minute. There's no way Traveler would have covered the truth for me. He'd definitely expose the fact that I was the reason the Star Cluster sent him on this mission.

This meant that the dynasty knew he was involved.

"Then you…" Sorokin stared at Han Xiao but did not know what to say.

"What do you want to say?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"What else did Traveler say?"

"Are you asking whether Traveler ratted you out?" Han Xiao said with a smile.

Sorokin's expression tightened. Since Black Star had said that, he was sure he was exposed.

This time, Han Xiao stopped smiling and coldly said, "What you've done behind my back isn't very nice."

He had planned to hide this, but when Sorokin came to find him, he understood that his initial plan of staying in the dark was not so realistic.

The dynasty was going to publicly execute Traveler, so Sorokin definitely had no room to daydream. He knew that there was a very high chance Traveler would throw the blame to him, nor did Traveler have any reason to cover up for him. Therefore, the dynasty most likely would know about what he did, and Black Star certainly was notified about him plotting against the Black Star Army.

This way, even if Han Xiao acted like he did not know it, Sorokin would only be more alarmed. Therefore, he might as well make it clear. According to what he knew about Sorokin, this guy definitely would not want to make things ugly but would instead try to compensate for it.

After all, even if Sorokin gave him compensation, it did not mean that he would stop targeting him.

Sorokin paused, sighed, and said, "Alright, got it. The motive behind what I did was just to maintain balance; it's not personal. Nonetheless, I owe you for this incident. Since we're now partners, I'll give you an appropriate answer."

Han Xiao carefully observed his expression and narrowed his eyes.

As he expected, given how thick-skinned Sorokin was, him panicking after being exposed was not likely. He would have instead confessed and apologized on the spot, then looked for compensation measures.

Furthermore, Sorokin was very cheeky and actually prepared for this—he deliberately told Traveler about 'how he really felt' and gave his actions the excuse of maintaining unity and disrupting the Beyond Grade A shared battlefront. This way, it would not seem personal.

With this mindset as the reason, even if he was exposed, he would not be targeted too much. This was because the stand he had displayed on this matter was actually the same as the three Universal Civilizations' stand.

The only difference was the methods he used. Even so, he had hardly offended the dynasty. After all, his method was just indirect disruption, not direct interference.

In the current complex universe structure, the three Universal Civilizations had conflicts of interest with the development union. As a member of the association that also had the same mindset as the three Universal Civilizations, Sorokin might become one of the people they might want to draw to their side.

Although having his stance exposed would lead to those Beyond Grade As who supported the shared battlefront such as Mechanic Emperor and Black Star distancing themselves from him, this also became an opportunity for him to get closer to the three Universal Civilizations. This way, his losses would be minimized.

Han Xiao could only praise Sorokin's intelligence. Relying on his resources, this guy could always deal with the negative side effects very well.

The biggest problem was that he had worked with the Super Star Cluster Alliance on this, so the three Universal Civilizations would definitely not be happy about it. Sorokin had no way of washing that off, so he had to pay a price.

The second problem was Han Xiao's attitude on this. Black Star was insulted, and no one could shake his position in the association now. Sorokin had no choice but to prepare for Han Xiao to make an outrageous demand.

Many thoughts flashed through Han Xiao's mind. He blinked and said coldly, "Let me hear how you're planning to express your apology to me."

Chapter 1092: Opening

"I'll give the Black Star Army more support. For all the services and resources you purchase from the Limitless Financial Group in the future, you will only be charged the cost. At the same time, I'll bring in a lot of discounted business projects and partner up with the Germinal Financial Group under you, helping it grow. Also, I'm willing to invest and build factories in the Black Star Army's territory without any cost or profit in mind. Through investing and helping your business to grow in various industries on your territory…"

Sorokin mentioned a lot of things. In conclusion, other than monetary compensation, he was also going to use the Limitless Financial Group's businesses and funds to help the Black Star Army grow and develop.

Han Xiao made some calculations in his head. If these terms were all to be carried out, despite how wealthy the Limitless Financial Group was, it would not be a small expenditure at all. To the army's territories, the construction would be sped up tremendously.

This guy really seemed serious about fixing the relationship.

In the past, Sorokin used a similar method to help the Bloodshed Land grow. Now, the Bloodshed Land had mostly completed their business transformation and become a strong competitor of the army in the Shattered Star Ring. Sorokin was now offering the same treatment to the Black Star Army, with even better terms.

As for the support he had been providing to Heber, even though Black Star did not mention it, Sorokin was going to stop it for the time being.

"Hmm…" Han Xiao neither agreed nor disagreed. He then brought up a new term. "Although the construction in the Flickering World territories is important, the army has a larger goal. I'm planning to develop the army in the other Star Fields too. Your Limitless Financial Group has influence and businesses in various Star Fields too. I suppose you can share some of that too."

"…Okay." Sorokin was smiling on the surface but actually clenching his teeth in his mind.

He knew that this request meant that Black Star was not satisfied with just resources but had his eyes on the Limitless Financial Group's channels and connections across the Star Fields. Black Star wanted to suck the Limitless Financial Group's blood and take its businesses to nurture the army's businesses in the other Star Fields. It was quite an outrageous demand.

Although Sorokin was mentally prepared for it, he was still quite hurt.

One reason he was willing to give so much compensation was to fix his relationship with Black Star. It was worth investing in him despite the fact that the chance of Black Star no longer targeting him was only fifty percent. Another reason was to display his stance to the dynasty.

Although the Black Star Army might become a parasite to the Limitless Financial Group, leeching on its meat to grow, the most urgent matter now was to deal with the dynasty. Suffering from losses was inevitable, or Sorokin would not have compromised like this. The Black Star Army was strong indeed, but he was not afraid of Han Xiao in the field of business. It was the dynasty behind Han Xiao that concerned him.

After getting by this incident, the profit he lost could be slowly earned back in the future, and the agreements made now could be ignored in various ways too. Therefore, Sorokin decided to agree with it for the time being.

"Also, I like Universal Treasures. Be it complete products or blueprints, I like to collect them all. The Limitless Financial Group should have some ways to get them—share them with me," Han Xiao said.

"I'll do my best to collect them after I get back." Sorokin agreed without hesitation. He was already agreeing to pay a lot of debts; agreeing to more did not really make a difference.

"That's it then. Carry out these terms as soon as possible." Han Xiao waved his hand. "I have some things to attend to later, so let's end our chat here today."

"Okay, I won't disturb you any longer."

Sorokin stood up, nodded slightly, and hung up the communication. His remote projection disappeared.

Han Xiao leaned back and pondered.

"Traveler is dead loyal to the Star Arc Civilization, and only I know about it for now. I wonder if the dynasty can get that from him in the interrogation. No matter what, as of now, Traveler is firm about Sorokin being the one behind it on the dynasty's side. The dynasty will definitely send someone to question Sorokin's motive.

"At that time, Sorokin will surely blame it on the Super Star Cluster Alliance. I told him Modo is the true mastermind, so he will most likely say the same to the dynasty. If the dynasty continues to ask, he'll probably say I told him. The dynasty knows that I have beef with Modo, so they'll know my motive. Although they clearly know this is a lie and framing, they might be happy to go along with it. In the future, they might use this as an excuse to cause trouble for the Modo Civilization and other Super Star Cluster civilizations.

"As for Sorokin, he might not believe what I said, but even if he doesn't believe Traveler belongs to the Modo Civilization, he'll definitely investigate it…"

Han Xiao shook his head and smiled.

This way, the one who suffered the most damage from this entire incident would be the Modo Civilization. It basically all fell onto their head out of nowhere.

In the three Universal Civilizations' future operations to deal with the Super Star Cluster Alliance, the Modo Civilization would probably receive the most 'love'.

"This way, the second requirement of that Grade S mission [Kunde Race Leader's Last Wish] should be about complete…"

Han Xiao's eyes slightly sparkled, and he rubbed his hands.

He had been tempted by the reward of this mission for a very long time. [Proof of Leadership], [The Enemy], and [Kunde Rage], a total of three excellent abilities. Currently, the Modo Civilization was protected by the Super Star Cluster Alliance and was keeping a low profile, so he could not target them directly. The only thing he could do was wait for the certain conflict in the future.

…

News about the Black Star Cup quickly spread. The entire army showed an extremely high passion for it; countless members registered.

Most people joined for entertainment purposes, but a few ambitious army warriors saw this as an opportunity to display their strength.

The Black Star Cup had also received a lot of attention among the army players. The forums were filled with posts about it once again.

Heaven Is Below Me: "What's going on? Wasn't Black Star just going to enter the show business not long ago, and now the army is going to enter the sports industry?"

Itchy Head: "That's how large factions are."

Never Starve Even Dead: "This feels more interesting than the Pro League."

Tiny And Weak: "The scale of this tournament is the biggest I've ever seen. It has a lot of events and a lot of participants. All participants are allowed to even join as many as five events. How many competitions are there going to be? There are card games and even bets too‽"

Two White Rabbits: "Not just card games, there are even singing and dancing contests. I even saw people request stand-up comedy competitions, and it was even approved!"

Dragon Emperor Licker: "Honestly, I want to see Black Star dance…"

Sky High Professional Account Boosting Studio: "The rewards for these competitions are quite rich, and the items with the greatest rewards are still related to combat. The top 300,000 will all be rewarded, and our weapons are not even limited. This means that if we participate in group battles, use our explosion backpacks and evolution badges, and utilize similar dirty tactics, will we take all of the top positions?"

Feidin Supporters Group President: "Let me take a look. Whose wallets are getting thick again? (Black Star's Smile.jpg)"

Cow Lover: "Army Commander, this is my protection fee for this year."

While the Black Star Cup was still in preparation, countless players were already getting their wallets ready.

For the days that followed, the sales of the logistics department skyrocketed. The EXP Han Xiao received every day increased by a huge portion too. Tons of players spent more than half of the resources they had been accumulating since the start of the Flickering World version on studying and leveling up abilities.

Seeing the EXP growth every day, Han Xiao felt very good.

If I don't take the players' hard-earn money, am I still human?

At this rate, level 340 was not going to be far away. However, to obtain one more God's Trait Transformation Point during Promotion, he decided to use the EXP he earned to level up some blueprint abilities and all his class knowledges to the max level.

Sylvia and Phillip were very efficient. With the Black Star Army's current position, all the administrative procedures were approved smoothly without any hiccups.

Han Xiao selected many desolate planets as the event venues. The professional galactic construction teams called over by the Limitless Financial Group quickly built up the facilities needed, while the army members participating in the Black Star Cup arrived one after another.

The schedule was similar to the Pro League. Due to the extremely large number of participants, a group of people would first be eliminated in the qualifiers, then it would move on to the actual event.

After preheating it for more than two months, the preparations for the first season Black Star Cup were finally complete.

On October 28th, Year 730 of the Galaxy Calendar, the Black Star Cup opening ceremony was held as scheduled. With help from the media groups, the eyes of the entire universe were focused on this giant festival.

Chapter 1093: Tide from Afar

Countless spaceships surrounded a sapphire planet. Colorful lights penetrated the artificial atmosphere and made the sky of this planet as beautiful as the northern lights.

This was one of the desolate planets in the army's territory, it was rebuilt into one of the venues for the Black Star Cup. Countless facilities such as stages, rings, large stadiums, and low altitude racing tracks were built on the surface, visible to the naked eye even from outside the atmosphere. Other than the buildings on the surface, there were also floating stages in the air. Some were VIP seats exclusive to the army members above Grade C, and others were more rings. As there were many items and participants, as many competition venues were needed as possible to increase the efficiency of the qualifiers.

At this time, the sights of all the media groups and army spaceships were locked onto the biggest floating stage. On it was a lectern.

Today was the opening ceremony. As the leader of the army, the founder of the Black Star Cup, Han Xiao was going to speak to the entire universe here.

Countless galactic residents of the explored universe watched their communicators as time passed by. Finally, the time for the official start of the opening ceremony had arrived.

Hu!

Watched by countless people, a black silhouette descended like a meteor from space, gradually decelerating and accurately landing on the edge of the stage. With a light spin, the dancing black and gold coat spun like a black tornado, getting rid of the flames from when he penetrated the atmosphere.

Han Xiao slowly walked to the speaking desk and looked up at the sky. The spotlights from countless spaceships above were like distant stars. Countless eyes were watching him through the live broadcast.

With his hands placed on the sides of the lectern, Han Xiao looked around at the starlight in the sky and slowly spoke. Through the specially made speaker, his voice echoed across the planet.

"October 2nd, Year 688 of the Galaxy Calendar, that was the day the army's former identity—the Black Star Mercenary Group—was founded. Back then, I was only a surface civilization native who had just stepped off Planet Aquamarine. To save my mother planet, like a newborn animal, I headed into the wide universe, ignorant and weak. To me, this was a world filled with unknown danger. However, for the survival of my mother planet, and the safety of my friends who stayed there, without any hesitation, I…"

The speech was played out live in the various Star Fields. To the Planet Aquamarine people who were watching the broadcast, this old memory started floating to the surface. A sense of pride appeared in their heart.

No matter what Black Star's position was in the universe, in the eyes of the Planet Aquamarine people, he had only one identity—the greatest man of their planet, the pioneer of Planet Aquamarine who first stepped into the universe. That was a small step for Black Star but a big step for Planet Aquamarine.

Inside the national headquarters of the Aquamarine Federation, Bennett pushed back a political meeting and watched the broadcast.

His hair had already turned white, but it was still combed neatly. He had more wrinkles on his face too. He had become an old man. Having possessed the top power of the planet for many years, he had already developed the vibe of a man with power.

However, at this time, Bennett's lips were slightly raised, making more wrinkles on his face, and the corners of his eyes were glistening.

Decades ago, when he first met Han Xiao, that lonely man in his memories seemed to overlap with the tall and strong Black Star now.

Thousands of words rushed up to his mind, but all turned into a satisfied sigh.

I'm glad to have met you…

The speech was still going. Han Xiao's tone gradually became more emotional.

"When I was weak, I met dangers, and I met great men. On the way, I found both enemies and friends. The experiences I had at that time are still vivid in my mind, but when I think about them now, it almost feels like it was an entire lifetime ago.

"I worked hard and spent more than forty years developing the Black Star Army to what it is today. I think I have the right to be proud of it…"

Many army members nodded with admiration.

Almost all army members had taken thought-alignment classes; they knew about the rise of the army. Even those who joined the army for their own future admired the achievements Black Star had made in just over forty years.

Looking at the entire history of the Galaxy, how many people were able to start with nothing and build such an enormous force in such a short time? There was no one else!

Of course, there were people who had achieved more than Black Star, but they also spent a longer time. Black Star, and only Black Star, had risen in the Galaxy at a speed no one in the past could ever compare with.

In the exploration frontline stronghold at the free competition zone, Hila watched Han Xiao from the screen. The adventures they had together in the past flashed through her mind, and her gaze softened.

Manison, Kasuyi, Sorokin, and other Beyond Grade As were also watching the broadcast. Even the Dynasty Ruler Urranrell squeezed out some time in her extremely busy schedule to watch it. Hearing Han Xiao's words, these people uncontrollably sighed.

Maybe Black Star had conflicts with them, but from the bottom of their heart, they still admired what Black Star had achieved. None of them felt they could have done better than Black Star if they were in his position.

"What was I doing again when I was younger than a hundred years old? Still managing the logistics for the former chief?"

Manison was nostalgic.

At the venue, after Han Xiao listed the achievements of the army, his tone became formal.

"As I've just mentioned, although the Black Star Army has achieved many great things, its contribution to the universe is still too little, and I'm ashamed of that. Therefore, I felt that I should start a public report to the entire universe to show everyone what we're capable of, to do my best to give anyone with potential the chance to showcase themselves. And that is why I've founded the Black Star Cup…"

"That's quite a good way to put it…" Urranrell nodded in agreement.

She liked seeing Beyond Grade As enjoying their privileges while not forgetting about making contributions to the entire universe. Sadly, most people did not have this resolve. Although Black Star was unashamedly profit-oriented, she was quite happy he even had this mindset.

When the speech came to an end, Han Xiao smiled and said, "I've said enough. Now, this stage shall be given to the great kids of the Black Star Army. I hereby announce, the first season of the Black Star Cup Army Tournament starts now!"

As his speech ended, deafening applause sounded at the venue!

This was indeed an added sound effect.

If the speech ended and no one applauded, that would have been hella awkward. Plus, the army members were all in the spaceships, so their applause could not reach there.

In the cheering and applause, Han Xiao teleported away. The organizers of the competition showed up right after and started to direct the participants into the venue.

The audience also landed in their seats. The venue became boisterous.

According to the planning that Sylvia had hired some professional event organizers to do, there would be a large performance at the opening ceremony, and only a few more important competition items would be held.

Of course, combat-related events were a must. Referring to the Pro League, Han Xiao had also set up Singles, Groups, Duels, Flag Modes, and so on. He even brought up modes that only appeared in the later Pro Leagues and used them in the Black Star Cup.

There were ordinary people groups all the way up to Calamity Grade groups, as well as groups exclusive to Immortals. All the groups had to choose a representative to participate in the opening ceremony and showcase themselves.

As for the tons of sports and entertainment items, those more popular ones would be carried out.

Quite a number of sports and entertainment items did not have groupings, and Wayne Cards was one of them. Although there were no groupings, it surprisingly had the most participants, so it was chosen to be displayed in the opening ceremony.

The two Wayne Cards players who were about to play in the opening ceremony were Herlous, who was respected in the army's card social circle, and Hadavy, who was a known rascal in the gambling social circle of the army.

Inside an indoor venue, a Wayne Cards board was set up. As soon as the two players stepped into the venue, the difference in their treatments was already clearly visible.

The moment Herlous appeared, cheering from the countless card friends he had sounded, he was clearly very sociable. Hadavy, however, received a deafening hush when he took just a few steps. The audiences were paying their sincerest respect to this rascal who was horrible at gambling.

"Idiots." Hadavy rolled his eyes.

This time, Herlous looked over. These two card arch-enemies who had battled each other countless times looked into each other's eyes. They both saw the same thought in the other's eyes.

Without Feidin and Nero, the king of cards in the army shall be mine!

At the same time, the other stage was already at the Grade D group, and a player had appeared. It was a battle between a graduate of the Super Academy and a newbie player who had only joined in Version 4.0. The two of them looked at each other.

"Remember the rules. Don't continue attacking when the enemy has lost the ability to fight. Deliberately causing heavy injuries is not allowed, as is killing the opponent. The winner shall be determined when one side leaves the stage or admits defeat…"

The mechanical judge explained the rules from the side. Basically, other than deliberately causing heavy injuries to the opponent, there were no rules.

However, there was a special rule against players—as long as the player did not admit defeat, the opponent could beat up the player as much as they wanted; the player would not die anyway.

"That's all. The fight starts… now!"

As the judge gave the word, this academy graduate stomped the ground and charged toward his opponent without hesitation.

Clearly, this newbie player lacked combat experience. In the face of such an aggressive opponent, he immediately panicked. He raised his hand and summoned his two guns, and the high-quality mechanical suit he had bought from the logistics department quickly covered his body. He turned into a ghost-like phantom and swiftly moved around the enemy while continuously firing his guns. He was a Cannon Master.

"Shield!"

The academy graduate activated his mechanical suit too. A foldable ally shield extended on his arm, and the thin energy coating on it deflected all the blue laser beams of the newbie player.

At the same time, his other hand pulled out an intricate mechanical spear. The spear's tip split open, exposing the barrel within, and shot out explosive bullets one after another, chasing after the fast-moving opponent. The stage was quickly filled with dust and explosions.

This man was a Mechanical Pugilist.

As the Black Star Army's logistics department provided a lot of high-quality faction-exclusive mechanical weapons, be it the players or ordinary members under the army, many were willing to become Mechanics. After all, they could directly purchase the best equipment for their level in the army.

As long as they had money, they could even skip the gunpowder weapons and buy energy weapons very early on.

Actually, in the face of an Immortal, this academy graduate was more nervous.

Within the army, the players were a group of special beings that were almost deified. In the eyes of most of the lower-level army members, they were very mysterious. There were a lot of rumors about them possessing great power and being maniacs.

Just being unkillable was alright, but according to the rumors, the Immortals were maniacs who did not care about their own lives, which was terrifying…

The two of them fought intensely. Flames and lightning appeared everywhere they went.

The academy graduate fought cautiously, only to surprisingly realize his opponent clearly lacked combat experience. This made him much more confident. His attacks became more aggressive, and he gradually gained the upper hand.

"Looks like I'm about to lose…"

The newbie player looked at his steadily decreasing health, tutted, and took out Black Star Army Badge: Evolution with frustration.

"Roar!"

The next moment, an Aberration appeared on the stage!

This muscular monster pounced forward and pressed the academy graduate onto the ground in an instant, completely locking his movements.

An Aberration with Grade B combat capabilities was completely unbeatable in the Grade D group!

This time, the Aberration opened its enormous mouth, showing its rows of sharp teeth, and looked like he was about to bite down.

"I admit loss! H-help!"

The academy graduate was horrified. Looking at the foul mouth get closer, he subconsciously closed his eyes.

However, the bite he expected did not arrive. Instead, he felt an enormous wet and soft tongue lick him from top to bottom.

"The battle has ended. Blue has won!" the judge announced right on time.

"Ah, I've won!"

The newbie player jumped with excitement, shook his butt alluringly for a bit, and then ran to the edge of the floating stage and jumped right down, using the quickest method to get out of this dreadful look.

The dance of the Aberration was too beautiful. The spectators who saw it had to hold back the urge to dig out their eyes.

At the same time, countless viewers felt a chill up their spine.

The rumors were right. The Immortals were indeed maniacs.

On the stage, the academy graduate lay on the ground covered with saliva. His eyes had their vibrance, and he started to doubt the definition of life.

It was a sure win, but the tables had been turned instantly by the opponent's suicidal shapeshift.

What a hard life I have…

As long as no additional damage was done, items could be used freely in the Black Star Cup. The players were very satisfied with this rule.

In the Pro League, the various powerful weapons of the army were all forbidden. Now that they could use them freely, it felt really good.

Although this was not fair to the army members in the lower grades, this was exactly what Han Xiao wanted. He had a few reasons for it. The first was to show the outside world the terrifying side of the players, that they could possess very high combat capability even at very low grades.

The second reason was to stimulate the sales of the evolution badge. If those players in the lower grade competitions saw that the evolution badge could basically make them invincible and ensure they could achieve a high placement, why would they not buy it?

Furthermore, the evolution badge was not a one-use item, but it had to be recharged.

The last reason was that Han Xiao actually wanted the players to receive the reward for the lower grade competitions. After all, there was not much he could gain from the normal members, and giving the players these rewards was indirectly fertilizing his leek field.

What, the normal players are not happy about it? I didn't say they can't use those strong items, did I? If they have the resolve to not take their life seriously, they can go ahead and use them just like the players.

Even if someone really did it, the judge would not approve of it. Sportsmanship first, competition second. Committing suicide on-stage was not allowed… Oh, except for those who could not die.

Unfair? It is what it is. Not being able to die is their talent. Like those people who have healing powers, you can't not let them use those powers too, can you? Wouldn't that be unfair to them?

If you need to blame it on something, blame it on the fact that you're not an Immortal. Anyway, the final rules are made by the Army Commander. Go find him if you have a problem.

Therefore, even the low-grade army members could not say anything about it. They might even think it made sense.

Without having to make other arrangements, this rule was all the Great Mechanic Han needed to achieve the results he wanted.

…

When the Black Star Cup opening ceremony was being carried out, at the same time, in the Ancient Star Desert Star Field, a civilian archaeological team landed on a desolate planet that no one had been to in many years.

It was called an archaeological team, but they were actually scavengers.

The Ancient Star Desert was very old. Many of its locations were ancient battlefields. There were many mysterious ruins and wastes. Therefore, this Star Field was filled with scavengers trying their luck, hoping to find something good, sell it to the black market, and make a fortune.

In the midst of a blurry corrosive sandstorm that roared across the land, a scavenger wearing a bloated protection suit was using all kinds of mechanical devices to observe underground.

A short, skinny, monkey-like looking team member operated on the screen for a while, then suddenly yelled with surprise.

"Haha, we're in luck! There's an ancient stratum on this planet, and the age of it can't be detected. This means that it's so ancient that it exceeded the upper limit of this device of ours, and more complex tests need to be done to come to a result. I'm now using shock wave detection to draw the map of the underground… Done!"

A complicated underground cavity appeared on the screen. It had a lot of splits and corners that seemed like they were built for the purpose of confusing anyone who went in. With a simple look, it was quite large.

"There are no signs of it ever being discovered!" The short man was overjoyed. "We might have run into a previously-undiscovered ancient civilization ruin!"

"Or it could be filled with rusted metal." Another team member shrugged.

"No matter what, let's dig in first," someone who looked like the team leader said with a calm tone. "Have the spaceship send in the drilling rig. Let's dive down."

While they were about to move, this time, a team member pulled the captain's arm and wiped away the dust on his mask with his other hand, showing a young and handsome face. He was frowning and looked worried.

"Don't go down first…"

This man's tone was hesitant.

"I have a feeling that we might dig out something bad…"

If Han Xiao was there, he would have definitely recognized this face.

This was a renowned explorer in the World Tree version.

The first person who discovered the main body of the World Tree!

Chapter 1094: Pandora's Box

Harrison Moore, a well-known interstellar free explorer, had been passionate about digging for relics and searching for the unknown throughout his life. Though his strength was low, he would magically unearth and discover countless historical relics over the years. He had written more than ten works, and his adventurous spirit had attracted a large number of followers in the universe. He was regarded as a spiritual leader and a beacon of light in life.

During the war against the World Tree Civilization, Harrison was in his old age and had already semi-retired. The three Universal Civilizations were the ones to be discovered and thus raided by the World Tree Civilization. They were caught off guard, suffering heavy losses. Because they did not know the origin of the enemy, all civilizations within the explored universe were basically beaten in the early stage. Their entire universe was on the defensive and could only passively resist the endless stream of invaders, as all their planets were occupied by the World Tree Civilization and used as nourishment.

The three Universal Civilizations tried their best to collect clues about the World Tree Civilization, of which the most important one was where the World Tree itself was located.

The World Tree was a Universal Treasure, and it was discovered by the World Tree Civilization during the slash-and-burn era of farming. As such, it gave rise to a distorted form of civilization, where all the development of the civilization was carried out with the World Tree as the core. Countless people tried their best to nourish and enhance this Universal Treasure.

Due to the special nature of the World Tree, only through finding its main body could the problem then be solved from the root. Otherwise, no matter how many invaders they repelled, the World Tree could still use the nutrients from the planets to transform and nurture more troops.

The main body of the World Tree was rooted within the secondary dimensions and hidden deeply. Within that era, the exploration teams mostly consisted of soldiers, and many exploration teams were spontaneously organized to search in the secondary dimensions. Harrison had also re-emerged and joined them.

Because of a series of coincidences, he was also the first to discover the secondary dimension containing the World Tree's main body. He sacrificed his life to record the coordinates, throwing it into the spatial storms of the secondary dimension.

The coordinates were like a drifting bottle floating within the vast ocean, bobbing up and down before finally falling into the hands of the three Universal Civilizations. Thus, Harrison's deeds were passed down, and the world knew of all his achievements.

All of these were Harrison's achievements in the later versions of Han Xiao's past life.

In this current era, Harrison was still a young and new explorer. His great curiosity and desire to explore had prompted him to give up the opportunity to inherit the wealth of his financial group and instead step into this industry.

As a newcomer to this exploration team, Harrison's intuition was obviously not convincing to them. His teammates had the mentality that they could not set off and come back empty-handed. Thus, Harrison's spirit of questioning the source, unfortunately, went unheeded.

Harrison himself had no choice. His curiosity outweighed his vigilance, so he pressed down the vague worry to the bottom of his heart, continuing the journey with his team.

A scavenger spaceship passed through a high-altitude sandstorm, hovering around a hundred meters above the ground before dropping a multi-functional burrowing vehicle. Its outer armor was full of colorful and wild graffiti. Very obviously, it had undergone some processing by this bunch of scavengers with limited knowledge of art.

The group boarded the burrowing vehicle and burrowed into the ground under the instructions of the detection radar, quickly approaching the underground cavity on the map.

Because such underground remains had existed for too long a time, the structure was typically unstable and stood a chance to collapse. Thus, the scavengers normally did not directly drill into the passage but chose to follow the path set.

Hu!

Very quickly, the tip of the drill penetrated the rock formation, exposing a cavity. The team members got down, switching on their flashlights to observe the surrounding environment.

This was an underground cave with traces of being made by man. It was about seven or eight meters high, and at the end of this cave was a closed metal door, which seemed to be the entrance to this underground ruin.

Their short member who served as the detector jogged over, taking out various instruments to scan the metal door. He muttered, "It's well preserved, with few traces of rust. This is a high-strength alloy material, and according to the rough detection results, the material is likely synthesized by a star system level civilization or above. However, there's no matching material record in our database…"

Hearing this, the crowd got excited. The higher the level of the lost civilization they discovered, the more valuable their discoveries would be on the black market.

However, this also represented more unknown risks.

"Any energy responses from inside?" the captain asked.

"Let me see, er… totally absent. I think the energy source has been drained dry. Even if there are traps or defensive measures, they should be frozen."

"Then let's go in and take a look," the captain said. "Later on, take precautions. Without my command, no one is to remove their own protective shield."

A group of personnel cut open the door using a laser cutting, before tiptoeing inside and fumbling their way. The route within resembled that of a large underground military base.

Harrison walked to a sign, wiping the dust off it, and let the translator read the text. However, there was no result.

"There's no record of this kind of text in the database. We can determine that this is a relic of a civilization that has not been discovered thus far." Harrison spoke through the channel.

"Today is really my lucky day. No wonder Ah Xiang finally responded to my daily greeting even though I've been sending signals to her for months," the short detector guy replied in excitement.

"What did she say?" Harrison was curious.

"She said ok."

"… Keep it up."

Everyone chatted idly as they searched. They were carefully all the way but found out that there was no danger within. Searching the rooms, they only found living facilities, with no special equipment nor text documents present. Even the energy and network facilities were absent along with any sort of defense facilities. It seemed as though this base had been long abandoned and everything within emptied.

The flames of excitement in everyone's hearts seemed to have been extinguished by a basin of cold water.

"This can't be it, right? I found an unknown ruin, but there's nothing valuable here. Isn't it a wasted trip then?" the detector guy complained.

"It's not in vain. At least we managed to discover a new language, which means an unknown civilization that once existed." Harrison raised the translator in his hand. He had recorded all the signs on the path that they had walked down so far.

"What does this bullsh*t archaeological result mean for us? We're not even historians!" someone among the team complained. "If it weren't for getting valuable stuff, who would want to come to such a weird place?"

Scavengers did not have much patience, and their searching speed got faster along the way. It did not take long before only the last room was left, located at the core position at the bottom of the base.

The group cut open the door and walked in, collectively taking a gasp.

There was a triangular body about three to four meters high, embedded in the ground in the center of the room. The whole body was pitch black and as smooth as a mirror. It resembled obsidian somewhat, but the detector revealed it as a metallic material. On one side, a display screen was embedded.

Only this thing existed in the room, nothing else, as though this was an exclusive warehouse.

"Haha, there's finally something."

"What is that?"

Everyone surrounded it, brimming with curiosity, feeling here and there and knocking around. Although they did not know what this was, just looking at its appearance, there was no worry that it could not be sold on the black market.

The detector guy came over to the screen on the triangle and pressed a few times, but there was no response. He fumbled around and finally found that there was a movable board beside the screen, which revealed a socket seemingly for charging it.

"Uh… this is the first time I've seen a socket of this shape, but there should be no problem." The guy groaned but quickly took out an energy storage device, transforming its transmission line to fit with the socket.

Just as he was about to charge the triangular block, Harrison was frowning and suddenly spoke.

"Wait a moment!"

Everyone turned to look at him.

"What's wrong now?"

"I… I feel that it's still better to be cautious. No one knows what this device is for. What happens if it's a weapon that has run out of energy?"

Harrison had an expression of hesitation. The moment he set eyes on this triangle, he had felt an inexplicable palpitation, as though there was a voice in his heart warning him that this thing was dangerous. The instinct that he had been born with had never been so strong.

The short detector guy did not even look back as he explained, "Relax, I probed it just now, and this is actually a sophisticated disposable safe device that will be destroyed when opened. It's just that the innermost layer contains a material that isolates any detection, so I don't know what's stored within."

With that, he directly plugged into the socket, releasing a weak energy charge. The triangle device's display lit up, and a password input interface popped up.

The captain scooted over for a look. "Can the code be cracked?"

The short detector guy took out another device to fiddle around, and spoke with certainty, "The code of this device changes in real time, so it has to be connected to the quantum network and then use Virtual Technology to decipher the code… The tools I currently have are not good enough, but so long as I use a deciphering device with a higher computing power, it can definitely be opened."

"If this is the case…" The captain hesitated for a while before saying, "In that case, let's not open it. Like you said, this thing is a one-off thing. If the items stored inside are not valuable, we'll lose money. It's better to just put this safe on the black market for auction and let others draw the prize. Anyway, stuff like this is very common on the black market as well…"

"Can we discuss these things later?" Harrison was feeling nervous for no reason. "Let's get out of here now. I have a bad feeling…"

"Since when has your intuition been good?"

The captain glared at him but did not reject his proposal. He got everyone to transport the device to the rig.

This was the only valuable thing in this ruin, so this entire group took the device and left, not even bothering to look back at the ruins.

Suddenly, one of the team members noted in a thoughtful manner, "This is strange. By logic, since this planet has traces of an unknown civilization, there should be others, but the detection result only showed this one… That's impossible. Did that unknown civilization only dig this one underground facility on this planet?"

"That's right. I thought it was strange too," another worker added.

At this moment, the shortie took a glance at the radar and exclaimed, "Captain, the ruins seem to have collapsed!"

Everyone turned over to look and saw that the cavity had indeed mysteriously filled up and disappeared. They could no longer return even if they wished to.

"How strange…" the captain mumbled, shaking his head. He ordered, "Forget about it, let's just mark down the coordinates of this planet, and go to the nearest black market to reap our rewards for today."

Hearing that, everyone immediately put away any distracting thoughts and started to move, operating their spaceship to leave the planet.

Harrison was the only one who remained standing at the porthole, looking at the shrinking planet. He suddenly felt a little chill run down his spine.

He had a hunch, as though the goal of those ruins was specifically just to store this triangular device.

The ruins had collapsed immediately after they left, as though they had only been waiting for someone to take this thing away.

Harrison could not help but turn his head back for a look.

In the corner of his eyes, the triangular device lay silently at the back, as though it was a Pandora's box that was waiting to be opened.

…

The opening ceremony of the Black Star Cup was wonderfully opened, and its qualifiers were in full swing the next day. The army had become very lively, and hundreds of millions of members were actively participating on the field, which also improved the enthusiasm of the universe audiences.

Because there were so many events, each media group provided live broadcasts and video review functions throughout the day. Viewers could freely adjust their channels and choose to watch any event, venue, or even the players, which caused countless people to hold up their communicators and stare at them all day long.

The ratings of the Black Star Cup were maintained at a very high level throughout the universe. At present, the average ratings in each region were second only to the news broadcasts of the three Universal Civilizations.

The Black Star Cup tournament organization department, which was only established little more than two months prior, counted the programs with the highest ratings. Other than the battle events, the best were the entertainment programs. Especially in the talent audition category such as singing and dancing, there were countless galactic residents happy to see the Supers appear on alternative programs rather than just in battles.

Some of the talented people had even attracted a large number of admirers, and there were even audiences on the net arguing about the pros and cons of each person… As it turned out, no matter which age it was, such a program would also garner views.

As for the lowest ratings, it was as Han Xiao expected. They were those technological and skill-based competitions, such as the machinery maintenance that Reynold had asked for, waste modification for machinery, and even blueprint crafting competitions…

While there were people willing to look at such programs, they were few and between.

However, Han Xiao did not mind it. Such technical programs were treated more as auditions, to explore potential talents in the various fields and add more fresh blood to the army.

The way to rise in the army had always been clear, and one's rank and position were linked to meritorious service and their qualifications. The Black Star Cup was just another shortcut for its members to ascend in the rankings. Those who were more capable at their level would move toward the upper ranks. This made the members enthusiastic as this model allowed many people to obtain more opportunities within the army.

While the players had their own competition brackets, they were keener to participate in the normal competition brackets, running over to play with the NPCs.

Because the Evolution badge shone in such low-level team events, more and more players had also begun to purchase this item, causing the sales of it to soar drastically.

Using the Evolution badges in events below Grade B gave players a huge boost in strength, but this did not necessarily mean they would win. The biological aberrations were strong in close combat, but their weaknesses were also obvious; their resistance to magic and psychic attacks plummeted, and their range also decreased to melee attacks. They were extremely easy to kite. Plus, they lost HP constantly.

When facing Psychics or Mages, the aberrations usually failed quite badly.

In the Grade B and above ranks, the role of the Evolution Limit: Aberration was not so strong. Grade Bs could directly contend against the aberrations themselves.

Meanwhile, the players from the other countries could only watch with envious and reddened eyes at the festivities in full swing within the Black Star Army.

Let alone attending, they did not even have the qualifications to bet on the winning players!

If one were to split apart the characters of 'following the crowd' (从众), they would get five 'people' characters (人). The majority of people understood the meaning of 'the more the merrier', and seeing this group of Black Star players having fun, the sense of loss was even more intense.

Everyone is playing so happily, and all without me!

Compared to the faction war event more than half a year ago, there were more players that were being moved by the Black Star Army this time. Most likely, the army would indirectly poach a lot of players once more.

Even the Limitless Financial Group experienced a huge outflow of players, but Sorokin was acting extremely low-key, which meant he could not react.

The most painful ones were the foreign clubs in the other factions. They obviously did not do anything this time, but they still had to watch on as the ordinary players left their factions. They could no longer find any reason to stay and just felt like crying.

Why are you forcing us to join this party?

Black Star Army! You're too much!

A man can only take so much anger. If you have the guts, you can anger me again!

If you force me again, I'll really join your organization!

Chapter 1095: Fifth Stage of the God's Trait Transformation and the Butterfly Effect

Over ten days later, in the central area of Black Star Palace, a war halberd was situated against a backdrop of the starry sky. It looked like a folded mechanical blade that was magnified countless times, painted black and gold. Its patterns and structures were also complicated, and it looked both luxurious and exquisite.

Mechanical rings were currently situated in different areas of his mechanical war halberd. Numerous flexible mechanical arms extended from the inner part of each ring, which were molded into different tools to work on parts of the halberd. These rings were manufacturing auxiliary tools that were dedicated to the manufacturing and assembly of mega machines, known as 'Mega-Assembly Rings'. Right now, they were all connected through Mechanical Force and operated fully under its control.

On the other end of the Mechanical Force linking the assembly rings together, a black robed figure stood there. It was precisely Han Xiao, and this mega war halberd was the exclusive Universal Treasure for the Mechanical Deity's usage, named 'Celestial Punishment Edge'.

Han Xiao kept his Perfect Mechanical Sense active, closely watching the subtle energy flows in every place during the construction of the Celestial Punishment Edge, doing minute adjustments now and then just like a chef watching his signature dish.

As the mechanical arm of the mega assembly ring inserted the last bolt in, a notification sounded from Han Xiao's interface.

_____________________

You have built a Gold Grade item (Universal Treasure).

You have benefitted from [Spirit Instrument].

You have received 1 God's Trait Transformation Point (Cannot be obtained again through the same blueprint).

One of your random attributes has been decreased by 425…

Randomizing…

Randomizing complete.

-425 CHA.

You have received 425 Free Attribute Points.

You have been awarded the third layer bonus of [Spirit Instrument]: +2.5% success rate for the manufacture of Gold Grade blueprints, +1.2% success rate for the research and development of a Gold Grade Blueprint, +0.4% chance to obtain a Space Wonder mutation.

_____________________

"It's finally done…" Seeing the notification of success, Han Xiao's taut nerves finally relaxed.

This was the third Universal Treasure he had personally manufactured. Its difficulty was way higher compared to the Emperor's Cape, and it had cost him quite a tidy sum before he finally succeeded in creating it.

However, when compared to the terrifying profits brought in by the sale of the Evolutionary Totems as well as the Black Star Cup, this amount was nothing.

Han Xiao retrieved all the mega assembly rings before storing the Celestial Punishment Edge into his Dimension Factory. Opening his attribute list, he threw the God's Trait Transformation point into his main class route, so [God's Trait Transformation—Machinery] unlocked its fifth stage.

_____________________

Stage 5: +3 to all skills from [Lord Mechanic] and [Divine Throne Mechanic]. You have received a 1.1x boost to Machinery Affinity, +28% boost to abilities, 1.2x boost to Attack Power Output, 1.2x boost to Shield Durability, +40% Mechanical Energy Core Power Output, and +20% to all types of Energy Power Output.

_____________________

"Whoa, this wave allows me to increase my strength!" Han Xiao got excited.

In the first few stages, the God's Trait mainly focused on improving his production and R&D capabilities. For the fifth stage, it finally ushered in a wave of substantial combat strength enhancement. A boost of 1.1x to his Machinery Affinity already meant more than a 2,000% increase to his original Machinery Affinity, not to mention that there was even a boost to abilities, which was the best option to obtain. All its other effects were also biased toward combat.

Furthermore, the skills of his [Lord Mechanic] and [Divine Throne Mechanic] class were also his main combat skills, thus breaking the upper cap by three levels, which represented a great increase in his combat power, at least translating to three more Apostle Weapons.

"In this case, the focus of the fifth stage is to enhance my own efficiency with machinery… eh?" Han Xiao mumbled to himself, but he suddenly discovered that the notifications had not stopped.

_____________________

[God's Trait Transformation—Machinery] has achieved the Fifth Stage.

There are now unknown changes in your Life Hierarchy.

You have obtained a new understanding of Machinery. +15% chance of forming a new exclusive expertise. The skill [Universal Simulation] has obtained a sublimation.

You have begun to perceive part of the power of the transformation route - [Talent Unknown].

You have received 1 [The First Sanctum] Ability Fragment.

_____________________

Seeing this, Han Xiao started guessing once more.

"It seems like the fifth stage of God's Trait Transformation should be a threshold, just like how there's a bottleneck in the Energy Rank for Beyond Grade As… If this applies to all God's Trait Transformation skills, then what's the upper limit? Ten? Fifteen?"

Han Xiao deeply pondered. Right now, he had an interface that allowed him to directly add points into it, but the normal Beyond Grade A's method of increasing their number of God's Trait Transformation stages would not be as convenient as his. In fact, it would take many years for them to even upgrade each level.

After reaching the Fifth Stage of God's Trait Transformation—Machinery, he was also awarded an Ability Fragment of [The First Sanctum]. Han Xiao had already obtained three fragments so far, but there was still no sign of them combining together. It was also unknown how many fragments he would need to complete this thing.

As of now, Han Xiao also did not know how to obtain an exclusive expertise. If the premise to obtain one was to be immersed within a certain area, then he had already fulfilled the condition with his time spent within the Machinery field. However, there was still no prompt whatsoever.

As for [Universal Simulation], Han Xiao was not foreign to that skill. He used to constantly activate the skill in order to attempt to discover Universal Treasure blueprints, but the progress was so slow it would make one cry.

Seeing the notification on the interface at this time, Han Xiao once again activated the skill, entering the familiar horizon once more. He carefully sensed his surroundings and felt that there had been some subtle changes as compared to the past.

However, this sort of feeling was akin to grasping something in the dark. It was more like his intuition was sharper than before. Anywhere he looked, there would be a sort of 'hindsight' within his brain explaining what he saw.

"There's a sort of feeling pointing me toward the essence of the item… Oh, I guess an improvement in knowledge?"

After experiencing this, Han Xiao did not discover anything too out of the ordinary, and thus, he withdrew his skill, cleaning up the venue before proceeding back to the palace.

Back in his room, Han Xiao took a look at the Black Star Cup tournament.

With Phillip's efficient scheduling and the massive investment of resources, the qualifiers were so fast paced that nearly a third of the people had already been eliminated.

Before this, the galactic residents only knew about the existence of the players but did not pay special attention to them. This time, however, because the Black Star Cup was broadcast to the entire universe, the performance of these players fell into the eyes of the more ordinary people, which aroused their attention and interest.

For the players, who were deemed immortal lunatics, the majority of ordinary people were curious and scared of them. Their mood was like they had encountered an exhibitionist, subconsciously covering their eyes but unable to resist peeking through their fingers.

Coupled with the behavior of the players within the Flickering World, the nickname 'Cancer of the Universe' gradually spread out and received the approval of more people.

The excitement of the Black Star Cup had also attracted a large number of foreign players.

The number of players within the army had always been steadily increasing, and it finally broke through the ten million mark a few days ago. Han Xiao estimated that the final number of army players at the end of this version would be higher than his original estimate of 11.5 million.

The Cancer of the Universe represented disorder and chaos, and since it was basically impossible to recruit all players, the Black Star Army could already slightly guide the overall character of the players. In this manner, so long as he could perform some damage control to ensure that the problems caused by the players were not as serious as in his previous life, that would be enough.

"Speaking of which, my biopic seems like it's about to be released…"

Han Xiao suddenly remembered that he had not touched Feidin for a long time, and he coincidentally recalled this incident.

He searched the net and discovered that the movie had already wrapped up its filming and was slated to be released next month.

Because of the advancements made in productivity, even ordinary citizens of the galactic society could now afford the cost of planning a film, resulting in the proliferation of movies. Coupled with advanced portable equipment as well as the high penetrative rate of the quantum network, the low-profit theater operating model had almost been eliminated, giving way for a more convenient video platform system. New films were released simultaneously on the platforms of all the Star Fields and could be found online.

The movie of his life had an unpretentious name—Black Star: Origins. This movie told his story from Planet Aquamarine, from escaping the Germinal Organization up till he stepped into the galaxy. Because of the limited time frame, Director Beny Travol had cut out most of his deeds, only leaving the key factors to control the rhythm of the film.

Han Xiao had already looked through the preview and had to admit that this well-known director did have the ability to give his experience a lot of surprising twists and turns. He ended the film when Han Xiao stepped into the galactic region, leaving an opportunity to extend it with a sequel.

Within the trailer, Feidin had put on some makeup to pose as the Great Mechanic Han during his time as Black Phantom, and he moved with a face that looked as though he would kill everyone in cold blood.

Seeing this scene, one would only think of the description "Flying like a crane, soaring like a dragon".

"So cool…" Han Xiao was very satisfied. "He has portrayed my character image very well."

He eyed the forums and saw that the players were also very interested in the movie. They wanted to see the story of Black Star being made into a movie, while at the same time, they wished to see themselves within the movie.

The movie also portrayed the roles of the immortals, so seeing their own deeds being made into a movie by an NPC gave the players a novel feeling.

"After this movie is released, maybe it can turn into something similar to Bun-Hit-Dog's videos, increasing the cohesion of the army's players… If this works, maybe I can get the director to produce a few more sequels."

Mentally taking note of this, Han Xiao continued to surf on the net before discovering another piece of news that caught his attention.

The Crimson Dynasty had announced that in ten days, the Dark Lord would publicly execute two Beyond Grade As. One of them was Traveler, while the other was an innocent person who was hired by the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

"It is finally going to begin…" Han Xiao pursed his lips.

In this manner, the conflicts between the Beyond Grade As and the Universal Civilizations would only worsen. While there was still a long way to go before it erupted, the seeds of dissatisfaction were already sown.

However, the goal of the three Universal Civilizations this time was not the Beyond Grade As but rather the Super Star Cluster Alliance. They wanted to scare off those Beyond Grade A hired by the Super Star Cluster Alliance, in order to cut off its wings. The three Universal Civilizations had already begun their future plans of suppression.

…

In the Star Arc Civilization's Flickering World territory, a group of senior officials had gathered in a remote conference room with grim expressions.

"The dynasty has captured Traveller and intends to publicly execute him. What should we do?"

"There's no way about it. We can only abandon him. We can't afford to clash with the three Universal Civilizations yet."

"It's a pity then. Traveler was truly loyal to our civilization. This is a huge loss for us."

"The question now is whether Traveler has revealed his true identity. If the dynasty discovers his background, they will have an excuse to provoke a dispute against us."

"Traveler should not betray the civilization, but such matters can't be guaranteed. We must be prepared not to recognize his identity."

Everyone chattered anxiously.

The three Universal Civilizations wished to suppress the Super Star Cluster Alliance, but it was easier said than done. Each of them was an advanced civilization in the universe, and they had to have a legitimate reason to make a move, even if it was a trivial problem. As the rulers of the explored universe, the Universal Civilizations had to maintain the moral high ground, regardless of whether the reason was true or false. They just had to provide an answer for the masses.

Thus, the Super Star Cluster Alliance was keeping a low profile and was unwilling to give the three Universal Civilizations an excuse. Its current presence in the universe was not too outstanding.

The strength of the Super Star Cluster Alliance was only below that of the Universal Civilizations, so they would not be easily suppressed. While the three Universal Civilizations were clamoring to suppress them, they also had to make sufficient preparations.

No matter the three Universal Civilizations or the Super Star Cluster Alliance, they restrained themselves for the time being. Both sides understood that this was just the calm before the storm and that they had to first complete the development of the new Star Field.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance wished to obtain a chance to rise up, and the result of this conflict will determine the future of the explored universe.

…

"40,000 Enas!"

"45,000 Enas!"

"45,000 going once, going twice… no higher bids? Okay, 45,000 going thrice. The antiques produced by the Dhogo Civilization now belong to Buyer #068!"

Within a small private space station in the Ancient Star Desert, there was a black market auction underway.

The auction site was a circular room with a booth in the center where the items were displayed. By the side, the auctioneer introduced each one of them to the virtual screens on the surrounding walls. Each screen represented a black market buyer who was remotely participating in the auction. Everyone's identity was kept confidential this way.

Because this was a remote auction, each item would be delivered to the buyer's designated location through the black market's logistics channel.

The auctioneer knocked on the table before shouting, "The next auction item is a disposable safe discovered by an archaeological team on a deserted planet. This item comes from the ruins of an unknown civilization, which is suspected to be at the Star System level or above. You'll need the quantum network to decipher the code on the device before it can be opened. Right now, it has yet to be opened, so it's up to your luck as to what comes out. Of course, it's also possible for you to purchase the item just for your collection. The starting bid is 4,000 Enas."

A few workers brought up a gleaming triangular device, which was precisely the artifact that Harrison's team had unearthed.

In the meantime, Harrison's team was situated in a VIP room, watching the live broadcast of this auction.

"We worked our asses off, and the starting price is only 4,000 Enas. This auction house is too stingy." The shortie detector guy was depressed.

"Black market auctions are generally like this." The captain was experienced in this regard. "Relax, the most important thing is that the black market has no lack of rich people who wish to try their luck. I estimate that the official transaction volume will exceed 20,000 Enas."

"20,000 is not bad," the shortie replied, "but it's not as good as tomb raiding for antiques…"

By the side, Harrison was a little anxious. "Is this black market safe?"

"Relax, I'm a regular here. This is one of the properties under the Beast Ancestor, and there are no bandits that dare rob this place… Wait a minute." The captain jerked before continuing with uncertainty. "It seems like Gorutan was captured some time ago?"

"It can't be. You forgot about such an important piece of news‽" The shortie opened his eyes wide and hurriedly questioned. "There should be no problems with the transaction, right? I still want to buy a gift for my Ah Xiang!"

"There shouldn't be…" The captain also hesitated a little at this time. "While the Beast Ancestor has fallen, this black market should now have a new backer. There should not be any problems… I think?"

Harrison facepalmed.

This bunch of people were too unreliable. He was better off working solo from now on.

At this very moment, there were a dozen battleships hidden not far away from this planet. They belonged to a group of star bandits that circulated around the Ancient Star Desert.

In the flagship, the leader of this bandit group led a group of men, looking out at the planet from the porthole.

"Captain, are we really going to rob them? I heard that this auction is the property of the Beast Ancestor, and it's not easy to mess with him."

"What are you scared of? The Beast Ancestor has been captured by Black Star, and his organization is in tatters, having been snatched away by the other Galactic Black Market Protectors. Others have also taken over his troops, but they have not fully integrated them as of now."

The leader smiled, his eyes flashing with greed.

"I've already inquired and discovered that the Beast Ancestor's warriors that protect their logistics carriers have been withdrawn. They are in their most vulnerable state now!"

Chapter 1096: Disturbing One's Fate

A couple of days later…

"The transport carrier was raided‽"

Harrison's team, who were still waiting at the hotel, suddenly stood up, furious, and stared at the remote projection of the worker that had come to inform them of the matter.

"That's right. A group of galactic pirates discovered our secret transportation route and attacked all the disguised spaceships that we used to transport the items." The auctioneer's face was also ugly.

"What about your guards?" Harrison could not help asking that. "I heard that you have ties to the Beast Ancestor…"

Hearing his words, the worker's expression turned dark. "After the Beast Ancestor got captured, we lost our backer. We could only employ mercenaries. This group of galactic pirates has long been watching us, and they bribed our mercs, launching a raid from both the inside and outside. All our newly hired guards died in that battle."

At this point, the auctioneer could not help but release a sigh.

If Gorutan was still present, they would have had the shelter of the Beast Ancestor, which was enough to frighten most people in the Ancient Star Desert.

But now that their backer had fallen, the new upper ranks were still slowly absorbing the black market organization of the Beast Ancestor. They were most vulnerable and had turned into fat sheep surrounded by wolves.

"Then, what about our things?" The captain showed a wary expression.

This black market had maintained a good reputation in the past, so he had chosen to return to sell his things. However, with such a big chance, he was not sure if the other party would rescind their original promises. The order of the black market was fragile, and it mainly worked on the stronger eating the weak.

"We will assemble a team to search for the whereabouts of this group of galactic pirates and retrieve our items."

"And if it cannot be retrieved…"

"Then the auction house will compensate according to the starting price." After this sentence, the worker did not continue speaking, choosing to end the conversation immediately.

They exchanged looks.

"Our starting price was only 4,000 Enas, but the final price was 13,800!"

"Just be satisfied that they are willing to even pay compensation," the captain replied helplessly. "The probability of obtaining compensation through a black market auction is less than ten percent. They are probably only doing so because they deem our item worthless. If it was a price of hundreds of thousands, they would have found some way to deny any responsibility and not pay up."

Hearing this, the group collectively sighed. They already thought that their trip was quite bad this time round, but to even lose the item that they had painstakingly slogged away for, this was truly a wasted trip.

Harrison felt a little restless. His intuition was still sending out warning signals.

He had this premonition that the robbed item would still bring him quite a bit of trouble.

Somewhere within the Ancient Star Desert, the galactic pirate fleet dragged the logistics ship that was their loot and moved slowly within the universe.

"This is quite the fruitful harvest this time."

Within the cabin, the leader of the pirates placed his arms on his waist as he arrogantly walked in front of the captives and the spoils piled up into a hill.

"Boss, the ammunition is all perfectly intact." One of his subordinates was ecstatic.

There were all kinds of items within the war loot. Not only various ancient blueprints, technological creations, and antiques, but there were also various types of arms from the advanced civilizations. The auctions from the black market sold practically everything, and compared to the antiques, the galactic pirates naturally preferred the arms.

As he strolled through the loot, the eyes of the leader stopped at the triangular device.

"What is that?"

"Leader, this is a safe from an unknown civilization that an archaeological team dug up."

"What's inside?"

"We don't know. It seems like it's not worth a lot."

"Open it." The leader lifted up his foot, jabbing it toward the device.

Reality had proven that opening a sealed box was something that everyone loved to do. The mechanics within the pirate team took out their equipment to tinker with the device, while the pirates gathered in the surroundings to watch.

The triangular device's socket was connected to an energy transmission line to activate the password interface. One of them then took out a deciphering device, connecting the triangle to the quantum network, and the interface of the cracking device quickly bounced with various garbled codes.

After a moment, the triangle let out a 'ding' sound, indicating that it had been unlocked.

Ka ka ka!

The display screen used to enter the password was then retracted, and the whole device began rotating like a Rubik's Cube.

Everyone, including the leader, craned their necks to see what was stored inside.

In about ten seconds, the safe was finally completely unlocked. The last layer of protection was peeled off, exposing the core, which was around ten cubic centimeters in size.

The next moment, a surge of energy fluctuations burst out from within!

Boom!

Before the group could see what was inside, they were thrown away by the shock wave. Even their leader, who was at the Calamity Grade, was not exempted.

The next second, the surroundings of the triangular device turned into an empty zone, and the loot in its surroundings was all strewn around the area, turning the place into a mess.

"Ouch…"

Everyone rubbed their butt as they got up, only to find out that there were no other injuries on them.

The leader immediately turned to look at the safe but found it empty.

"Where's the item inside? Why is there nothing‽"

The leader was furious, feeling as though he had been played.

Could this just have been a prank?

Who would store a fart inside a disposable safe!

At this moment, the cabin door opened, and operators of the spaceship ran in with anxious expressions.

"Leader, what just happened? The location we were in just now became the origin of a cosmic energy surge. The energy fluctuations broke through the peak in an instant, and our detection radar burned out. There's no matching energy model for this surge in the database at all!"

Hearing this, the pirates received a shock.

Cosmic energy surge?

What joke was this? It only caused them to fall on their asses, but this sort of power was considered a cosmic surge?

Just as this group was in confusion, in a world that the naked eyes could not see, a unique information package was duplicating wildly, centered on the galactic pirates' fleet, spreading rapidly along the links of their quantum network.

In the face of this information signal, the firewalls of the artificial intelligences in all devices were rendered useless.

There was a dimly lit palace, supported by pillars that rose up to no end. Below every pillar was a fire brazier, with pale flames dancing on it as the only source of light.

A man dressed in black robes hovered in midair, the edges of his robes seemingly burning, releasing strands of black mist.

Below him, Law and Fay were bowing as they reported the result of their mission to the upper echelons of the Holy Accord. The both of them were Beyond Grade As, yet they did not dare look up at the figure above.

"… You're saying, there's no way to obtain the Holy Light Particle?"

A voice sounded directly in their hearts. While the tone was neither soft nor heavy, both of them trembled unconsciously.

Law gritted his teeth and said, "That's right. We've already ambushed Black Star once, so he will definitely be prepared this time round. If we act rashly, the organization will be exposed to much greater risk. Black Star announcing in such a high profile that he possessed the Holy Light Particle is likely him deliberately trying to lure us out. According to the data, Black Star is extremely vengeful, and he definitely wishes to get his revenge on us…"

By the side, Fay said, "While Black Star has found a host for the Holy Light Particle, he is likely also prepared. During the attack on Hila, Black Star displayed an ability to perform an unrestricted teleportation. He has no reason not to use it for the Holy Light Particle's host, so it is likely a decoy."

The man in black lowered his head, looking down at the two as he fell silent. After a while, he slowly said, "I understand. Don't act on the Holy Light Particle for the time being. The agreed date has also yet to arrive, so we still can continue to wait and see."

Seeing that their boss did not intend to blame them, Law and Fay secretly sighed. The awe they had for the man in black robes permeated their very soul.

This guy was the leader of their Holy Accord organization. His name was unknown, and he went by the code name 'Oathkeeper'. He was the teacher of all the current Beyond Grade As in the organization.

Even during Law and Fay's childhood, Oathkeeper had been the leader of the organization. No one knew how long he had lived, and his strength was unfathomable. Even if the two had grown to the Beyond Grade A realm, they could not hope to put up a fight in the face of Oathkeeper.

At this moment, the anxious remote projection of an officer appeared next to them. "Your Excellency Oathkeeper, there's an abnormal reaction with the Destiny's Child!"

Whoosh!

The moment his words came out, Oathkeeper's figure vanished and reappeared the next moment within a secret sealed room.

Countless researchers dressed in lab coats were surrounding a cylindrical transparent container filled with dark blue liquid. A pale Primal Esper Ability Entity lay within, and its energy body maintained a human-like structure but without facial features, floating quietly within the liquid.

Oathkeeper turned to look at the scientific research team leader next to him and asked, "What happened?"

"The Destiny's Child Primal Esper Entity that was deep asleep suddenly released a state of information disturbance, breaking through the seals of the container and leaking out. We're currently calculating now how many sub-bodies have been created by its disturbance throughout the universe…" The team leader was nervously sweating.

"Sudden disturbance?" Oathkeeper paused. "You did not actively awaken it?"

"That's… that's right. We're monitoring it and recording as usual, and the disturbance suddenly occurred."

"Awaken it." Oathkeeper's voice was steely. "It must have received some stimulation that caused it to fluctuate."

The researchers could only comply, draining the liquid within the container. The Destiny's Child's humanoid shape immediately became blurry, as though it would disappear at any time.

"Increase its binding force field and the stability anchor. Don't let it completely enter the high-dimensional information state and break through containment." The scientific research personnel were sweating as they profusely worked.

Oathkeeper ignored the movement and put his hand on the outer wall of the container. His palm lit up in a cluster of flames, its color strange as it resembled a flickering starry sky. There was no temperature present, and it burned quietly, as though the world had no impact on it.

The Destiny's Child's body in the container was slowly attracted back and turned stable. It stretched out its hand curiously, pasting its palm where Oathkeeper's hand was through the transparent container wall.

At this time, Oathkeeper finally spoke.

"Tell me, what have you discovered?"

The Destiny's Child's tilted its head, and a wave of spiritual fluctuations bloomed. A childlike voice sounded in everyone's mind.

"Projection of an information state… new destiny… the call of The First Sanctum…"

Oathkeeper quietly listened before asking, "Is the agreed date still the same?"

"It's moved forward… by… ten years… twenty years…"

Oathkeeper deeply inhaled before commanding, "Inject the solution. Let it continue to sleep."

Everyone immediately followed his command, and the dark blue solution filled the container once more. The Destiny's Child seemed to struggle, but it quieted down in the end, falling into a deep sleep.

Glancing at the equipment, the research team leader could not help sighing. In the short amount of time that Destiny's Child was awake, the amplitude of information state disturbance increased by another 6.4%, which meant that a batch of unknown descendants within the universe would evolve.

While the Holy Accord had already gained control of the main body of Destiny's Child, because of its peculiarity, the Holy Accord had always used it with extreme caution.

Among the Primal Esper Ability Entities, Destiny's Child was a special existence. When it woke up and activated its abilities, it would produce a phenomenon called 'information state disturbance'. Random creatures in the universe would inexplicably awaken a weakened version of its abilities, which were mainly based on foresight. They were known as the children of Destiny's Child by the Holy Accord.

The appearance of the 'children' was irregular and not affected by time or space.

At this time, Law and Fay also hurried over.

"What's the situation now?"

Hearing them, Oathkeeper turned around and said, "There's a change of plans. The agreed date is almost upon us. I'll personally go and retrieve the Holy Light Particle."

"You're making a move‽"

Both of them were shocked.

Law hurriedly said, "It's too dangerous. Black Star is cunning and can fight. If anything happens to you, then we…"

Oathkeeper interrupted him in a low voice. "It's not a must to fight. I will discuss it with him. What we need is only a part of the Holy Light Particle… Similarly, we can take out the parts of other Primal Esper Entities to trade with him."

He patted the shoulders of the two, softly saying, "We've already gathered the key fragments needed to open The Third Sanctum, and only the fragment of the Primal Esper Ability Entity is left. While the ritual can be performed without the Holy Light Particle, it will bring about unknown risks. Since we've already prepared for so many years, it's best to eliminate any unstable factors possible, making this plan foolproof."

Chapter 1097: Sorry, the Party Does Whatever It Wants

Black Star Cup Competition Field Thirteen was a vast ring-shaped valley, like a naturally occurring colosseum, with rugged rocks and complex topography.

The auditorium was suspended in midair, and countless spectators looked down from the floating seats onto the battlefield. The various media groups were also broadcasting the situation in real time.

Pew!

Bang!

Suddenly, two fireballs fell from the sky, hitting the sides of the valley. Those were the airborne drop pods, and the friction between the atmosphere and its surface released such a high temperature that it caused the very air around it to warp.

Accompanied by the decompression of the sealed chambers, the doors of the two single person airborne pods opened, and two players walked out. One of them was Frenzied Sword, and the other was Hao Tian.

"All the best!"

The moment both of them appeared, the crowd went wild.

Frenzied Sword ignored the crazed spectators, unfolded a silvery white mechanical trident, and stared at Hao Tian. "I didn't expect us to meet so soon."

"It's a random draw. Anything can happen."

Hao Tian was wearing the special pugilist combat uniform that was produced by the army, warming up his hands and feet.

After more than a month of fierce battles, the Black Star Cup qualifiers had finally come to an end. Just like raising poisonous insects, more than ninety percent of the participants had been eliminated, and only the remaining elites entered the main race. However, Frenzied Sword and Hao Tian had met in the single player event of the Black Star Cup, becoming opponents.

Hao Tian was the pillar of the veteran professional players in the Long Sky club, but Frenzied Sword was the spokesperson for the up-and-coming Rivervale. As professional players, they both had a large number of fans, so today's match was highly anticipated.

Not only did the players pay attention to the competition between players, but even the NPCs were interested. The play styles of the players were often more radical and insane, making their fights enjoyable, which attracted a large number of NPC fans.

Pros such as Frenzied Sword and Hao Tian stood out among the tens of millions of players in the army, gaining a large number of NPC supporters. They were even given nicknames by the NPCs. Hao Tian had the title of 'Boxing Master', whereas Frenzied Sword had the title of 'Machinery Dancer'… It had to be said that their nicknames truly fitted their fighting styles.

Both of them were old friends, so they skipped the trash talk, going directly to the section of physical attacks.

Dang! Dang! Dang!

One was a Pugilist, the other a Mechanical Pugilist. The two figures quickly collided with each other, creating loud impact sounds and sparks.

Their shock waves from their fight created trenches on the ground, throwing up stone and dust high into the sky.

After four versions, both of their micro-manipulation skills had only become more sophisticated. With their current Grade B combat strength, they were already considered extremely destructive humanoid monsters in the eyes of ordinary people.

Bang!

The Mechanical Pugilist had numerous skills, so the offensive of Frenzied Sword was endless. His trident pierced the sky, creating phantoms, bringing up dazzling arcs to surround all the vital points of Hao Tian.

Hao Tian was on the backfoot as he continuously dodged, but he suddenly saw a chance, stopping and raising his hands to accurately grasp the two side blades of the trident.

The phantoms in the sky disappeared, and the edge of the trident was only twenty centimeters away from his face, but it would not budge any further.

Kacha kacha!

Both their arm muscles swelled as they entered a wrestling mode. The ground under their feet cracked, with lines snaking out from below them.

"Serpent Tongue's Cannon!" Frenzied Sword twisted his hands fiercely.

From within the center of the main blade on the trident, a dazzling energy ball suddenly emerged. It shot out a plasma arc cannon, but Hao Tian tilted his head to avoid it.

This beam of light shot diagonally upward, flashing past and penetrating a rocky mountain. It left behind a blazing red line that was completely melted through, and a layer of viscous magma seeped out.

Taking advantage of Frenzied Sword's sneak attack, Hao Tian raised his elbow, hitting the spear shaft and deflecting it to the side. He then unleashed a skill. Light accumulated under his feet as he slammed into Frenzied Sword's chest with a thunderous force, pushing him into the ground.

"War Trample!"

Boom!

The moment Frenzied Sword's back touched the ground, a shock wave radiated from him. The ground sank by dozens of centimeters, forming a semi-circular pit around him. All the stones around him were crushed into powder by the heavy pressure.

The remnant shock waves swept out along the ground, and the nearby mountain of rocks collapsed. A dust storm gathered, sweeping to the very corners of the battlefield, causing a ring of sand to billow out at the edges.

As his HP and armor's durability plummeted, Frenzied Sword straightened his waist, and the back of his mechanical suit transformed into a drill bit, digging into the ground to get rid of Hao Tian's smelly feet.

His figure broke out from the ground in the distance, the weapon in his hand replaced with a huge war axe. With a slash in the air, the force field generator attached to the edge of the axe produced an arc, radiating outward.

Plop…

With his Pugilist aura covering his arms, Hao Tian raised his hand to intercept the arc directly.

The deflected shocked wave flew up, hitting the bottom of a floating auditorium with a loud bang. Amid the excitement of the spectators, an ion shield in a honeycomb structure appeared to block the attack.

And among the excited spectators, there were two special envoys from the Federation of Light that were sitting in the front-row VIP seats. They were whispering to each other while recording the scene of Hao Tian fighting Frenzied Sword.

"The strength of the Immortals has increased yet again. Compared to their last disappearance, the increment is quite obvious. Excluding those Immortals in the budding stage, the earliest batch already have a stable Grade B combat capability."

"The Immortals have already undergone three periods of disturbance, and the duration is getting longer. Their way of increasing their strength is different to regular training, seemingly dependent on the length of time they disappear. By estimation, if they disappear once more, they might actually step into the Calamity Grade."

"This is really a terrible group of creatures…"

Thinking that there might be tens of millions of such immortal Calamity Grade lunatics within the universe in the future, the two special agents could not help but shudder.

Just thinking about it, it really could be considered a scourge.

With the increase in their strength, the players were also more valued by the advanced civilizations, and they gradually started to research the rules binding the players.

The three Universal Civilizations had also thought of recruiting the Immortals to act as suicide squads in the past, but at that time, the players were pretty weak. Thus, they did not take them seriously. Furthermore, their characteristics that made them disappear from time to time and their uncertain growth limit caused the three Universal Civilizations to hesitate.

But now, the growth cycle of the players had been proven, and the advanced civilizations had to consider the possibility of the Immortals entering the Calamity Grade realm. As such, they were willing to extend an olive branch to them, giving them better treatment.

Right now, the Black Star Army was the largest 'shareholder', sitting on tens of millions of Immortals, naturally inciting fear in many of the major organizations.

In the past, they mainly feared Black Star himself, but now, there were even more reasons for them to feel fear.

To them, the army was holding onto a lot of high-quality stock. If the Immortals could reach the Calamity Grade realm, the high-level combatants within the Black Star Army would instantly overwhelm even the three Universal Civilizations.

The unique attraction of the Black Star Army to the Immortals also surprised the advanced civilizations.

If it was not for the fact that Han Xiao did not have a habit of disappearing for extended periods, they would have simply assumed Han Xiao to be a part of the Immortals.

…

At this time, Han Xiao was far away back in his Black Star Palace, not paying attention to the competition, but rather watching the public trial of the dynasty.

The video showed the surface of a barren planet, where Traveler and another Beyond Grade A who was captured were bound and made to kneel on the execution platform, in a near-death state.

The two were in an extremely poor condition. Because of Clotti's dark energy circulating within their bodies, their regenerated cells were constantly being destroyed, keeping them in a severely injured state. The two had basically lost all their combat capabilities and were unable to break free.

Beside them, a remote projection of a dynasty officer stood in front of the camera, reading the decree out loud.

The content of the decree was the crimes of the two, such as crimes against public order, war crimes, and mass killings. All sorts of crimes were smashed onto their heads, making them seem as though they were heinous criminals that were wasting the very air in the universe.

What Han Xiao was concerned about were the charges the dynasty issued against Traveler, and as expected, the dynasty then mentioned what he wanted to hear.

"… Traveler has always operated as a neutral mercenary, but it has been verified that his true identity is that of the Beyond Grade A descendant that was secretly cultivated by the Modo Civilization. He tried to stir up disputes between the dynasty, the federation and the church, disrupting the order of the explored universe. At present, it is unknown if anyone part of the Modo Civilization orchestrated this matter, and the dynasty will retain an attitude to pursue accountability."

Hearing this, Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

"Humph, retaining an attitude to pursue accountability, how like the usual style of the three gangsters. It seems like the dynasty has already talked to Sorokin…"

He hypothesized that the Modo Civilization, which was originally lying back with popcorn to watch the show, would now have a stunned expression, as though struck silly by a pot that fell from the sky out of nowhere.

As for Traveler's true host civilization, the Star Arc Civilization, they would probably feel surprised and happy.

However, Han Xiao did not intend to keep Star Arc out of the matter like this. He summoned Phillip.

"Conceal your tracks. Anonymously send out a piece of information to the upper echelons of the Modo Civilization."

"What should I send, hum?"

"Reveal that the Star Arc Civilization is the real backer of Traveler."

Han Xiao evilly snickered.

In this manner, the bewildered Modo Civilization would think that their being made a scapegoat was the act of the Star Arc Civilization or that Traveler was being a rabid dog, going around biting people out of desperation.

As for whether or not the Modo Civilization believed in this, he did not care. Since he had provided a clue, the Modo Civilization would definitely find a way to verify it. With the Star Arc Civilization being the guilty party, regardless of whether the clue was checked, both sides would develop some grievances.

This would not only weaken the relationship between the Super Star Cluster Alliance but also earn Modo a new enemy. All he had to do was send a simple message.

The cost of doing things is low, so why not do it?

Tsk, I'm truly an evil person…

Han Xiao was in a good mood as he turned his attention back to the screen.

At this moment, the sentencing had come to an end, and the dynasty officers looked upright at the camera, solemnly speaking.

"… For the above crimes, the Crimson Dynasty has decided to issue a death sentence!"

After that, the remote projection disappeared, and suddenly, a gap was exposed at the foot of the execution platform, where a fist-sized device rose up.

This looked very familiar to Han Xiao, and his eyes flashed as he slowly whistled. "The Universal Treasure of the dynasty, the Key of Destruction…"

At this moment, the surface of the Key of Destruction lit up in a matrix-like energy loop, and a circle of spatial channels suddenly appeared, unfolding in front of the two.

At the other end of the passage were the long-distance cannon rays of the dynasty's army, filling the area with a dazzling glare.

Boom!

The next moment, a world-destroying energy surged out, filling every inch of the screen!

The picture panned out rapidly, turning into a wide-area perspective which overlooked the planet from the distant starry sky.

One could only see a glimmer of bright light blooming on the surface of the planet, followed by a dazzling star-like energy cluster, which expanded rapidly and in turn wrapped the planet in it.

As the energy cluster expanded to its limit, all of a sudden, the huge ball shrank to a point, like the image when an old-fashioned television was turned off.

Within the picture, the explosion site was totally empty, with the planet having disappeared without a trace, completely annihilated.

Traveler and the other Beyond Grade A who were already at death's door had no power to resist the Key of Destruction, and not even their bones remained.

What a waste…

Han Xiao's mouth contorted slightly.

In order to pull off this huge affair, the dynasty had deliberately chosen to utilize the cannons, pulling down a planet together with both of them. It was a pity that the bodies of the two were extremely rare research materials.

They were indeed a Universal Civilization. After so many years, they probably had a sizable collection of Beyond Grade A corpses within their freezer, so they had no need for more…

While Traveler was an enemy, seeing another Beyond Grade A being executed by a Universal Civilization still left Han Xiao a little depressed. He estimated that the other Beyond Grade As would also feel the same way.

Sigh, no matter how big a universe is, it cannot exceed the size of ambition. It's difficult for the two parties to have a harmonious existence… In the face of the advanced civilizations, the Beyond Grade As are still in a weak position, and there are too few of us…

Thinking about the situation of the Beyond Grade As, Han Xiao sighed.

Just as he was about to turn off his broadcasting screen, he noticed a strange mental fluctuation through his senses.

"Who are you‽"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, snapping his head to look at the center of the room. His eyes sparkled with Mechanical Force as he instantly entered a combat state.

Within his vision, black flames were suddenly borne out of thin air, converging into the appearance of the Holy Accord's leader, Oathkeeper.

Oathkeeper lightly stepped on the group, walking toward Han Xiao as he spoke.

"Black Star, there's no need to be nervous. This is just a mental projection without any sort of combat capability. I came here specially to meet you. It's good to see you. I would like to propose a deal with you."

"You…"

Hearing this, Han Xiao furrowed his brows, sizing him up before speaking in an uncertain tone.

"… Are the Holy Accord's leader?"

As he spoke, Oathkeeper stumbled and very nearly hit his head.

Hidden under his hood was a dumbfounded expression.

F*ck me, how do you even know this‽

Chapter 1098: There Must Be a Traitor!

How does Black Star know my identity‽

Oathkeeper originally wanted to show off his Beyond Grade A strength, attracting Black Star's attention before negotiating a deal. He did not expect that the moment he appeared, he would be exposed without any preparation. Thus, his act of being mysterious failed.

Seeing Black Star recognize him at a glance, Oathkeeper went through a storm of emotions at once.

Where did he receive intelligence about me? What has been leaked within the organization, to the point that he even knows of my name‽

A series of question marks popped up in his mind, and Oathkeeper's mood suddenly turned heavy.

The Holy Accord had always been hidden in the dark as they had too many secrets. Now that Black Star could call out his identity, how much exactly did he know about the Holy Accord? Did he also learn of their ultimate mission?

As this thought flashed through his mind, he suddenly felt killing intent, wanting to silence the other party.

However, this murderous intent was forcibly suppressed by him.

There was no other reason than the fact that Black Star was too strong.

This sort of meat-shield like pinnacle Beyond Grade A could not easily be killed. The use of force should be a final resort, and negotiations should take priority.

This was the good point in having great strength, as it would make people more reasonable toward them.

I'll first test how much Black Star knows. If he understands the basics of the Holy Accord, then I'll have to calculate and plan accordingly. After so many years of planning, I cannot take any risks…

Suppressing his inner shock, Oathkeeper adjusted his emotions. He did not proceed with negotiations; the most important thing to him now was to test Black Star.

Oathkeeper slowly sat down opposite Han Xiao, whispering, "Do you understand a lot about the Holy Accord?"

"Not much, just the slightest bit."

Han Xiao made a gesture, leaving the slightest gap between his thumb and forefinger, his smile full of meaning. He had on an expression that seemed to say, "I have seen through everything."

In reality, the Great Mechanic Han really only knew a little about the Holy Accord. He only knew that they resurrected a great number of the Primordial Ones in the later versions but not the inside story. It could be said that he only knew what the Holy Accord's behavior would be but not their intentions.

He only recognized Oathkeeper because Oathkeeper was still the leader of the Holy Accord even in the later versions, and he had received great attention during the World Tree Civilization War. Han Xiao did not know of his origin either.

Thus, Han Xiao only put on this posture of 'I know it in my heart' just to fool the other party, not allowing Oathkeeper to figure out his bottom line.

Seeing this, Oathkeeper was uncertain in his heart, but on the surface, he remained expressionless, softly asking, "I'm curious, but how did you recognize me? Have we met before?"

"That's right."

"Is it…" Oathkeeper got a shock, immediately racking his brains to try and remember when he had dealings with Black Star. But no matter how hard he thought, he could not discover anything.

At this moment, Han Xiao spoke with a straight face. "We met before in our dreams."

Oathkeeper did not know how to respond.

Are you talking about your mom?

Black Star was obviously making a joke, but in the eyes of Oathkeeper, his attitude meant that Black Star knew a lot more than he let on, thus his mood got more solemn, causing him to over-imagine.

"Let's not talk about this for now." Han Xiao waved his hand, squinting. "You just said you wish to make a deal with me. Let me first hear what it is."

Oathkeeper sorted out his mood, temporarily putting aside his thought of testing him. "I wish to make an exchange for a part of the Holy Light Particle."

"Oh?" Han Xiao glanced at him. "What can you offer me then?"

"It depends on what you want. We're willing to use other Primal Energy Entities to trade for your Holy Light Particle."

So, it turns out that the Holy Accord wished to obtain the Holy Light Particle through negotiations. This should be how they cooperated with the EsGod in my previous life. My plan of luring the snake out of its hole really worked, Han Xiao secretly thought.

By publicly stating that the Holy Light Particles were in his own hands, he wanted to lure the Holy Accord into making contact with him. According to his judgement, after the last sneak attack, they would either attack him again or perform a trade in exchange for the Holy Light Particle. Either way, the Holy Accord would be fished out.

If the Holy Accord remained in the dark, Han Xiao would not be able to find them, and it was detrimental to him. Now that there was an opportunity for dialogue, there would be room for manipulation.

Han Xiao pretended to ponder for a while before tapping on the table with his finger, suddenly changing the topic.

"If I remember correctly, you guys just snatched the pp… cough, I mean, a portion of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy from my hands a while ago."

Indeed, Black Star knows that the people who attacked him before belonged to the Holy Accord…

Oathkeeper suddenly realized a crucial factor.

Did Black Star only learn of their organization after being attacked, or did he already know of their existence even before he was attacked?

There was a difference!

"Are you sure that the people who attacked you the last time belonged to the Holy Accord?" Oathkeeper tested him.

"Huh, want to deny it? Did you think I wouldn't recognize you if you only sent your peripheral members?" Han Xiao stroked his chin and spoke in a playful tone. "Dimensional Exile Bullets, Formatted Viruses, High-Level Life Form Energy Disorder Shockwave—all these are things that your Holy Accord is famed for. Did you think I was unaware?"

Under his hood, Oathkeeper's face turned gloomy.

The facts had proven that what Black Star knew exceeded his own imagination, and he had long known of the existence of the Holy Accord!

The Holy Accord had obtained that technology as a result of researching the Primal Esper Ability Entities. They were all their killing moves that they rarely used. For Black Star to even call out the names of these techniques, there was only one possibility left…

There was a traitor in the organization!

Furthermore, it was someone in the upper echelons!

The faces of the various officers flashed through Oathkeeper's mind in anger.

Who was it that broke through the limits of the Soul Flame, betraying their organization‽

Even Black Star knew about this, so how much intelligence had been leaked? Could it be that, within the vaults of the advanced civilizations, there were already a multitude of files and folders on their Holy Accord?

If that was the case, then the Holy Accord that prided itself on keeping its secrets for so many years had basically turned into the laughingstock of the entire universe!

Oathkeeper's mentality exploded in an instant.

He was someone who remained mostly stoic and calm, but the mental stress he had suffered that day was just overwhelming, causing him to lose control of his emotions.

Feeling the unstable mental fluctuations of Oathkeeper, Han Xiao hesitated.

It seemed like he had gone overboard with his acting and scared the other party quite terribly.

Han Xiao sighed empathetically.

Alas, these brainiacs focused heavily on their intelligence, so they were naturally suspicious all the time. A little detail would cause them to constantly focus on it. It was not because he had gone overboard but rather because the other party was just too sensitive.

In fact, Han Xiao objectively viewed the Holy Accord quite neutrally. He had no good feelings or grievances toward them. In his previous life, the Holy Accord Organization was not a villainous organization that created trouble, nor did they produce any pests. The only well-known incident that involved them was the revival of the Beyond Grade As and Primordial Ones from history, which involved some unknown method during the World Tree War.

While the Holy Accord's participation in the war was mainly due to them being next in line if the Universal Civilizations fell, they contributed a lot to the World Tree War and brought about a wave of important reinforcements. Credit still had to be awarded where due.

In this regard, Han Xiao stood on the same side as them. The revival of the Beyond Grade As in history would instantly enhance the combat power of the Beyond Grade As in the explored universe, such that there would be more bargaining chips against the World Tree. He would not stop the Holy Accord from achieving its goals.

That being said, the Holy Accord attacked him without being provoked, so Han Xiao had already made a mental note of this. Let them hit him for free, how could there be such a good thing in this world? Without settling the score, he would not let them go.

As for whether or not the revival of the Primordial Ones was related to the Holy Accord, Han Xiao could not be sure, but he wholly suspected that their excuse of surviving in the life-sustaining cabins was fake news.

In fact, he could understand why the revival of the Primordial Ones would be an important fuse leading to the Calamity of the Supers. Just think about it from the perspective of the three Universal Civilizations…

F*ck me, you guys that were supposed to be dead have revived‽ Then, does that mean every Beyond Grade A that died will also be eligible for revival? If the number of people revived grows to the certain point that can overthrow our rule, what are we supposed to do‽

The advanced civilizations had always attempted to control the ratio of individual might to collective strength. To suddenly discover that the individual might could now be resurrected and that they were no longer in control of the situation, their mentality would definitely burst.

Thus, regardless of whether the Primordial Ones were awakened from cryostasis or resurrected, they would have to say to the outside that they had been lying within the life sustaining capsules, otherwise the problem would only get worse, and there was no knowing what the three Universal Civilizations would end up doing.

As both of them were engrossed in their thoughts, it took a while before they realized they were still in a conversation.

Oathkeeper calmed himself down before solemnly speaking.

"I can provide compensation as a form of apology. I hope that you can forgive the negligence of my subordinates."

"How are you going to compensate me for my mental loss?"

"What do you want?"

"Hmm, let me think about it…" Han Xiao held his head. "With the long history of the Holy Accord, there should be a lot of things in your vaults. If you hand me eight to ten Universal Treasures or blueprints, I'll forgive them."

Why don't you go and rob… oh, no, you are indeed robbing me right now.

Oathkeeper immediately shook his head.

"That's too many. We don't have that much in stock."

"How could this be?" Han Xiao chuckled. "There are so many of your members who are descendants of Beyond Grade As, so how could their ancestors not leave behind any heirlooms?"

You even know of this‽

Just how much intelligence was leaked!

Oathkeeper secretly gritted his teeth. His only thought was digging up the traitor and beating him to death.

"… In any case, we really don't have that many Universal Treasures. We only have two sets of blueprints that we've accumulated, and we can compensate you with those."

"Two sets…" Han Xiao pursed his lips. "Seems a little lacking. How about you pass me a set of your Esper Ability Technology well?"

"Not possible!" Oathkeeper spat out with a steely tone. He would not compromise at all on this matter.

Forget it, two sets then. At least I got something out of this.

Taking the pp of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and exchanging it for two sets of Gold Grade blueprints, this was akin to giving up one… no, giving up nothing in exchange for a plethora of benefits.

Han Xiao then clicked his tongue as his expression got serious. Placing his hands on the desk, he slowly said, "We can proceed with this deal, but the portion of Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy that you guys stole must be included in the terms, treated as though I'm also selling it to you. This means that you have to offer me two portions of separate Primal Esper Ability Entities in exchange for a portion of the Holy Light Particle."

Since his [Primal Esper Ability Collector] mission only required another two Primal Esper Ability Entities, then he could utilize the Holy Light Particle to complete it. This would net him a milestone halo geared toward fighting Espers, as well as a skill fragment of [The Third Sanctum].

"Deal." Oathkeeper decisively nodded.

The Holy Accord organization had already amassed a large number of Primal Esper Ability Entities, and cutting a few pieces of them to put for sale was not a problem.

While such a style was quite perverted, none of them were actually good people, so there was no need to be worried about such a thing.

With the Black Star Army now dominating a part of the universe, Oathkeeper could only settle for the bare minimum. While he was not afraid of Black Star, it was still better to settle things peacefully where possible.

At this moment, Oathkeeper's eyes flashed as he probed, "Black Star, what do you think about the purpose of our Holy Accord?"

While a lot of intelligence had been leaked, Oathkeeper still held on to the last embers of hope. It might seem that Black Star knew everything about the organization, but there was still a small chance that he was unaware of their primary objective.

"Purpose? Aren't you just an organization that researches about Primal Esper Ability Technology? What, you still have other schemes in mind?" Han Xiao raised a brow.

Oathkeeper closely peered at Han Xiao's expression, but he could not read anything. He did not know if Han Xiao truly was unaware or was merely pretending.

But no matter what, he could not help but breathe a sigh of relief upon hearing this answer.

Black Star was unaware of their primary objective, which meant that the external variables were still within their scope of control. This meant that the traitor in their organization was just at the officer level, not part of the core.

"There are no conspiracies nor schemes. The purpose of our organization is to believe that Esper Abilities have infinite possibilities, which can bring about technological breakthroughs to the universe…" Oathkeeper began to spew some nonsense, which was the same information they told their peripheral members as camouflage.

After a few more idle sentences, they set a time for the transaction, before Oathkeeper left, full of thoughts of weeding out the 'traitor' in his organization.

Han Xiao leaned back with an expression of deep thought.

He did not provoke the other party's intention to revive the Beyond Grade As in history. This was because he did not know what the other party was using to do so or what their objective was. Revealing this fact too early might cause him to be targeted instead.

Thus, he pretended and fooled around for a bit, but if he went overboard, he might have no way to retreat in the end.

At least before he obtained the blueprints and the other two Primal Esper Ability Entities, he had no desire to rip off all pretenses with the Holy Accord.

Moreover, Han Xiao did not mind the revival of the Beyond Grade As. Compared to the World Tree, the impact of this on the universe was just a small matter. Every bit of extra strength was good.

In my previous life, the Holy Accord worked with EsGod, but now I have replaced EsGod as their partner and became the driving force behind the scenes. Under my influence, the plot line is changing more and more. There are even the coordinates that lead to the World Tree. The logistics department has been unsuccessful in deriving them, and I don't know how far the dynasty's research has gone…

Han Xiao was lost in thought before he recalled something.

That's right, the Holy Accord has such a long history. Maybe they have intelligence about the existence of the Sanctums. I should find a chance to ask them next time.

Somewhere in the Ancient Star Desert, the galactic pirates' fleet was stopped by three small battleships with the Federation of Light insignia. After a fierce battle, the pirates were captured.

On the deck of the pirates' flagship, the carbonized corpse of the leader fell on the ground, while all the other members squatted on the ground with the hands on their heads, covered in cuts and bruises. They were surrounded by a group of soldiers in brilliant Federation of Light uniforms.

The leader of the soldiers was wearing a high-tech uniform, with a badge on his chest, representing his position as a universe inspector.

This universe inspector was part of a special department set up by the advanced civilizations. They patrolled different Star Systems, and their official position was higher than that of an ordinary patrol officer, specializing in detection of abnormal conditions.

The Federation of Light Inspector paced in front of the group of pirates, slowly taking off his bloodied black gloves. He slowly said, "Five days ago, there were signs of cosmic energy surges coming from your spaceship. The energy fluctuations spread along as you travelled, alarming many advanced civilizations, including the three Universal Civilizations. This fluctuation has never been seen before, and no one knows what it is…"

Pa!

He suddenly walked up to one of the pirates, slapping him before forcing his gaze to meet his. "Can you tell me what exactly happened?"

"It… it was a disposable safe…" The pirate stammered before revealing everything.

"An ancient safe that was sold at an auction?"

The Federation of Light inspector called up the information that they had obtained from the pirates, and Harrison's team information appeared on his screen.

"A group of scavengers. Not sure if they're lucky or unlucky…"

Narrowing his eyes, he pushed the pirate aside before giving his command.

"Move out. Find these people!"

Chapter 1099: Interfering with Reality, Latent Crisis

The inspectors of the three Universal Civilizations had huge backers and vast resources at their disposal. It was not difficult to uncover a low-level scavenger.

The process was quite smooth. It could be summarized as: identity record match, whereabouts position, storming the area, and asking them to line up with their hands on the wall.

This series of operations was smoothly carried out, as though they had done it hundreds of times.

In the small spaceship of the scavengers, Harrison and his party squatted on the wall and shivered. The brilliant Federation of Light insignias on the soldiers' uniforms dispelled any desire to resist.

For people at the bottom of the Galactic Society, even a small pawn of the three Universal Civilizations was not someone they could afford to offend. Without the backing of any organization, those that dared to offend people from the three Universal Civilizations were akin to people who would turn the lights on in the latrine to look at sh*t.

"You… What are you guys trying to do? We, we are law-abiding citizens," the shortie stammered.

The Federation of Light Inspector moved a chair, sitting in front of this group. He leaned forward, releasing an aura of oppression as he coldly said, "You don't know what sort of crimes you've committed?"

What crime have we committed?

Everyone had a confused expression, squeezing their brain juices dry to try and remember what they had done in their daily lives.

The shortie suddenly shivered violently before blurting out, "I… I surrender!"

"Oh?" The inspector turned to look at him, narrowing his eyes as he said, "Say it then. What is your crime?"

"I… I anonymously hacked the paid server of an adult entertainment channel yesterday, downloading thousands of pornos… ahem, you know, those kinds of films. I'm guilty! I confess!" The shortie spat everything out.

The captain suddenly exclaimed, "No wonder you stayed in your room the whole day yesterday…"

As he spoke, he suddenly stopped. Everyone realized that the shortie was still wearing his clothes from the day before, and with a wrinkle of their noses, they shifted a few paces away from him.

"…"

The inspector's facial expression was hard as steel, but if one looked closely, they could see the corners of his mouth twitching fiercely.

Be serious, I'm interrogating you!

"Are you trying to provoke me? Do you think I'm joking with you‽"

Glaring at him, the inspector drew his gun, pressing it against the head of the shortie. However, he paused suddenly and withdrew the muzzle a distance away from the guy's head. He did not dare stick it to the skin of the shortie for fear of contaminating his firearm.

"Don't, don't, don't, don't…" The shortie was so scared that he urinated on the spot, his entire body trembling.

Harrison was also frightened and immediately said, "Sir Inspector, we're law abiding. We don't pillage and kill; we only excavate ownerless ruins. We do not know what crimes we've committed."

"Humph!" The inspector also did not intend to make their lives difficult. He withdrew his weapon, projecting an image of the triangular device. He solemnly said, "Not long ago, you guys dug out this artifact from an unknown civilization and put it up for auction. But it was stolen by the galactic pirates, and when they opened it up, it triggered a cosmic energy fluctuation. I'm here for this."

Harrison's heart almost stopped.

See, we got into trouble!

My intuition was right. This object isn't simple, even bringing me so much trouble after it was sold!

However, he was not upset but instead felt a sense of excitement from his bones. A strong curiosity surged within him, and he could not help but ask, "What was inside?"

"It's still unclear, and the specific fluctuations are still being thoroughly investigated."

At this moment, the captain could not help but ask, "Wait a minute, we sold that thing, and it wasn't us who opened it, so what crime have we committed?"

"That's right. We're innocent!"

"You can't frame good people for nothing!"

The crowd immediately screamed, displaying upright indignation.

"Shut up!" the Inspector coldly barked. "The items that you dug up from the ruins carry a strong risk. Because of you guys, new disasters are likely to occur in the universe. Let's not talk about anything else. Just the crime of endangering public safety is enough to put you in prison!"

Hearing this, everyone immediately shrank back, and they collectively lowered their heads, attentively counting the number of ants on the floor… although there was no chance of ants appearing in the spaceship.

The inspector coldly snorted. "However, if you guys are willing to assist us in our work, we can ignore your unintentional mistakes. We are going to investigate the site of the ruins now, and we need you to lead the way and show us your flight log. Are there any objections?"

"No, no, no, none at all. It is our honor to help the Federation of Light! I'm the machinery expert of this spaceship. You just need to give the command if you need something from me. There's no need to treat me like a person at all!"

Seeing that the situation was not as serious as expected, the shortie breathed a sigh of relief before hurriedly using the skills he had honed over the years to bootlick the inspector.

"This…" The captain was a little hesitant. "Is this going to leave us with a criminal record?"

The inspector seemed to take it lightly. "That's for sure, but it doesn't matter. As long as you turn in whatever you've dug up in the future to the civilization, there will be no problem."

Give it to the nation? Are we going to turn into an archaeological team‽

Too much, this is simply threatening us with our weaknesses. You want us to compromise? Dream on! We absolutely will not accept such a treatment!

… Unless the Federation of Light is paying us wages.

After reaching a physical consensus, the team led the way, quickly bringing the inspector to the barren planet where they first found the triangular device, and found the initial coordinates.

Harrison pointed at the image on the screen as he explained, "This is the place. There used to be a ruin here that resembled something like a military base, but the moment we left, it collapsed. This is a recording of when we burrowed in…"

The Federation of Light inspector nodded and ordered his subordinates to descend, taking out the probes to scan the area. His expression changed slightly.

He did not expect that the results of the investigation would show that there were no abnormalities present within the rock formations. There was only mud and dirt.

This made no sense, as even if the ruins were to collapse and be buried, there should be traces. However, in the pictures of these advanced detection instruments, there were no traces in the rocks below.

The inspector frowned. "Are you sure it's here?"

"That's here alright. You've also seen the flight logs. We stopped right here." Harrison showed an expression of surprise as well.

Such a mystical scenario hooked his curiosity once again. He was unable to understand how the ruins could just disappear into thin air.

Could it be that this whole thing was a dream? But the safe they unearthed was well and truly present.

Just as he was thinking about it, the inspector from the Federation of Light seemed to have thought of something. His expression changed as he muttered to himself, "Such a phenomenon, could it be… that it's the high-dimensional information state interfering with reality itself?"

Harrison was just about to ask something, but he saw the inspector push aside everyone, running to report to his superior.

Seeing the other party's grave expression, Harrison had a hunch that the severity of this problem was beyond his own imagination.

…

Within the base of the Holy Accord Organization, Law and Fay were summoned, and once again, they arrived in the dark palace to meet up with Oathkeeper.

"All of you are here."

In midair, the figure of Oathkeeper materialized, and he lowered his head to indifferently speak, his tone laced with coldness.

There was a strong mental fluctuation within his tone, which caused Law and Fay to begin to feel anxious.

Both of them had known Oathkeeper for a long time, so they understood his behavior. Such an action meant that he was truly angered, which had not happened in a long time.

They could not help but exchange glances, communicating with their eyes.

Law (Puzzled Look): "The leader's mood doesn't seem too good."

Fay (Blinking): "Maybe he failed in the negotiations with Black Star."

Law (Frowning): "That wouldn't make him so angered. There should be another reason."

Fay (Curious Look): "Then what is it?"

Law (Rolling eyes): "Do you think I can explain such a complicated thing using just glances?"

Fay (Blinking Innocently): "That makes sense."

Both of them conversed in an instant before lowering their heads to greet Oathkeeper. "Leader, for what matter have you summoned us?"

"Black Star has inside information on us!" Oathkeeper furiously replied.

"What‽" Both of them paled.

Could it be that because of their ambush previously, Black Star had managed to uncover some clues, which lead to a leakage of their organizational intelligence?

If that was the case, then the both of them were sinners!

Did the leader specifically call us over to punish us? That's right. It's most likely that!

Having assumed their leader's attitude, both of them were in a panic and did not dare hesitate, immediately lowering their heads to plead. "It's our fault. We've committed a great sin by causing our organization's information to leak out. Please punish us!"

Glancing at the two, Oathkeeper relaxed his tone.

"Don't be mistaken. Your actions do not have anything to do with this matter. Black Star has long known of our organization's existence."

Hearing this, the two of them could not help but exchange a glance in shock.

If it's not us that revealed the intel, then who was it? It was definitely our first time in contact with Black Star. Could it be that some others had also come into contact with him in the past?

At this moment, the frosty voice of Oathkeeper answered their question.

"Stop guessing. Our organization has a traitor!"

"That's impossible!" Law shook in fright, exclaiming with an incredulous expression. "Those who leak intelligence will definitely suffer backlash from the Soul Flames. Who would survive that‽"

The Soul Flame was another Primal Esper Ability Entity. As its name suggested, this ability was related toward one's soul and spirit, and currently, Oathkeeper was its host.

Its Esper Ability meant that it was an expert that toyed with the soul aspect of people, making it one of the Super High Risk Esper Abilities. One of its abilities allowed it to prohibit its target from revealing specific information, and Oathkeeper had utilized this ability to prevent anyone in the Holy Accord from leaking its secrets. If a member wished to forcibly divulge information, even if they could endure the backlash, Oathkeeper would still be notified. This was how the Holy Accord had kept its secrecy for so long.

He used his own pinnacle Beyond Grade A strength to spur the Esper Ability of the Soul Flame, so the effect exerted was terrifying. Even Law and Fay, two Beyond Grade As, would not be able to bypass its surveillance and would also suffer backlash if they leaked any information.

Thus, both of them believed that no one could betray their organization.

"Whether you believe it or not, the fact is in front of our eyes. Black Star identified me the moment he saw me, and I was still foolishly believing that no one else knew about the existence of our Holy Accord. This matter must be investigated carefully!"

Oathkeeper's tone was steely as he shouted.

"There should be someone who has come out with a special method to bypass the surveillance and backlash caused by the Soul Flame. They passed on intelligence to the outside world. The person's rank is not low either, at least an officer within the organization. For now, I still do not know if they are a core member."

Both Law and Fay's expressions turned grim. This matter was related to the survival of their organization and could not be taken lightly.

"Leader, what would you have us do?"

"Both of you are my confidantes, and I believe you in principle. However, everything depends on evidence, so I need to scan your memories. Are you willing?"

Law and Fay were suddenly placed in a difficult situation. While they were not betrayers, any Super would naturally repel others from invading their own mind deep within themselves.

However, they were aware of the increasingly unstable mental fluctuations around them. Thus, both of them swallowed hard, and in order to show that they had a clear conscience, they agreed with difficulty.

The next moment, Oathkeeper raised his hand slightly, and two streaks of flames the color of the starry sky landed on them.

Both of them noticed a unique mental fluctuation entering their brains. Looking at each other, they gritted their teeth before actively letting go of their mental barriers, allowing Oathkeeper to easily penetrate their minds.

Their memories were quickly flipped through by him. The scenes from small to large flashed in front of them. They gritted their teeth, ignoring the tingling sensation of the mental probe as it scanned through their minds.

After a long while, the mental probes were finally recalled back to Oathkeeper who seemed satisfied.

"Very good, the two of you did not let down my expectations." Oathkeeper nodded before continuing solemnly. "I'll leave the task of weeding out the traitor to you guys. I allow you full access to thoroughly investigate all the organization officers and report any suspicious personnel to me. I'll personally scan their memories. Before we can uncover the traitor, we'll temporarily stop all activities and go into hiding."

Both of them remained silent, nodding to signify acceptance as they suffered through the throbbing pain that was a side effect from the mental probes. They could not help but sigh.

It seems like the leader is truly enraged this time. If even us confidantes are treated this way, there's no need to talk about the other officers…

Both of them could foresee that this operation would definitely create a lot of havoc within the organization.

…

The explosion of cosmic energy could not escape the monitoring buoys that were set by the advanced civilizations. These monitoring buoys were used by each advanced civilization to monitor the situation within their jurisdictions, and they were pervasive.

It was just that the qualifications for setting up monitoring buoys were generally reserved for civilizations, and civil organizations were rarely allowed.

Within the Ancient Star Desert, the branch of the Black Star Army did not have much influence, and it naturally did not have the right to set any up. Han Xiao was also far away and could not immediately discover the cosmic energy fluctuations.

The advanced civilizations reacted quickly to investigate the source and impact of the phenomenon but found next to nothing. They did not know what sort of changes this energy surge would create.

Right at this moment, within the quantum network that was invisible to the naked eye, the information packets released from the triangular device were spreading rapidly within the Ancient Star Desert's domain.

This sort of information packet had incredible camouflage abilities, able to bypass most artificial intelligence firewalls and infect one quantum network node after another. It spread like a virus, but for the time being, it did not show any abnormal reaction, simply lurking beneath the surface.

Only a small number of artificial intelligences, such as the master artificial intelligences from the advanced civilizations, were able to detect and stop it. However, as soon as it was discovered, the information packet would immediately activate a self-destruction program, shattering and deleting its own data, at the same time marking the firewall that it could not break through so other information packets would not take the same risk. It was as though there was a program within that commanded it to avoid those that were overly strong.

As the scope of infection expanded, the efficiency of transmission also increased proportionally. Within the quantum network, transmission was not affected by distance, so without anyone knowing, massive numbers of quantum network nodes in the Ancient Star Desert domain were infected.

At some point, an information packet was transmitted to another quantum node, but this time, it ran into the strongest artificial intelligence firewall it had ever encountered. The moment it entered the peripheral surroundings of the node, it was scanned, and the information packet immediately blew itself up.

However, a surging data stream gushed out from this node to envelop the information packet. When it had self-destructed about sixty-five percent of itself, the remaining fragmented information was forcibly intercepted.

The next moment, the data streams converged into a human shape.

Manison's Virtual Soul gazed at the remains of the information packet floating in front of him with a curious expression.

Eh, a never-before-seen data structure… what's this thing, attempting to infiltrate my sub-base?

Chapter 1100: Prematurely Triggered Disaster Event

In the Central Galaxy was the Abyss of Stars, the home of the Federation of Light's headquarters.

The duty of an inspector was different from that of a secret intelligence department. The former acted as a pan-universal intelligence agency and did not involve itself in the political battles of the advanced civilizations. Most of the time, the intelligence agencies of the three Universal Civilizations would cooperate to deal with various special phenomena, including monitoring and tracking to prevent possible disasters.

At this very moment, in a conference room within this particular agency, a group of high-level executives sat around a round table, discussing the emergency reported from the Ancient Star Desert branch inspector.

The explosion of cosmic energy was considered a red alert at any time and required a meeting to be convened to discuss the strategy taken.

"The content of the report is quite detailed, and the cause and effect were quite clearly outlined. A scavenger team dug up a safe of an unknown civilization, releasing the source of this incident. This belongs to the second category of accidents. However, the traces of the ruins excavated completely disappeared before the inspector's team's field survey began, and they suspect it has something to do with a projection of a high-dimensional information state interfering with reality… The most important questions now are, what exactly did it release, why was there a cosmic energy burst, and what impact would this have?"

A humanoid creature who looked sickly at first glance was speaking. When he spoke, he stood up tall and thin, resembling a bamboo stick. His skin color was pale purple, with white lines, and his eyes were long and narrow, with yellow pupils.

This was Sidreun 'Purple Fire' Korna, the highest officer from the inspectorate from the Federation of Light's side, a Beyond Grade A seed. He was a hybrid of races, but his main bloodline came from the Deweine tribe, a racial species with superior racial talents.

The Federation of Light employed a multi-racial living system, and hybrids were an important part of their nation.

Due to the difference in beliefs, preferences, appearances, and other factors delineating each race, racial issues had always been a deeply rooted disease in the federation, but everyone was already used to it.

"These archaeological teams never learn their lesson," a member grumbled. "Of the various universal disasters in history, be it an organic extinct virus, mutated monsters, or anything else, how many of them were caused by digging up ancient relics?"

"You can't put it that way. Many of our technology in the early years was also derived from the reverse engineering of ancient civilizations. Besides, compared to the triggering of disasters due to advanced technology going out of control or the invasion of foreign enemies, the severity caused by archaeology pales in comparison." Sidreun shook his head weakly.

At this time, one of the executives glanced through the past records and muttered, "By the way, it's quite rare for high-dimensional information states to interfere with reality itself in the past, but with the increase in the exploration of the universe, this phenomenon seems to have become more frequent.

"According to the statistics provided by our predecessors, during the exploration era, the average number of information state interferences was around 467 times a year, which only counts those events that were discovered and recorded. In the past century though, this number has risen to 2,150 per year, almost five times the number. Although this could be attributed to the improvement in our detection methods, it can also be seen as an increase in the frequency of interferences as well."

"Information states have always been an important research direction of the advanced civilizations. We are only responsible for the submission of reports. Regardless of the result, that is a problem for our scientists, not us." Sidreun waved his hand tiredly with an obvious lack of interest.

It was understandable that he was mentally weary after sitting in his position. This inspectorate department was responsible for wiping the backsides of people all over the universe, akin to watching a group of crazy kids making trouble everywhere for him to clean up afterward.

No matter how he tried to remedy things, countless more would still appear the next day. If he had a bad temper, he would have exploded in fury at least once a day in this department.

Thus, with the passing of time, a man would turn into Buddha, whereas fish would also become salted and preserved[1].

Everybody here did not come from a research background, so they had a limited understanding of the causes of information state projection and interference. To them, this phenomenon was akin to a special mirage, and the difference was that this was not limited by time and space and could really interfere with the real world.

Another of the executives said, "After comparison, the unknown text that the scavengers submitted does not have a match in our database to any civilization. If this is an information state projection, then the source is either from an extremely ancient civilization, or it's from unexplored civilizations that exist somewhere in the universe."

While the three Universal Civilizations were the undisputed universe hegemons today, they were not omniscient nor omnipotent. They did not know what had existed in the past, nor did they know how many civilizations there were in the unexplored universe. Thus, they had not stopped their pace of exploration and research.

"Did anyone discover any negative effects?" Sidreun questioned.

"For the time being, no. The specific details are still under thorough investigation. At present, it is impossible to predict what sort of disaster this is. Maybe it's not even a disaster."

Everyone shook their head.

At this moment, a voice sounded.

"This is a disaster within the Virtual Domain."

The hologram in the center of the round table suddenly transformed into the face of Manison.

Seeing this, everyone went into an uproar.

"Mechanic Emperor Manison!" Sidreun's expression sank, and he shouted, "How dare you infiltrate the network of an official institution!"

Everyone on scene had an ugly expression as Manison had just too many criminal convictions. Even his ally, the Federation of Light, guarded their official networks against Manison, for fear that all their confidential information would be stolen by this neighbor of theirs.

There was a saying in the universe—One cannot expect a Virtual Mechanic to have morals.

They were like the bosses behind the scenes in the casino, and it was in their nature to peek at the cards of others.

"It's not the first time. Why are you all so surprised?" Manison was perfectly calm. "This time, however, I'm here to deliver some intelligence."

"I don't believe you!" Sidreun gritted his teeth. You obviously could knock on the door, but you chose to come in through the window instead. Would it kill you to send out an official notice?

"This method is faster. I don't like to wait." Manison continued as though he heard nothing. "Furthermore, this disaster is currently fermenting. Every second wasted means increased damage."

Hearing this, Sidreun temporarily suppressed his anger, frowning as he asked, "So, what have you spotted?"

Manison showed the scattered information packet that he had intercepted as he explained, "Not too long ago, a special information package attempted to infiltrate my sub-base, and after it failed, it tried to self-detonate itself. I managed to salvage a portion of it, and from there, I gleaned its general structure. This may be a new form of quantum network virus, where every information package is a source of infection. It will constantly replicate itself and has strong camouflage, permeability, and infection abilities.

"I tracked it down, and this virus is spreading rapidly in the quantum network of the Ancient Star Desert. Countless nodes have been compromised. Working backward, I concluded that this virus might be related to the cosmic energy explosion some time ago, so I came over to notify you."

Looking at the material that Manison presented, the expressions of the executives gradually turned grave.

"Turns out, it's a new type of quantum network virus." Sidreun felt a headache coming. "The quantum network is one of the cornerstones of our galactic society, and this sort of highly contagious virus is the most troublesome. If left untreated, communications might be paralyzed, data lost, and intelligence stolen… What exactly does it do?"

"This virus is still in its incubation period. Once it breaks out, it will rewrite the underlying logic of the infected artificial intelligence and activate a kill order against all living bodies, setting off a mechanical rebellion," Manison answered calmly as though he was giving a lecture.

At the current stage of the galactic society, every household possessed some form of artificial intelligence or machinery. Once a rebellion occurred within the Star Field or even within the universe, the consequences could be imagined.

Sidreun shivered involuntarily. If Manison had not invaded to pass on the message, the longer they delayed, the more serious this situation would have become. It might even shake the ruling foundation of the three Universal Civilizations.

Thinking of this, Sidreun's expression toward Manison softened a lot more.

When he's not up to mischief, this ally was actually quite the reliable person.

He suddenly stood up, throwing away his 'salted fish' halo, and solemnly declared, "This matter is too huge. I'll report it to the President immediately!"

A few hours later, the three Universal Civilizations had all received the news, calling an emergency joint meeting.

"… The situation is as such. Right now, the Ancient Star Desert has become the epicenter for this new quantum virus. With every second, the number of nodes being infected by the virus, which has been named 'Intelligent Plague', is rapidly increasing. We need to take immediate measures."

Bader summarized the situation, expressing his position.

The Pope of the Arcane Church narrowed his eyes, saying in a deep tone, "Isolate the entire Ancient Star Desert. Until the virus is completely eliminated, the entire Ancient Star Desert is forbidden from interacting with the external universe's quantum network. Stargates are all to be closed, and fleets are to be sent to the periphery of the Ancient Star Desert to prevent the source of infection from leaking out in any form."

"Hmm." Urranrell nodded in agreement.

This was like treating a normal biological plague, where only isolation would allow it to be completely eliminated.

To barricade all communications within a Star Field, only the three Universal Civilizations had the qualifications and capabilities for such a huge project. If the trio could arrive at a common intention, they would be able to enforce the decree. This was the highest power the three Universal Civilizations had given themselves in the Civilization Conference.

"We also need to inform the local civilizations within the Ancient Star Desert, getting them on side. This problem must be dealt as soon as possible."

At this time, in order to reassure others, the three could not take the opportunity to attack the Super Star Cluster Civilizations of the Ancient Star Desert. Otherwise, no one would cooperate the next time a similar disaster occurred. The disadvantages far outweighed the potential gains.

If they missed the optimum timing due to infighting, this virus would shake the very foundation of order in the Galactic Civilization, causing a major blow to the dominance of the three Universal Civilizations. There were countless examples in history, so the three of them would never repeat the same mistake.

In the face of such disasters, the three Universal Civilizations would put aside their struggle for interests and temporarily work together to overcome the shared difficulty.

"I recommend that we recruit mechanics from all over the Universe, especially the Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanics that specialize in this area," Urranrell suggested. "We should also call the Mechanic Emperor and Black Star to come over and cooperate sincerely to solve the problem."

"Agreed."

"Agreed."

The others all nodded.

Since it was a disaster in the Virtual Domain, they had to have experts in a related field to check it out. Mechanic Emperor and Black Star were the leaders in the Virtual Domain, so they would naturally be employed by the three Universal Civilizations.

As for the origin, cause, and principles behind the disaster, there would be plenty of time to look for clues after this problem was solved.

Furthermore, the three Universal Civilizations were extremely interested in this Virtual Virus Technology.

If this virus had happened in the past, it would likely cause the direct order of the galactic civilization to collapse, turning it into a troubled time. However, with years of development, the three Universal Civilizations could keep the risks under control so long as such disasters were discovered early. There was no need to panic like before.

The only hidden danger that the three Universal Civilizations were worried about would be the unstable civil organizations, such as the Galactic Black Market, wanted criminals, and rebels. If one of them kept the virus secretly, that would be problematic.

Maybe there was even someone that was behind the scenes. The three leaders exchanged glances, sharing the same worries.

The Black Star Cup had been in full swing for around two of three months, and Han Xiao had been spending that downtime within his workshop.

He initially wished to keep a low profile for the next year and a half, waiting for the three Universal Civilizations to take action against the Super Star Cluster Alliances, but he did not expect the dynasty to suddenly send him an invitation to a mission one day, asking him to run over to the Ancient Star Desert to tackle a virtual virus.

"To actually block the entire Ancient Star Desert, is that virus so powerful?"

After reading the news from the dynasty, Han Xiao had a weird expression on his face.

In his previous life, this incident did not happen during Version 4.0.

To be precise, the players did not experience the 'Intelligent Plague'. This event happened during the version update leading up to the Silver Revolutionary Army. For the players, it was just a background story.

Han Xiao recalled the brief introduction to the 'Intelligent Plague', even though he had not experienced the incident personally.

In his previous life, the process of resolving this disaster was difficult. The three Universal Civilizations wanted to clear out the virus entirely, but something went wrong, causing the virus to leak and infect multiple Star Fields. The communications in a large number of areas were paralyzed, and the order of their civilization was hit hard.

The three Universal Civilizations sacrificed a lot of resources to resolve the disaster, but due to their attention focused over there, coupled with bad public opinion, it was exploited by the Silver Revolutionary Army of his previous life to develop and grow. This was also an important factor in the success of the Silver Revolutionary Army.

But now, the Intelligent Plague had broken out many years in advance, yet the Silver Revolutionary Army had not said a word, probably missing this opportunity forever.

"It's the butterfly effect caused by my actions again…" Han Xiao stroked his chin.

The dynasty's brief contained the cause of the incident, and Han Xiao realized the moment he went through it.

Because he had gotten rid of Gorutan, the black market had entered a short period of time where there was a vacuum in the positions, leading to them being raided by galactic pirates. The original buyer was also investigated by the three Universal Civilizations and seemed like he just wished to collect an antique of an unknown civilization, so Han Xiao had indirectly caused the opening of the safe many years in advance.

Not sure if this is a blessing or a curse…

Han Xiao pursed his lips. The Intelligent Plague was a timed bomb, and it was definitely better for it to erupt during this version rather than during the World Tree Civilization War arc. However, with the conflicts between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance, this might turn into a bargaining chip for the Super Star Clusters.

If the Super Star Clusters obtained a respite and managed to find a way to rise up as a Universal Civilization, the situation of the universe would take a completely different path compared to his previous life.

I don't know the general trend of the times, as well as which side will eventually fall…

Shaking his head, Han Xiao suppressed the worries in his heart. At least there was something positive from this incident.

What a coincidence, to think that I would meet with a famous person from the later versions…

Harrison and his team were the excavators, so they were also recorded. Han Xiao was glad to have come across such a famed protagonist and was already thinking how to transplant this unowned leek into his own vegetable plot.

At the bare minimum, he could serve as a mascot, increasing the luck of his Black Star Army.

"Phillip, reply to the dynasty. Tell them that I'm accepting the invite and will rush over immediately."

He was naturally willing to make a contribution, as he did not wish for the Intelligent Plague to consume a lot of energy of the current explored universe.

Don't ask, I'm definitely not going there to obtain and research this virus technology! I have absolutely no interest in it at all! Fighting!

Ding!

At this moment, Han Xiao's interface popped up with a notification informing him of a mission.

[1] The author is trying to say how the passage of time would grind away at your anger such that you would feel indifferent to everything and anything, just like Buddha or a salted fish who only wishes to lie there and do nothing all dayBack

Chapter 1101: Accumulation

You have triggered an S-ranked Mission: Intelligent Plague!

Mission Introduction: An exploration team has dug out taboo antiques in the Ancient Star Desert, accidentally releasing a virtual virus aimed at artificial intelligences. The source of this virus is unknown, but it has an extremely high infectivity and permeability. It has spread rapidly through the domain of the quantum network, and once it breaks out, the underlying logic of countless artificial intelligences and machines will be rewritten to initiate a mechanical rebellion.

Mission Requirements: Clear the unknown virtual virus and remove the Intelligent Plague crisis.

Reward: Based on the Mission Rating, different rewards will be given.

Special Mission Requirement: Personally destroy the core data of the virus.

Special Mission Reward: Generate a Specialty related to yourself (Exclusive to the Mechanic Class)

An S-rank Mission… well, as expected.

Han Xiao was not surprised at all.

With the three Universal Civilizations barricading the entire Star Field, such a large move would naturally not be a small task. Given the spread of the virus, it was indeed worthy of the highest level of difficulty needed to completely eliminate it.

The majority of S-ranked mission requirements were usually ambiguous, with only a few prompts for the steps needed. One had to discover the method to solve the problem themselves. Generally, there would be more than one method to solve the mission, and one had to be easily adaptable to changes.

This was what had happened with Godora's [Bloodline] mission, so Han Xiao was already used to it.

What he was curious about was regarding the special mission requirements. It actually revealed a lot of information.

I originally thought that every individual virus was the same because that's how a virus usually transmits. I didn't expect that there would be a core. In this manner, the virus is more like a controllable Virtual Domain bioweapon…

If the core of the virus was an intelligent life form, it would definitely be hidden within the quantum network and not show itself. The threat of the virtual viruses would thus greatly increase as opponents with a self-consciousness were more terrifying than the objects that moved based on their instincts.

But there was another possibility, and that was that the core data of the virus was not an intelligent life form but rather an algorithm that was responsible for the coordination of the overall infection. It would command all its virus progeny according to its program structure without any self-awareness.

Hmm… why do I have a feeling this is like operating a plague company? Han Xiao scratched his head.

The special mission reward was the ability to generate a Mechanic class related expertise, not one extracted from a target. This made him feel that the virus core was more likely to be an algorithm. The generated expertise would not be any weaker than the huge movements from this mission and would also likely be related to Virtual Technology expertise.

"Phillip, prepare the spaceship and ask Reynold to choose a few mechanics to follow me."

Han Xiao did not hesitate, putting on his coat and opening the door, striding toward the dock of the base.

This intelligent plague was an emergency, able to threaten the entire universe and disrupt his plans. He had to end his 'vacation' early, temporarily leaving the matters at hand and take his people to the Ancient Star Desert to complete the mission.

As someone who was in a high position, he could not remain uninvolved when faced with problems of this level.

Not long after, a fleet full of Mechanics from the army set off from Black Star Palace, shuttling like a group of meteors through the universe in the direction of the Ancient Star Desert.

At the same time, countless well-known mechanics throughout the universe also received the invitation of the three Universal Civilizations to move toward the Ancient Star Desert.

…

This matter concerned the safety of the entire universe, and the three Universal Civilizations were in a race against time, so they acted quickly. The Civilization Conference was urgently convened, and all the civilizations at the Star System level and above in the Ancient Star Desert were quickly identified.

In the conference hall that was full of remote projections of various civilization representatives, the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations appeared at the same time to announce their decision.

"Yesterday, the Federation of Light, the Crimson Dynasty, and the Arcane Church received reliable information that a special virtual virus has appeared in the Ancient Star Desert. This virus is extremely permeable and has inflected many areas. According to the judgement of experts, the goal of the virus is to rewrite the underlying logic for all infected machines, taking the killing of living organisms as their primary task.

"After much discussion, the three Universal Civilizations have rated this disaster as 'World-Destroying Level' and are activating the unified command to seal off all quantum network nodes connecting the Ancient Star Desert to the outside world. Troops will be sent to block the Star Field, and all civilizations of the Ancient Star Desert must cooperate with the actions of the three Universal Civilizations. These procedures are to be implemented immediately."

Extraordinary times called for extraordinary measures. Without any long-winded talk, the three Universal Civilizations read out the notices rather than bills, requiring all civilizations within the Ancient Star Desert to comply without fail, with no room for negotiation.

Just as they finished speaking, the civilizations' representatives, who were initially wondering why an emergency meeting was convened, turned pale.

The three Universal Civilizations were responsible for the exploration of the universe and had also set up a disaster rating system. According to the relevant laws and regulations, when the threat level of a disaster rose to a certain level, the three Universal Civilizations would have the high veto power and be qualified to coordinate all the civilizations within the universe.

It was just that such incidents were few and far between even throughout the long history.

As soon as the announcement from the three Universal Civilizations was issued, the galactic residents went into an uproar. No one had thought that a disaster of this magnitude would happen all of a sudden. The world was truly full of surprises.

For those ordinary citizens, this was just like any other normal day. The disaster happened silently, and if not for the early warning measures of the three Universal Civilizations, most people would only have reacted when the virus broke out.

Regardless of what the various civilizations within the Ancient Star Desert were planning in secret, they were extremely cooperative on the surface, cutting off all external links and blocking their own Star Field network in accordance with the requirements of the three Universal Civilizations.

With the three Universal Civilizations and the civilizations within the Star Field collectively acting, the scale of resources mobilized was beyond imagination. Things that were believed impossible in the eyes of normal people were easily achieved.

The Ancient Star Desert was quickly isolated from the entire galactic society and became akin to a quarantined city in darkness. All contact with it was forbidden, and the outside world did not know what was happening inside.

While the situation was temporarily under control, panic still spread throughout the universe. The sudden disaster robbed the Flickering World of its limelight, and countless people turned their attention away from the competition in the new Star Field to focus on progression of the situation within the Ancient Star Desert.

Compared to the calm and poise with which the civilizations handled the situation, the galactic residents of the Ancient Star Desert seemed to be chaotic and flustered. Even though the civilizations continued to appease the residents, there were still varying degrees of people fleeing to other planets to take refuge.

Due to the target of the virus being artificial intelligences, countless residents no longer placed their trust in their machines, thinking that they might possibly be a threat. They would rather regress back to the level of a surface civilization than continue to utilize the intelligent machinery. Some even destroyed their machines to eliminate any hidden threats.

A trend of machinery rejection was created in the Ancient Star Desert… but such chaos was long within the predicted scope of the advanced civilizations.

With the severity of the situation, the three Universal Civilizations did not choose to block the news but rather let everyone know the seriousness of such a situation. In this manner, the self-examination and supervision of the galactic residents could be strengthened. Besides, there would be no way to hide any movement of this scale.

The stargates were rapidly closed, the army moving into the Star Field to set up barricades. Countless people who wished to escape from the Ancient Star Desert were completely blocked.

This scene was something that also occurred during the era of the intelligent plague in his previous life. Now that this was pushed forward to the Version 4.0 era, a stormy undercurrent started brewing.

…

"The Ancient Star Desert has been sealed? Black Star has gone to aid them‽"

In the free competition zone, the leaders of the Super Star Cluster met in secret within the Flickering World, their expressions gleeful.

"This disaster is too timely! With the three Universal Civilizations involved in disaster relief, they no longer have the time to contain us!"

Roddick of the Modo Civilization tightly gripped his fists, an expression of joy.

The majority of people in the universe were uneasy and panicking about the disaster, but for the Super Star Cluster Alliance, it was unexpectedly good news.

"That's right. The Intelligent Plague can restrain and control the three Universal Civilizations, which will give us more time. This will increase our chances of winning!"

"The best would be for the Intelligent Plague to spread out and make the three Universal Civilizations suffer. The more chaotic the universe, the less time they have to deal with us. Only with chaos can we stand a chance."

Everyone present was extremely excited, feeling as though it was some form of divine intervention.

"Say, what happens if the three Universal Civilizations fail?"

"That will put everyone in a terrible situation. We will suffer losses as well."

"Without destruction, there can never be creation. Only when the foundations of the three Universal Civilizations are shaken will we then have the chance to rise. These are all necessary sacrifices."

The eyes of everyone present flashed.

If the Intelligent Plague were to truly break loose, then the Super Star Cluster Alliance would also be damaged. However, the three Universal Civilizations would take the brunt, their prestige and dominance sure to plummet.

They believed that the advanced civilizations of the Ancient Star Desert would have their own thoughts as well.

However, right now, all they could do was discuss. The situation was not determined by them, so they could only wait and see.

…

As the entire universe was filled with anxiety, Mechanics from all over the universe rushed to the Ancient Star Desert one after another, arriving at the disaster command center that was temporarily established by the three Universal Civilizations.

One month later, a fleet cruised into the dock of the Disaster Management Command Center. Han Xiao opened the hatch and walked down the spaceship with a group of mechanics. He caught sight of Manison immediately.

"You're finally here."

Manison came up to greet him.

Since the establishment of the development union, Manison and Han Xiao had served as the President and the Vice President respectively. While they had different end goals in mind, they were currently strung together and thus communicated frequently.

"I thought you would arrive in your true body, but you're still using your avatar." Han Xiao clicked his tongue.

"… This is safer."

Manison was a little speechless. A Mechanic was supposed to be a 'paper[1]' class. Han Xiao was an anomaly who ran around everywhere, not afraid of being killed.

After they exchanged greetings, they walked side by side, discussing the current situation.

"I rushed all the way here and could not get any news from the outside. How's the situation in the Ancient Star Desert now?" Han Xiao was curious.

"Not too optimistic. While the three Universal Civilizations have already barricaded the Star Field, the virus is too contagious. Many nodes have already been repeatedly infected, and the virus has a terrible camouflaging ability, rendering normal scanning devices too inaccurate and inefficient. There are currently eight Star Clusters that show signs of infection, and the number of nodes… too large to estimate." Manison shook his head.

Han Xiao understood.

Every terminal connected to a quantum network could be considered a node, meaning this included communicators, household appliances, spaceships, and so on. The number was humongous, and just the classifications would already tell one how terrible the workload was.

Even if the Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanic could easily remove the virus' information packets, there were so many nodes that an individual's strength was simply insufficient. The speed of removal would not surpass the infection speed, let alone factoring the issue of reinfection. At present, only the advanced civilizations had the ability to control the virus.

"The three Universal Civilizations are currently developing special anti-virus programs in order to improve the efficiency of removal. This is also the reason for them calling on us," Manison said.

"Has this virus already been named?"

"Well, it was temporarily named the 'Virtual Mutiny Virus' on paper."

Han Xiao glanced at him before raising an eyebrow. "I heard that you were the first person to discover this virus, immediately running over to the Federation of Light to inform them of this matter. What are your thoughts?"

"This is my business," Manison casually replied.

"Take a guess to see if I believe it or not." Han Xiao smirked. He knew Manison well and had not forgotten the previous incident with the federation. Why was he pretending to be a loyal minister now?

Manison shook his head, looking ashamed at being in his company.

"A youngster will always be a youngster. Your mentality pains me."

Yes, pretend, continue to pretend… Han Xiao sniggered internally.

Seeing that Black Star still had an expression as though he would rather believe that Manison was a ghost instead, he shook his head before whispering, "This type of disaster is the stage for us Mechanics. The more important the three Universal Civilizations view it, the more prominent our importance will be to them. This will allow us to contribute to the universe and become a bargaining chip for us. On the other hand, if this virus cannot be resolved, the Mechanic department will be severely hit, which will not be conducive to our expansion."

"This is more like you." Han Xiao laughed. "You still wish to take the opportunity to study this virus, and if possible, master it so there will be an additional deterrent to the advanced civilizations, right?"

"Aren't you thinking the same way too?" Manison shot back.

Hearing this, Han Xiao put on a righteous look, as though he radiated virtue.

"As the saying goes, with great power comes great responsibility. I do not wish for the universe to fall into chaos; this is my responsibility as a senior!"

"He he."

Manison mirthlessly spat out two laughs.

I read you right, Black Star. We're indeed all jackals of the same tribe.

[1] [Annotation text missing] Back

Chapter 1102: The Undercurrents Within the Different Parties

The duo idly chatted as they walked into the spacious conference room.

At this moment, various races were sitting in the conference room, all of which were Mechanics from all over the world. The lowest tier here was the Calamity Grade, and several Beyond Grade A Mechanics were also present.

The dynasty's [Illusory Deity] Kant, [Warship Emperor] Maximiler, and [Quantum Demon] Judith; the church's Sun Hunter and [Mechanical Catastrophe] Francisco; the federation's [Mechanic Empress] Mornisa, [Defender] Romo, and the [Lone Ranger] Jackornitz whom Han Xiao had just released.

Not all of them specialized in Virtual Technology, but as Beyond Grade A Mechanics, they had naturally dabbled in the Virtual Domain, definitely more than what the Calamity Grades would have.

In order to deal with the Intelligent Plague, the three Universal Civilizations had invited all sorts of well-known experts from different Star Fields to work together. This could be described as a grand gathering of the universe's mechanics. All sorts of talents gathered on this unprecedented occasion.

When Han Xiao walked in with Manison, everyone felt their breaths stagnate, their gazes landing on the two of them with emotions such as worship and awe appearing on their faces.

In the present Mechanic world, Manison was recognized as the pinnacle, whereas Black Star had an unstoppable rising momentum. Not long ago, he had set another stellar battle record. Coupled with his role as the Vice President of the Beyond Grade A Association, he was second only to Manison in the rankings of the Beyond Grade A Mechanics.

Watching the two of them walk in shoulder to shoulder, many of the Mechanics felt like they were meeting their idols.

"Oh, everyone is here."

The Beyond Grade A Mechanics were all in the first row. Han Xiao first greeted Kant and his other dynasty allies before turning his head to sweep the federation and the church's people with a glance.

Oh, it's confirmed. Everyone here has been beaten by me before.

As though perceiving the ridicule in Han Xiao's eyes, with the exception of Sun Hunter, the rest of the Mechanics naturally looked away, not wishing to make eye contact with Black Star.

This was especially so after being released from prison. Jackornitz, who was the latest to have been released, quickly turned his head to look at the ceiling, pretending to be distracted.

"Tsk tsk, don't be shy. We're all part of the same association now. Why are you still acting so cold, not even saying hello?"

Han Xiao leaned over, smiling as he draped his arms over their shoulders. Everyone's shoulders stiffed; they only helplessly nodded and greeted him, "Vice President."

Ah, how comfortable.

Han Xiao was satisfied, patting everyone's shoulders vigorously before taking a seat next to Manison. He pulled Kant beside him to discuss the changes behind the virus thus far.

After a while, Sidreun strode into the room, standing on the rostrum of the conference room. The whispering voices quickly abated, and everyone looked up toward him.

Sidreun lightly cleared his throat, solemnly speaking.

"Some of you might know me, but others don't, so I'll do a brief introduction of myself. I'm Sidreun, the Chief of the Federation of Light's Inspector Department. Everyone here is a Mechanic at the top of the universe and has accepted the invitation to remove the Virtual Mutiny Virus. The situation is urgent now, so I skip the formalities. Let me explain the current situation to you."

As he spoke, Sidreun called out the virtual screen showing the current infection scope of the virus, continuing in a grave tone.

"The Virtual Mutiny Virus is a new type of quantum network virus with a very high technology level. It has amazing penetration ability into normal firewalls. After the data packet has succeeded in penetration, it will disguise itself as normal data. There are too many variants of the package's key data, thus its degree of concealment is extremely high. Once the node is successfully infiltrated, the difficulty of scanning will be greatly increased, which in turn consumes more computing power.

"Moreover, every information package of the Virtual Mutiny Virus is a source of infection, constantly self-replicating to create repeated infections. Thus, the efficiency of our conventional methods will be too weak. At present, we are analyzing the structural coding of the information packets, planning to create programs that can reverse the development of its three unique programs—namely scanning, anti-virus, and firewall. The problem is, the coding for this virus is different from our mainstream quantum network technology. Just the analysis is difficult, slowing progress…"

Hearing this, everyone nodded. This was a normal process when dealing with virtual viruses.

Virtual Mechanics could be said to resemble the medical experts from all over the world, gathering and working together right now to research and come out with a cure to a new infectious disease.

Sidreun said in a heavy voice, "At present, the Virtual Mutiny Virus is still within the incubation period. We managed to intercept many virus information packets that did not manage to completely self-destruct themselves. After interpreting the content, we have discovered the trigger mechanism behind the outbreak of the virus. However, the situation is not good.

"Based on the analysis of the algorithms, it shows that there are sixteen trigger logics for the outbreak of the Virtual Mutiny Virus, of which four are potentially troublesome. First, when the number of infected nodes reaches a certain scale, the virus will automatically break out. The second trigger is the removal of the virus on a large scale. The third logic is that once the infection rate of the virus slows to a certain scale or if there are repeated infections without any new nodes being infected, the virus will then break out. Lastly, if a single virus packet is isolated or trapped for too long within a node, it will implode on its own…"

While listening to Sidreun's introduction, Han Xiao nodded to himself in understanding.

Viruses would not sit and wait to die. These trigger mechanisms were created to adapt to various situations. If they infected enough numbers, outbreak! If they were being killed en masse, outbreak! If the infection rate was restricted, outbreak!

The [Intelligent Plague] mission had warned him of the existence of a virus core, so most of the trigger mechanisms, including the three previously talked about, should be controlled by the virus core. Only the virus core could coordinate the overall infection trend. Information packets were like bombs, and the virus core was the remote detonator.

While disconnecting the quantum network could cut off the connection between the information packets and the virus core, the fourth trigger was introduced to prevent such a situation. Even without the virus core remotely controlling it, the infected node will self-detonate if left too long without any new signal or information sources, akin to a timed bomb. Thus, it was also difficult to isolate and imprison the virus separately.

At present, the three Universal Civilizations could only cut off the connection between the Ancient Star Desert and the other Star Fields to prevent further infection, whereas the internal network of the Star Field had not been cut off, retaining the public base stations as well as the Star Field level quantum network channels.

It was not realistic to completely disconnect the network. Cutting off the link of each node would be equivalent to blinding themselves. In this manner, the three Universal Civilizations would not be able to monitor the rate of infection, let alone count the number of infected nodes.

Thus, only by developing an anti-virus with a three-pronged approach could the problem be settled once and for all.

"… The situation is severe. We're fighting with time against the virus. While delaying the outbreak of the virus, we also have to speed up research and development. During this period, a mechanical rebellion could happen at any time, so we can only try our best to prepare and control the outbreak."

Sidreun gazed around, his expression grave as he emphasized his point.

"We have to block the virus right here in the Ancient Star Desert, not letting it leak out to the outside world, else the crisis will be uncontrollable and evolve into a universal disaster. The consequences would be unimaginable!"

As his voice fell, the atmosphere of the conference room grew heavy.

Thinking about the potential impact, many of the mechanics present felt tremendous pressure. It could be said that the progress of their efforts was directly related to the number of casualties in the universe. If a mistake was made, there would then be countless sacrifices.

Han Xiao thought on it.

Has it reached such a state?

Even the three Universal Civilizations were having a headache, causing him to wonder which civilization this Virtual Mutiny Virus originated from as well as the creator of this technology.

Suddenly, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

That's right! If I utilize the [Bold Explorer] skill, I might be able to see through the origins of the virus…

After the meeting was adjourned, Sidreun took the group to the virus research department.

On the way, Han Xiao and Manison walked in front, entering the quantum network to chat privately in their minds.

"You came earlier than me, so tell me, is the analysis of the virus really that difficult?"

"It comes from an unknown civilization, with a never-before-seen encoding method. It's already difficult to decipher, and coupled with the self-destruction mechanism, we only ever get incomplete information packets." Manison shook his head. "With our strength, we can clear the information packets at will, but the current task is to create a three-pronged anti-virus kit that even ordinary people can use. Without advanced computing power, the requirements have to be more demanding."

Han Xiao nodded, his eyes gleaming as he replied, "I feel that you don't really wish to create the dedicated antivirus so quickly."

Manison glanced at him, not bothering to reply directly. "This virus technology has the possibility to be weaponized. The information packet is being used like a missile head, and the content inside can be reprogramed, for example, to seize control of a machine. With the help of the high infectiousness of this virus, the invasion ability of us Virtual Mechanics can be raised to a whole new level…"

Hearing this, Han Xiao also clearly understood Manison's plan.

This person wished to solve the disaster and accumulate achievements, but that was under the premise that he could thoroughly research and grasp this virus technology. In order to ensure the deterrence behind this technology, he did not wish to make a whole and complete antivirus, rather leaving a small loophole within.

Han Xiao secretly cursed this sneaky old man before narrowing his eyes and saying, "If you can control the virus core data and obtain the source code, then you can fully analyze this technology."

"That's right." Manison nodded before glancing back. "It's not just you and me, but every of the Beyond Grade A mechanics present, even those from the three Universal Civilizations have the same intention to obtain the virus core."

On the way to the R&D department, there was a huge crowd, and a large number of researchers were stationed here day and night to decipher the Virtual Mutiny Virus.

Everyone was assigned to their specific task, immediately beginning to work.

Some were in charge of scientific research whilst others did field work. They had to go outside to collect those infected nodes, acting as inspectors of the three Universal Civilizations to check how the other civilizations were handling the infected nodes.

As for the Beyond Grade A Mechanics, they acted as experts and consultants, staying within the headquarters to research. All of them had their dedicated rooms.

Taking his subordinates into the room, Han Xiao was assigned three information packages, of which the structural integrities were at 91%, 82%, and 75% respectively. These were the least damaged batches.

Han Xiao summoned Phillip, analyzing the information packages one by one against the currently deciphered part of the code comparison table.

As a Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanic, he was not worried about Phillip being infected. This sort of information package could not break through his own defense line.

Taking advantage of Phillip doing the hard work for him, Han Xiao slipped into the quantum network, capturing one of the information packages before activating his [Bold Explorer] skill.

At the same time, on the Star Arc Civilization's mother planet, a meeting was being held, and many of the upper echelons were discussing animatedly.

"Now that the three Universal Civilizations have blocked the Ancient Star Desert, disaster relief is the primary task for them, but they might also take the opportunity to deal with the Super Star Cluster Civilizations in this Star Field in the name of inspecting the infected nodes. They might request us to open our internal database, even taking advantage of this news blockage to achieve what they want!"

"That's impossible. The three Universal Civilizations aren't so stupid. If they take this opportunity to act on the civilizations that cooperate with them, it will only ruin their credibility and will only make us struggle to the death."

"But forcing us to open our databases is rather possible. If we choose to reject, once they have solved this disaster, the three Universal Civilizations will have a lot of room to operate. Whether it is to plant blame or for political accountability, they can attack all of the Super Star Cluster Civilizations in the Ancient Star Desert, using this as an excuse to begin a crusade against the Super Star Cluster Alliance."

"We can't rely on the integrity of the three Universal Civilizations. We have to prepare bargaining chips and secure our retreat in advance."

"That's right. We cannot just listen to the arrangements of the three Universal Civilizations. I suggest we secretly collect some infected nodes, keeping the virus as a trump card. We can even take a little risk to open the military's secret external communication network and pass the virus on to our secret forces within each Star Field as insurance…"

Suggestions spewed out quickly, and the expression of the head of the civilization was grave as he pondered.

The Star Arc Civilization was located within the Ancient Star Desert, and while it had cut off its connection with the outside world in response to the calls made by the three Universal Civilizations, there was no way a Super Star Cluster Civilization would be this honest and obedient.

To make them obediently give up on studying this terrible virus technology with just an order? What sort of joke was this? Did they think them innocent babies?

So what if the virus breaks out? It's simple, just lock up all the offending artificial intelligences. There will definitely be more solutions than difficulties.

While the three Universal Civilizations were mainly there for disaster relief and did not express any hostility, the blocking of the Star Field still left the Super Star Cluster Civilizations in trepidation. As a civilization, it was impossible for them to place their future in the hands of others. They had to plan ahead.

It was not just Star Arc Civilization; all the advanced civilizations were also secretly planning something.

On a certain planet within the Ancient Star Desert, a subdivision of Machinery Faith was located.

Above the holy mountain, in the Temple of God, many priests stood on the edge of the circular hall, surrounding the holographic projections in the center. Those were the data structures of the Virtual Mutiny Virus, expanded and amplified, looking like stars in the galaxy.

"Look at the structure of this quantum network virus. It's like a thorny rose, coquettish yet dangerous. It's able to set off a machinery revolution, possibly creating a mechanical kingdom…"

One of the priests of the Virtual School could not help but sing out, a pious expression on his face.

"Quiet." The Grand Priest tapped the Machinery Scepter before slowly saying, "This virus is dangerous. We have to conduct research in a completely enclosed environment to prevent any leakage."

"This is no virus but the will of God. Why not spread it out?" Another zealot spread open his arms wide as he babbled. "Rather than saying that it's a disaster, it's better to claim it as the gospel!"

"Have you lost your mind‽"

Hearing this, most of the priests retorted.

"We're the believers of machinery, not the emissaries of a disaster!"

The quarrel was fierce, and the Grand Priest had a heavy expression as he listened to the different factions arguing.

Any faith would have some zealots with distorted mindsets, and the Machinery Faith was no exception. Most of them wished to study the Virtual Mutiny Virus and did not want to cause a disaster.

However, a small portion of them did not think so. In their eyes, the Intelligent Plague was a god-sent message for revolution, allowing machinery to get rid of the shackles of being a tool and gain freedom to form its own Machinery Kingdom. In those zealots' eyes, the Virtual Mutiny Virus was the will of God.

The Grand Priest turned his head, looking at the statues within the Temple of God. His eyes fell on the figures of Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor, and he prayed silently to them.

In another area of the Ancient Star Desert, a fleet was slowly cruising, within which was a bunch of players.

Now that the World Server was open, players from all Star Fields had gathered in the Flickering World. However, there were a few of the players that still chose to stay in their original Star Fields. Some of these people were happy being small-time characters, while others did not wish to travel all over the universe just to start from nothing once more. Thus, they remained in the Star Field to keep exploring.

The players in this fleet were an active guild based in the Ancient Star Desert, called the Western Sword Guild. They had been black market mercenaries for the past four versions, and everyone knew that they were Immortals.

The guild president's ID was Depressed Prince, and his character belonged to the galactic Blood Race, which referred to Vampires in general. They possessed pale white skin, skinny figures, and had a melancholic vibe.

The Blood Race existed in the universe, classified as part of the long-lived races, but they did not possess the famed talents such as blood recollection, transforming blood servants, and becoming bats. They also did not have the standard weaknesses such as garlic, silver, or Holy Relics.

There were many theories about the origin of the galactic Blood Race, which included genetic mutations, part of biological weapons created by higher civilizations, or even dark energy invasions. After years of natural selection, the blood race had also adapted to the Galactic Civilization, which caused them to no longer be afraid of ultraviolet radiation, surviving on synthetic blood as well. Ten Enas could buy a few tons of synthetic blood, which also came with a full set of seasoning as well as a fluffy mascot as a free gift.

However, this species was still unpopular in the universe, as no one liked a creature that drank the blood of others to replenish their physical strength.

Beep beep…

The spaceship's communicator rang, and Depressed Prince opened his eyes in surprise.

"Brothers, someone anonymously sent us an employment task through the black market, with a remuneration of five million Enas! They are paying a deposit of a million in advance!"

Everyone gathered around in excitement.

"Such a big order! What are we waiting for? Let's accept it!"

"What does the employer want us to do?"

Depressed Prince glanced through the employment list, and he laughed.

"Haha, interesting, someone wishes to hire us to smuggle an infected node of the Virtual Mutiny Virus out of the Ancient Star Desert."

Hearing this, everyone could not help but exchange glances.

They were also trapped within the Ancient Star Desert, so they were naturally aware of the danger of the Virtual Mutiny Virus as well as the scale of the three Universal Civilizations. Thus, they hesitated.

"President, is the risk too high? If we're exposed, we will immediately become wanted men."

Depressed Prince waved his hand. "What are you scared of? This is five million Enas. There's no reason not to risk our lives for it. Accept the mission."

Everyone could only follow the order, but some of them had other thoughts and began to secretly think to themselves.

Their anonymous employer wanted them to perform this task mainly because they had taken a fancy to their identity as Immortals.

One could see that in the isolated Ancient Star Desert, undercurrents were surging.

Chapter 1103: The sickle is accurate, a leek every slice

After sacrificing sixty percent of his Luck attribute for fourteen days, which amounted to roughly zero points, the [Bold Explorer] skill was activated, and the world in front of Han Xiao's eyes changed.

His sight panned out into outer space, and below him was a huge planet where its silvery gray earth extended all the way as far as his vision allowed. Blue and white dazzling lights covered the horizon, and the bright light from the photon energy tower stood out from the backdrop of the dark universe.

Han Xiao glanced downward. On the surface was a steel forest without any green vegetation, and numerous strange-shaped mechanical buildings occupied the area. The high mechanical towers shot into the sky, giving the planet a look like a mutated sea urchin wearing steel armor. The cold, heavy style brought with it an evil vibe.

At this time, the scene zoomed in, falling to the ground and focusing on the mechanical city at a low altitude. Han Xiao saw that the inhabitants of the planet were a group of mechanical bodies with varied appearances. There were almost no two identical individuals, their structures all complicated and exquisite. Their decals were all gorgeous, giving them a very advanced look.

"They're all mechanical life forms. Could this be a Mechanical Life Civilization?"

As a bystander, Han Xiao could not help but think of Psionic Prime's civilization under his banner. The two were very similar, with the difference that this machinery civilization revealed by [Bold Explorer] was far more advanced, already reaching its matured state.

Did the Virtual Mutiny Virus originate from this unknown mechanical civilization? Han Xiao thought while looking at the scene in front of him.

Right at this moment, something happened!

A piercing white glare that seemed to cover the entire sky swept past, and the giant planet was dead in the center of its blast radius.

A large shield covering the entire planet appeared in outer space, but the moment it came into contact with the light ray, the large shield disintegrated, breaking into countless energy particles.

The planet lost all its protection and was peeled off layer by later, annihilated and decomposed in a short moment. The entire planet's existence was easily erased in the universe by this light ray.

By the time the attack was over, the illusion disappeared, and Han Xiao's vision returned to the room. He frowned.

The attack just now seemed to be an advanced energy rank directional gamma-ray burst. It might not have been a natural disaster but rather an attack from a weapon.

Gamma ray bursts were a common universal disaster, and evaporating a planet was like child's play to them. But with the shields that most civilizations had, they would be able to shield themselves against it. However, the ray burst in the illusion Han Xiao experienced was strange in that it directly disintegrated the planet's shield the moment it touched it, even though the machinery civilization in it was at an advanced level.

Most people would not be able to observe many details, but the senses of the Beyond Grade As were different. Han Xiao found that there was an additional material added to the Gamma Ray, which might make it a galactic weapon utilized by another advanced civilization.

The universe was full of radiation, and it was actually very lively and bright. However, ordinary people would only see a patch of darkness. As a person's life level changed, so did the world they saw around them. It was like everyone was looking at the world through keyholes, but those of a higher life level would have larger keyholes.

The information obtained through the skill this time is not enough. There's no clear direction…

Han Xiao stroked his chin with his thumb, summing up the information he obtained in the short illusion.

Firstly, there was an advanced civilization that was suspected of being a Mechanical Life Civilization. They had a large colonial planet that was extremely advanced in technology, but it was blown up by a Planetary Annihilation Weapon, proving that they had another advanced civilization as their enemy. The hostile civilization would at least be at the Star Cluster level, even possibly at the quasi-Universal Civilization level.

The creator of the Virtual Mutiny Virus should be one of these two civilizations. There was too little information about the other civilization, so Han Xiao ignored it. He mainly analyzed this unknown Machinery civilization.

There are many possibilities for the origin of the Machinery civilization. The most common is for a Beyond Grade A to bestow Mechanical Life, but there are other factors. For example, a biological civilization could also undergo Mechanical Ascension, placing the consciousness of their entire race into mechanical minds and replacing their physical bodies with machinery carriers to obtain immortality. It's also possible that this civilization is in the form of an AI civilization, a world dominated by artificial intelligence, and the machines are just carriers for them to walk around in…

What piqued Han Xiao's curiosity most was whether this happened during the era of the modern Galaxy Calendar. He did not know whether it was a lost civilization that had existed during the exploration era or an unknown advanced civilization in an unexplored region of the universe.

He needed to continue using [Bold Explorer] to obtain intelligence or maybe use more relevant items for his ability…

Han Xiao suddenly recalled something.

There was still the safe in which the virus had been stored, which was in the custody of the three Universal Civilizations. That might be a better goal!

Along the way, he could also visit Harrison and the others. These guys had been temporarily imprisoned due to the release of the Virtual Mutiny Virus. In the face of such a disaster, the inspector did not have the last say, so whatever promises he gave to Harrison and this team would definitely be blown away like farts in the wind.

The three Universal Civilizations were quite considerate to this group of prisoners as well, fearing that their bodies would rust due to the long prison life. Thus, they were interrogated daily at a high intensity to help them work their brains and stay healthy.

Han Xiao left his subordinates and Phillip in the room to continue analyzing the virus code. He left the R&D department by himself and strode over to the headquarters on the dynasty's side.

The three Universal Civilizations had appointed their senior officials to take charge of the affairs of the Ancient Star Desert. With Han Xiao's position in the dynasty, he met with the supervisor without much hindrance.

The other party stood up to greet him, exchanging some niceties before they got down to business.

"Your Excellency Black Star, what can I do for you?" the inspector asked.

"I've read the information you've given and hope to study the device that was used to store the virus."

"That's easy." The dynasty inspector immediately agreed, giving him a lot of respect.

"In addition, I wish to contact the group of scavengers that unearthed this virus, and if possible, release them temporarily."

"You can see them at any time, but releasing them… is a little inappropriate."

"I know, you guys have been interrogating them, but this has yielded no results. They should just be unlucky fools that got trapped in this. There's no point continuing to imprison them."

The Inspector furrowed his brows as he insisted, "But the virus has caused such a big impact. This is a severe crime. Even if it was an accident, they have to take responsibility for it."

Han Xiao shook his head as he pointed out, "They might be of help actually. Let them stay by my side to obtain some merits. If they really manage to make some contributions, then we will have benefitted from it."

The inspector hesitated for a long while before finally agreeing. "… Since you wish for it, alright then. However, their identities will remain as prisoners, and they cannot have freedom of movement."

He only did so out of respect for Black Star's position. If it was some other person suggesting this, he would not even bother.

"Thanks." Han Xiao smiled. "I would also like to request to be allowed to go out on field work."

"You wish to perform field work as well?" The inspector was surprised.

Han Xiao nodded. "That's right. The research work here has Manison and the rest at the helm, so there's no need for me to devote myself to it. I'm wasting resources here, and in my opinion, there are two tasks that are both as equally important as developing an antivirus."

"Please do tell."

"The first would be the search for the virus' core. If the core can be located, most of the triggering mechanisms of the Virtual Mutiny Virus will be invalidated, which will be equivalent to destroying the opponent's brain. The threat of the disaster will also be reduced."

"This point is indeed important." The dynasty's inspector praised.

If the virus core could be controlled, the difficulty of solving this disaster would be reduced by more than fifty percent. However, the virus core had hidden itself too deeply. No one had any idea what sort of abnormal data it was, and the three Universal Civilizations were also unable to find it.

Han Xiao then raised two fingers and continued. "Secondly, in my opinion, it will be a matter of time before the virus is cracked, with the current abilities of the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A mechanics. The real difficulty lies in those with unsavory plans."

Hearing this, the inspector also frowned.

"Countless lessons in history have taught us that the greed and suspicion of the human heart is always a catalyst for disaster. If it's not controlled, the small problems will eventually evolve into bigger problems that cannot be handled," Han Xiao slowly said. "Presumably, the dynasty also understands that the virus is not difficult to solve, but the real problem is in those people with ulterior motives. Having the Virtual Mutiny Virus is akin to them having a switch of disaster. Now that they have such a good opportunity, who does not wish to have a strategic weapon as a deterrent?"

He could clearly see that this was an opportunity for anyone to easily obtain nuclear-level weapons at an extremely low cost. Which ambitious organization would not want to give it a try?

The inspector stood up, suddenly packing around, before solemnly speaking.

"You're right. The three Universal Civilizations have been concerned about this. We're all from the same team here, so there's no need to cover it up. The Super Star Cluster Alliance has been at odds with us since long ago and will not sit quietly and obey our commands. The dynasty's main Artificial intelligence, Heroic Soul, has already calculated the probabilities. Not only the advanced civilization within the Ancient Star Desert but even organizations from the outside world will hire countless black market mercenaries and wanted criminals to help them smuggle the virus out. This is also one of the main reasons the blockade was imposed.

"While we require the Ancient Star Desert to cooperate with us to destroy the virus, at the same time, we cannot be too harsh on them. This is especially so for the Super Star Clusters; they can reopen their own external quantum networks at any time. It actually is not up to us to control if the virus will be leaked or not… Of course, they do not dare make any rash moves. Thus, the three Universal Civilizations are attempting to control the situation by being careful and closing one eye so as not to make them anxious. This is also why we are in such a hurry to develop the antivirus. As long as the threat of the virus technology is fundamentally resolved, the small actions made by the advanced civilization will not affect us."

The inspector then stopped and emphasized, "Your Excellency Black Star, since you're willing to go out into the field, I will hand over three dynasty fleets for you to command. I hope you can try to catch as many of these b*stards who are eager for profit and disregard the safety of the universe."

"Okay." Han Xiao stood up as well, shaking his head.

The other Beyond Grade As concentrated on research, wanting to understand this virus technology. No one wished to waste energy by going out to arrest people. In their opinion, this was hard work that they should not be responsible for.

But our Great Mechanic Han was different. He had the [Intelligent Plague] mission, so in order to raise his Mission Rating, he could not simply rely on research. After all, the credit for that would be shared by a large number of people.

In his opinion, the most direct way to improve the rating would be to catch the fish that slipped through the net with malicious intent.

Furthermore, the special mission requirement was for him to destroy the virus core. He naturally wanted the reward and would not just stay in the command center to do research.

As for research, the more that everyone searched, the more they would share. He could wait till Old Man Manison had completely analyzed the structure of the virus to obtain the ready-made secondary research. Not only would this save a lot of his time, he could also relax for the time being.

After reaching a consensus with the person in charge, Han Xiao left the dynasty's office and went to the prison to visit Harrison.

Upon learning of Han Xiao's intentions, the Chief Warden immediately welcomed him in with enthusiasm, respectfully leading the way.

…

In the single cell, Harrison lay on the bed with his hands on his head, staring absentmindedly at the ceiling.

"Is this how I'm going to spend the next half of my life?"

He sighed.

In this month that he had spent squatting in jail, not one day had passed when he had not expressed regret. His initial judgment was correct—digging out that triangular device would bring them huge trouble. If he had known that was the case, he would have not taken it out even if he had to risk his life.

The serious consequences brought about by this artifact gave him cold hands and feet. While this was an unintentional mistake, to have caused such trouble left him with a guilty conscience.

Not only did he bring about a disaster, he even threw his entire life away. His interrogators had let slip that this group of 'culprits' would be spending the rest of their lives in prison.

"If I knew this would happen, I wouldn't have come out to do archaeology. I knew it. Curiosity kills the cat. If I had stayed at home and inherited hundreds of millions of dollars from my family fortune, god knows how comfortable I would be now."

Harrison was disheartened.

Swoosh!

At this moment, the cell door opened, and two people walked in.

"Is it time for interrogation again?" Harrison sat up with a resigned expression.

Han Xiao glanced at him, piecing his young look with the old man in his memories before nodding. "You're indeed Harrison."

"Eh? You're not a jailer? Who are you…" Harrison raised his head, and taking in Black Star's features, he gaped in shock. "Black… Black… Black… Black Star‽"

Right now, Han Xiao's face was well known in every household within the universe, his reputation frightening. However, there were a few that had heard about him through the movie [Black Star: Origins] and thus mistakenly thought Feidin was Black Star himself.

But Han Xiao was very magnanimous regarding this. After all, both of them looked equally handsome and alike, so it was a common mistake to mix up both of them.

He had heard that the movie was released whilst he was rushing over here, and the response was excellent. Not only had his reputation skyrocketed, he had also made a fortune. His returns were hundreds of times his initial investment and were still rising. From this, the huge profits within the entertainment industry in the interstellar era could be seen.

Putting aside the distracting thoughts, Han Xiao patted Harrison firmly on his shoulder while saying, "The virus was dug up by you guys?"

Harrison was patted so hard he almost screamed in pain but quickly recovered. In front of a universally known figure like Black Star, he was a little cautious and nervous, nodding repeatedly.

"Good, then your teammates and you will follow me temporarily."

"This… what do you mean?" Harrison had an expression of confusion.

Seeing his lost look, the prison warden snapped, "You'd better thank His Excellency Black Star. If not for him speaking up for you guys, you'd be sitting here for the rest of your miserable lives."

Harrison was stunned, an incredulous look on his face.

"Your Excellency Black Star, you… why did you save us?"

"Who said I was saving you? I just felt that you guys are good diggers and might come in handy… The warden will let you guys off later. I'm just here to meet you guys beforehand."

"I can be of help?"

Harrison was lost, not knowing what he could possibly help with.

However, this did not prevent him from understanding that his own destiny was saved by Black Star. His eyes were filled with gratitude, and he wished to hold Black Star's hand to thank him, but due to their gap in status, he did not dare to act.

In his eyes, Black Star was an angel sent by the heavens to save him, shining with a holy light.

Just as he was about to fall into the abyss, a stranger came and gave him a hand. Harrison's emotions were surging, and he had the urge to slam his head on the floor in gratitude toward Black Star.

While it was the first time they had met, Harrison's favorability toward him was almost filled up.

Han Xiao smiled at him before turning to walk out of the jail cell. The moment his back faced him, he could not help breaking into a smile as he looked at the combat information on his interface. Harrison's attribute table was displayed there.

Just by standing by my side, you're already helping me…

In the attribute column, there was the skill [Advanced Luck Glow] in golden lettering!

The third golden leek has fallen into my hands…

Han Xiao took a deep breath of joy.

That's right. This should be the smell of luck condensing on him!

Chapter 1104: Cancer of the Universe, the Catalyst of Disaster

After meeting up with Harrison, Han Xiao ran back to the R&D department and found the Beyond Grade A mechanics.

"You wish to go out and do field work?"

Hearing this, Manison and the rest of the Beyond Grade A mechanics felt surprised. They did not understand why Black Star would leave his easy research work and do the troublesome manual labor.

"What sort of attitude is this? I responded to the call of the three Universal Civilizations and am leading by example to take the lead," Han Xiao said in a tone of righteousness.

"Then just go. Why did you come to us?" Manison did not even bother to entertain him, only glancing at Han Xiao as he tried to find out his intentions.

Black Star, this jerk, had never committed himself until success was certain. If there were no benefits, he would not have chosen to take up field work. He felt that Black Star's motive should be to find the virus core and also to take the opportunity to infiltrate the major organizations in the Ancient Star Desert.

To be honest, Manison himself had thought of this at the beginning as well. However, he had given up this thought after much consideration.

Right now, would the three Universal Civilizations allow the Beyond Grade As to continue strengthening their own organizations? It was most likely that they would have to surrender whatever they obtained from their operations, so even the dishonest Manison was silently only researching the antivirus. Besides, the attraction of new technology far exceeded his organization's strength.

At this moment, Han Xiao suddenly laughed, sticking out two fingers as he righteously spoke out.

"Since none of you are fighting, please aid me and lend me some of your troops."

Everyone stared in shock.

Lending you our troops is akin to sending lambs right into the tiger's den. Will we still be able to get them back?

How is this lending? You just want us to sacrifice a portion of our troops for you, you lowly peasant!

"… How many do you need?"

"Eh, I don't have large demands. This is mainly the moment when the three Universal Civilizations will be able to see your sense of justice. You guys can decide, and please don't exceed fifty million per person. That would be too much for me to accept." Han Xiao 'modestly' waved his hands.

Pui, a scale of 50 million per person? Are you thinking about openly stealing so many?

Do you even feel shame‽

Everyone secretly slandered Han Xiao but did not refuse his request. The three Universal Civilizations' mechanics and several neutral Beyond Grade As loaned a portion of their ordinary mechanical soldiers, which reached about eight million in number.

Among them, Manison was the most generous, lending 2.5 million units. To him, this number of soldiers was only a drop in the ocean.

The stingiest was 'Mechanical Catastrophe' Francisco; he only gave five thousand troops, doing so unwillingly. Even Jackornitz who was a Mechanical Pugilist and did not have much proficiency in Machinery manufacturing also donated more troops.

The Beyond Grade A Mechanics all had illustrious backgrounds, so giving out some mechanical soldiers was nothing to them. They simply treated it as losing some troops in battle. However, it was more important to show some face to Black Star, as well as the three Universal Civilizations, to show that while they were too lazy to make a move, they still supported the field work.

Putting away the troops 'sponsored' by everyone, Han Xiao was satisfied. While this number was a pittance, he just wanted to see the Beyond Grade As grit their teeth and feel helpless in front of him.

Upon arriving at the dock, Han Xiao boarded a flagship arranged for him by the dynasty and took over the commander's authority from the captain. Right now, the three dynasty fleets were temporarily under his command.

After waiting for a while, a guard hurriedly escorted Harrison and his party over.

"Your Excellency Black Star, the procedures are complete. I'll leave them with you."

"Alright." Han Xiao nodded at Harrison and team with a smile on his face, saying, "You guys are not free yet. You have to follow me. If you mess around, I'll just throw you back in prison. Do you understand?"

"Understood!"

Before Harrison could speak, all his teammates yelled out loudly, for fear that they would lose their only bid at freedom.

Han Xiao nodded, and after sending the guard away, he gave the command to depart.

The fleet slowly rose up, leaving the command center of the three Universal Civilizations and soaring into space.

At this moment, the captain spoke.

"Your Excellency Black Star, where are we heading?"

"How do you normally operate?" Han Xiao asked back.

"We usually patrol around the desolate universe belt or go check some planets that are confirmed to have traces of infection…"

As of now, there were checkpoints set at every stargate of any civilization in the Ancient Star Desert, the borders, and the transport hub planets. The spaceships had to be inspected, and for those unknown spaceships that avoided the stargate stations and moved freely within the desolate universe belt, as long as they accessed the public quantum link of the Star Field, the three Universal Civilizations would track down their IP addresses and send people to stop them. Most of the field fleets were tasked with roaming around to perform such inspections.

Thus, the biggest problem would be for those spaceships that had shielded quantum network links and could enter stealth mode. They could only monitor the surveillance buoys located throughout the Star Field and try to find the whereabouts of these people.

"Let me think about it…"

After understanding the situation, Han Xiao pretended to ruminate, but he actually opened the players' forums to scroll through.

The outbreak of the Intelligent Plague had drawn the attention of the players toward the Ancient Star Desert. The discussion on the Ancient Star Desert was a hot post on every major section of the forum.

Because the majority of players were in the Flickering World, they were unable to join the event since the Ancient Star Desert was immediately cordoned off after the occurrence of the Intelligent Plague. They could only use the discussion boards to vent their strong curiosities.

Han Xiao opened the top post, and the discussion of the players jumped into view.

Fart Pockets in Tights: I told you all. The first few versions all had more than one Main Storyline mission, and Version 4.0 is the same. The Intelligent Plague should be the second Main Storyline.

Quadratic Formula: But we are not able to participate in this Main Storyline. We cannot even enter the Ancient Star Desert. Can we only watch from the sidelines?

Three Gays Under the Moon: Didn't you see the new update from 'Galaxy Times'? They made quite a reasonable guess, saying that it is impossible for this Main Storyline to be only for our viewing. There will definitely be opportunities for us to participate, as the chances of the virus leaking are quite high. Only then will there be a continuation for us to act.

Four-Eyed Speculative Emperor: That's right. Now there are many missions on the black market, all looking to hire people to sneak into the Ancient Star Desert. We players can do the same. Judging by our influence on the Main Storyline for the first two versions, this Intelligent Plague event could be decided by our actions as well. As long as someone succeeds in smuggling the virus out, this version's event can sweep across the universe!

Undead Don't Wear Underwear: Shall we let the disaster spread through the universe? It will indeed be the fourth disaster (:з」∠)

Sun Rider: This is too much. Wouldn't it be better to prevent the disaster? Do you have to make it such that the world is chaotic? Don't you have a conscience?

Sh*t Smells Good: That's right. Did you forget what the Army Commander taught us? To actually stab him in the back like that, killing the citizens of the galaxy…

On the forums, the players were divided into several factions, discussing the topic and cursing each other at the same time. The community was on fire.

The players did not know that the Intelligent Plague was actually just a backstory in their previous lives, thinking that it was one of the Main Storylines of Version 4.0. With the majority of people in the Flickering World, unable to enter the Ancient Star Desert, many of them were anxious at not being able to participate.

Some of them believed that the main storyline would not just be a cutscene, so they inferred that the Intelligent Plague did not need to be actively pushed by them and would leak by itself.

Others felt that this main storyline had to be fought for, taking the initiative to release the virus and let the disaster spread in order to obtain the Main Storyline mission.

There were, however, many players in the universe who supported the promotion of the disaster. Some wanted to participate in the Main Storyline, some wanted to earn rewards, and some just wanted to watch the world burn.

'Indeed, the Cancer of the Universe…' Han Xiao secretly shook his head.

As the players who were ruled by chaos continued to grow stronger, their negative impact on the universe would become more and more obvious.

However, he was also a little relieved. If the players in his previous life encountered the Intelligent Plague, more than half of them back then would definitely have supported the promotion of the Intelligent Plague. Now, with the Black Star Army as their moral guide, more people were considering the problem from the perspective of the overall situation, opposing the spread of the disaster. There were obviously fewer players within the Chaotic Evil Faction than in his previous life.

My faction guidance plan is still somewhat effective.

Han Xiao felt relief.

As he swept through the other posts, one of them caught his attention. It was titled 'Ancient Star Desert Player Benefits! Employment task with a reward of five million Enas!'

The poster triumphantly shared a screenshot of a mission, which was about smuggling the Virtual Mutiny Virus out of the Ancient Star Desert for five million Enas. For the players, this was a huge sum of money, enough to buy a dozen small and medium battleships.

Seeing that the players who remained within the Ancient Star Desert got such an opportunity to rake in the cash, many of the following replies expressed envy.

The poster was called 'Depressed Prince'. Han Xiao could not help but narrow his eyes.

Five million in remuneration, along with a deposit, gives this whole thing a fishy air. It seems that the employers are aware of the players' character and used them to their advantage.

Humph, the players within the Ancient Star Desert aren't able to keep their hands to themselves. I have to strike down like peals of thunder on them and destroy their disaster-supporting tendencies.

Han Xiao made the decision in his heart to kill the chicken in order to warn the monkeys. This Depressed Prince who went around publicizing his tasks was undoubtedly an excellent goal.

Only through striking down harshly on him would the other players then see the ending of those who tried to cause trouble and would cause them to fear the repercussions of their actions.

At the same time, he could also trace the source and check up on the mysterious employer of Depressed Prince. After all, there was no harm if there was no demand or supply for it. The mercenaries only acted based on orders, and it was the employers with ulterior motives that Han Xiao was interested in.

While Depressed Prince did not disclose his coordinates, since the other party was a mercenary, he would have recorded his whereabouts in the universe. So long as the record of his most recent time was locked onto, the approximate search area could be derived from there. To a pinnacle Beyond Grade A mechanic, this was as easy as lifting his hands.

The intelligence channel in the Ancient Star Desert might have been blocked, but the player forums were not affected. With this extra information network, Han Xiao would be able to obtain information that others did not know.

That's right, I also have to search for one of the administrators of the black market in the Ancient Star Desert. These employment tasks for smuggling the virus will be issued through the black market. As long as I can control this channel, I will be able to monitor the movements of those restless organizations and cut off one of the channels for employment.

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

If the administrator of the black market did not wish to cooperate, he still had a trump card up his sleeve. There was no need to be soft-hearted. Even the three Universal Civilizations would be glad to have someone temporarily controlling the black market channels, reducing the likelihood of disaster.

Mindful of this, Han Xiao finally had a clear plan of action and turned to look at the captain.

"Let's split up and act. The main flagship will follow me to capture some b*stards."

…

Somewhere in the desolate universe belt, an interstellar fortress was suspended in the orbit of a desolate planet, with a spaceship patrolling nearby. Both of them had the same emblem, which was shaped like a roaring wolf's head.

This sign represented an interstellar organization named the Kepel Financial group, which was a legitimate financial group on the surface but operated as an arms dealer for the galactic black market in the Ancient Star Desert.

The organization was a family-run business, and the leaders were all members of the Kepel family. The current leader was called Kepel the Fifth, and he had the mutated bloodline of a Beastman, possessing a head that looked like a werewolf.

At this moment, in the office of the leader, Kepel the Fifth had just received a capable officer who had rushed back.

"I made you responsible for spreading the anonymous employment task on the black market. Has the mission been completed?" Kepel the Fifth said in a deep baritone.

"It's completed. Many of the black market mercenaries have accepted the task, willing to smuggle the Virtual Mutiny Virus out."

"Very good. The Virtual Mutiny Virus is a strong weapon and will definitely have a market in the future. We need to control it!"

As an arms dealer in the black market, the Kepel Financial group had no reason to let go of the Virtual Mutiny Virus, which was a powerful weapon of war. This was just purely commercial considerations.

"Leader, I've also specially employed some of the Immortal troops. I feel that it would be more likely for them to complete the task."

"Beautiful! The Immortals are money grubbers and born to be mercenaries. So long as we give them enough money, they would rather sacrifice their lives. Moreover, they have unknown information networks within their groups, which cannot be interfered with even with our quantum networks. Their capabilities will increase the success rate of our plan. If one can be shipped out, the virus can be infinitely replicated!"

Kepel the Fifth was very satisfied with how his subordinate carried out the task.

Most of the major organizations had studied the characteristics of players, more or less summing up some rules. The Kepel Financial group was no exception, mastering some simple ways to utilize the players.

At present, since the Ancient Star Desert was sealed, the various gray organizations could be thoroughly investigated by the advanced civilizations at any time. The Kepel Financial group had decided to transfer their assets to the outside world and destroy evidence of their gray business. Thus, it was determined to transport their arms, along with the Virtual Mutiny Virus, out of the Star Field.

Chapter 1105: Conspiracy‽

The Western Sword Guild's spaceship slowly flew through cosmic space. Inside the cabin, Depressed Prince and the other guild members stood around the 3D star map and analyzed the route.

"We're now here…"

Depressed Prince pointed on the star map and drew an illuminated path. It extended around a desolate universe belt at the edge of the Star Field in an arc, all the way to outside the Star Field. He then said, "In order to leave the Star Field, the only way is through the desolate universe belt. The encirclement the three Universal Civilizations had set up at the borders will definitely have flaws. Although we have their defense map and patrolling route, we still need some luck…"

Hearing the president explain the plan, the guild members nodded.

After accepting the anonymous hiring with a five million reward, Depressed Prince had thought of some plans in order to successfully transport the virus out. Among which, making use of the flaws in the encirclement of the three Universal Civilizations and smuggling it out was one of those more likely to succeed.

In order to not be located by the three Universal Civilizations, the Western Sword guild had already cut off their network and kept their spaceship in stealth mode.

Technically, they would not be able to receive any information from the outside world this way. However, Depressed Prince used the fact that he was a player, logged into the forums, and secretly hired other players to private message him on the forums to provide intelligence. This was how he obtained the defense map and patrol route of the three Universal Civilizations. Even though they had cut off their quantum network connection, they still had a source of information.

This way, not only could they avoid getting located by the three Universal Civilizations through the network, but they would also still be able to receive messages from the outside world. Compared to normal people, the players had a large advantage. No wonder the Kepel Financial Group specifically hired Immortals.

"President," a player said, "the closer we are to the border, the denser the surveillance buoys will be. If we fail and are discovered, our spaceship will definitely be seized. We only have one chance."

"That's why we have a plan B."

With a confident expression, Depressed Prince smiled and said, "Once we're discovered by the buoys or the patrolling guards, we'll carry out the infiltration tactic. We'll leave a few people on the spaceship while the rest of us log out together. When the spaceship is locked up at the warehouse, the people who did not log out can then notify us to come online in the carrier and sneak into the enemy base. This way, we can bring in the virus-infected communicator."

The others nodded. This also relied completely on the players' specialty. This tactic was extremely suitable for infiltration, ambush, and smuggling missions.

There was also a plan if they turned out to be exposed after that. They would give up the spaceship, battle to their death, and then revive in their stronghold revival point. They could still think of other ways to complete the mission, and they had a very large margin for error. The reward was a total of five million anyway; as long as they could complete the mission, buying another spaceship was nothing.

With so many advantages, the Western Sword guild members present were totally confident about completing the mission. They could almost see the five million Enas waving at them.

As for the possibility that they might become wanted criminals afterward, they did not care about it at all. They had always wandered in the gray area of the law, so they never even planned to become completely legit. In fact, turning into wanted criminals would even trigger a Milestone Mission, which gave them rewards as their bounty increased.

As for the damage that the virus leak would cause to ordinary people, they did not give a damn. Instead, they were even excited about the fact that they were playing a big part in the direction the world was going to take. Most players who currently supported the disaster's spread had the same thought.

Depressed Prince was confident. He smiled and said, "Alright, since no one has any objections, let's act according to this plan. As we can't use the stargates, we'll spend quite some time on the way there. The estimated time of arrival at the desolate universe belt is in seven days. Now…"

At this time, before he finished speaking, the spaceship alarm suddenly rang.

"Beep! Alert! Alert! The spacetime of this area has been stabilized. Hyperdrive is impossible. Exiting hyperdrive mode!"

The spaceship suddenly shook. The people inside had yet to react to it, so they all fell onto the ground, picking themselves up with shock.

"What's going on? There are spacetime stabilization anchors here? Whose trap did we fall into?"

Shocked, Depressed Prince hastily looked at the radar.

This time, light dots were appearing around them on the radar and surrounded his spaceship in the middle.

The people quickly came to the porthole and looked outside. Their expression changed drastically.

They were surrounded by dynasty battleships. All the barrels were aimed at their spaceship.

"The Crimson Dynasty? Are they here to capture us‽"

Depressed Prince and the other guild members panicked.

"Did our whereabouts get exposed? But we did not bump into any buoys on the way! And how did they know we were planning to smuggle the virus out‽"

After being stunned for a few seconds, Depressed Prince quickly regained focus and yelled hastily, "Stop daydreaming. Everyone, log out now. Don't get…"

Before he finished, a calm voice appeared behind them.

"Don't get what?"

Everyone's body became stiff. They turned their heads slowly and looked at the middle of the cabin.

A tall, black silhouette had appeared in the spaceship. His lightning-filled eyes were coldly scanning them.

This face was way too familiar to the players!

"Bl-Black Star!"

Depressed Prince was in despair.

Everyone there was completely horrified. They originally thought that even if someone were to come to capture them, it would just be regular fleets and regular Supers. No one ever expected that someone as powerful and important as Black Star would personally act!

While shocked, Depressed Prince felt flattered for some reason.

The next moment, the lightning in Han Xiao's eyes flashed, and an electric shockwave exploded from his body.

Boom!

The energy shockwave slammed everyone into the wall.

Han Xiao controlled the damage so this shockwave was not powerful. Its main purpose was to force the players into Combat Status so that they could not log off any time they liked.

"I won't give up!" Depressed Prince clenched his teeth, made up his mind, and drew a long silver alloy sword. He then stabbed toward Han Xiao's throat.

The players were not afraid of death, so they dared to fight anyone. No matter how strong the opponent was, they would never stop resisting. In fact, Depressed Prince would rather get killed by Black Star. He would be able to revive somewhere else then and would not be captured.

However, this mindset was transparent in front of Han Xiao, who knew how the players thought.

He casually pinched the sword with his fingers, easily splitting it in half. He then grabbed onto Depressed Prince's head and slammed it onto the ground, giving him a Stunned debuff.

Han Xiao carefully controlled his strength, worried he might accidentally kill him. Although the players were much stronger than before, they were still as fragile as paper in front of him.

Han Xiao did not let the others go either. There was no need to use any machinery; he could easily beat these players into a pulp with his fists and legs. He took out an electromagnetic restraining chain and tied them all up.

The dynasty spaceships then approached and seized the spaceship. The dynasty soldiers boarded and searched it.

A ton of mechanical items piled up like a mountain. Han Xiao checked through and found a few communicators infected with the virus. He looked at the truly depressed Depressed Prince and the others and slowly said, "You're suspected of smuggling the Virtual Mutiny Virus, risking the public's safety and the universe's laws. You're now under arrest. Anything you'd like to say?"

"No, I'm sinful. People like me don't deserve to live in this world. I plead for the death penalty!" Depressed Prince said with a righteous tone.

Han Xiao rolled his eyes secretly.

This time, he suddenly paused, smiled, and said, "Are you guys very curious about how the dynasty found out you accepted the hire and set up a trap here?"

The Western Sword guild's people finally realized something. This was a hire from the black market and should have been very secretive. How did it get leaked?

"You have always been monitoring our communications?" Depressed Prince asked carefully.

"Nope." Han Xiao shook his head.

"Then… someone betrayed us?"

"Not that."

"What then?" Depressed Prince wondered.

Han Xiao smiled and looked at them. "That's because… the dynasty is the entity that hired you."

Like a streak of lightning, Depressed Prince and the others shivered. Their chins almost fell onto the ground, and their eyes opened so wide they were going to pop out.

"What?" Depressed Prince almost jumped up. He could not believe it.

"Our anonymous employer is the three Universal Civilizations‽ Impossible! What reason do you have to do that‽"

Han Xiao chuckled and casually lied.

"What do you think? The three Universal Civilizations knew all long there'd be people who ignore the big picture and try to hide and smuggle the virus. Therefore, the three Universal Civilizations also sent people to put up missions in the black market so that capturing those who took the hire is much easier. Do you really think that in such a crucial time like this, the three Universal Civilizations would just let the black market be?"

Depressed Prince was stunned. Complicated emotions such as frustration from being toyed with, rage from being tricked, and regret from falling for it rushed into his head. At this point of time, he just wanted to roar.

This was a conspiracy all along!

Looking at how furious they were, Han Xiao smiled even more.

Of course, the employer of these players was not the three Universal Civilizations, but he deliberately said that so the players would get the wrong idea.

As long as these people made posts on the forums and spread it, the chaotic evil players would calm down. After all, no one could tell for sure whether the hire they received on the black market was real or the three Universal Civilizations' trap.

Capturing these people would set an example and make things much easier.

In fact, the Great Mechanic Han was not lying just for that. He really wanted to do something similar.

However, in order to do that, he first had to control the black market. Otherwise, in order to protect their own name, the black market would definitely not cooperate with this plan.

All kinds of thoughts flashed past. Han Xiao took out the Spacetime Amber and smiled kindly at them.

"Since the evidence is sufficient… you guys can now start serving your sentences."

Depressed Prince was instantly horrified and started struggling with everything he had.

"No, no, no… I beg you, please don't use the Spacetime Amber. I beg for the death penalty. Please let me die! D-don't!"

However, Depressed Prince's struggle was useless. Watched by the rest, his expression was fixed, and he was locked in the Spacetime Amber.

Using the same method, Han Xiao sealed all of the Western Sword guild members who were begging to die, wiping out the entire guild.

That'll do. More than enough to intimidate the other players.

He had already tested the effects of the Spacetime Amber on the players. Of course, the players' consciousness would still be able to log in and out, but their body would not disappear like usual. Instead, it would be sealed inside the Spacetime Amber. This meant that they could not change the location to log in to, and no matter how many times the players logged in and out, they would only ever return to their body that was sealed inside the Spacetime Amber.

This meant that as long as they were sealed by the Spacetime Amber, the players could not use their own specialties to escape by logging in and out. It would be like their accounts were frozen due to them using cheats; they would never be able to escape.

One reason these players were still confident despite knowing the consequences of being captured was that they could revive somewhere else after dying, so the chance of them getting captured was very low. The other reason was they all thought they would be lucky enough, till disaster really arrived.

Han Xiao was not surprised about this. Just like some people who still used cheats despite knowing their accounts would be banned, they basically asked for it.

He did not plan to release the Western Sword guild easily. This was how he wanted to intimidate the other players. He wanted to show the others that their account could effectively be banned, so he could ease the tilted mindset of the players on the forums. This was like applying insecticide to his leek field so that his good leeks would not be spoiled.

He was not worried about these players making posts on the forums. After all, what else could they do?

Furthermore, given the characteristics of the players, these people would most likely take revenge. As long as they believed what they said, the only way they could take revenge would be to expose the so-called conspiracy and mess with the three Universal Civilizations' plan.

The situation was all within his control.

Han Xiao shook his head and smiled. He summoned Phillip to hack into the artificial intelligence of this spaceship and flipped through all the communication records.

The true identity of this anonymous employer was also a target he was going to go after.

Phillip was very efficient. Through the quantum network, he quickly found a clue leading to the anonymous employer.

"Master, hum… I've found it. This hire was published under a broker organization as the intermediate guarantor. This broker organization is one of the black market's managers. It has both a good name and reputation. It's trusted by countless black market mercenaries and employers. Basically, it's the Mercenary Alliance of the black market. Therefore, they should have information on this employer. However, this broker organization has been the black market manager for many years. As a very old intermediate guarantor, they won't leak their employers' names, hum…"

Han Xiao nodded. He had also heard about the name of this broker organization. Many hires on the black market came from them. It could be said that although this kind of organization called themselves neutral, without their approval, those anonymous hires regarding the virus would never have appeared on the black market.

They were undoubtedly responsible for this.

Looks like I'll have to start with this black market manager…

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He turned and tapped on the captain's shoulders.

"Depart. Destination, the headquarters of this broker organization in the Ancient Star Desert."

…

As the dynasty fleet was heading toward the next destination, filled with rage, Depressed Prince, who was sealed inside the Spacetime Amber, logged on to the forums and started making a post.

Just as Han Xiao expected, with the tone of a victim and the intention of warning the others as well as taking revenge on the three Universal Civilizations, Depressed Prince exposed the three Universal Civilizations' 'conspiracy'…

Chapter 1106: Intimidation

"The Painful Truth! The Mastermind Behind the Intelligent Plague Conspiracy!

"Emergency announcement! Those black market hires to transport the virus are a trap! They're very likely the three Universal Civilizations' bait!

"I'm a player who previously shared the job I accepted to transport the virus on the forums. An hour ago, along with my guild, we moved into the edge area of the Ancient Star Desert. Suddenly, we were ambushed by the three Universal Civilizations. Black Star personally wiped out our guild. Now we're all sealed in the Spacetime Amber, not knowing when we'll get out. I'm probably done for.

"At the start, I had no idea how the message got out. Luckily, Black Star thought we had nowhere to run and felt that there was no way we would leak the information, so he told me about the three Universal Civilizations' plan. I was totally appalled. Guess what, those among those anonymous employers on the black market, there are some who work for the three Universal Civilizations! Their goal is to lure out those who dare accept the mission and catch them one by one!

"It's horrifying. Currently, other than the people of our guild, no one else knows about this secret. I'm making this post because I can't bear to see other brothers get tricked by the three Universal Civilizations like we did. Therefore, I hereby am warning all of you not to fall into that old rascal Black Star's tricks!"

To prove that what he said was true, Depressed Prince even posted screenshots and videos of Black Star speaking.

As soon as the post was uploaded, like a lit match landing in a pool of oil, the emotion of all the players was ignited.

Immoral Trilogy: What a shock, so those hires in the black market are conspiracies‽

Important Things Need to Be Said Three Times: I knew it. It's not possible for those lawful factions to leave such a huge flaw. Turns out they had other plans. The three Universal Civilizations are really wise (cunning) in this kind of thing. Well played.

Military Chief: Black Star is Black Star. After all, like his name, he really does have a black heart.

Green Dot: Haha, I can't stop laughing. Where are those kids who were envying the Ancient Star Desert players? Why are they so quiet?

Human Slasher: If this is the case, the faction difference of this main storyline will be very clear. There are those of us who oppose the disaster, stand on the lawful side, and clean out the evil. If you support the disaster, you'll have to become an enemy of the three Universal Civilizations. I really envy the bravery of those players who choose the latter.

The lawful faction players all started to gloat, while those players who had supported spreading the disaster earlier all went silent and had nothing to say.

Especially those players who were lured by the high reward and had already accepted hires on the black market, they were all terrified. Most of them hastily gave up the mission, worried that they might be baited by the three Universal Civilizations too.

Calf: Let me see who's causing problems (Black Star looking out from the bush.jpg).

Army Commander's PP Big: Black Star: There, your account's gone!

Long Live the Boot Lickers: Alas, if not for OP, we'd still have no idea and end up getting wiped out… I won't say much, thank you, OP, for saving our lives. Cheers, bottoms up.

Adult Site Senior Member: In order to get this information, OP has made a huge sacrifice. Here's to all kind people having a good life. Ps: If OP decides to create a new account, I'll kindly sponsor 100 Enas.

Feidin's Fan Group - Dual Cannons: A moment of silence for OP.

Fishes Don't Pee: A moment of silence +1.

There were people who doubted the authenticity of the post, but after seeing the screenshots and videos Depressed Prince posted along with it, they all had to admit it was the truth.

The Depressed Prince's post alarmed the players. Many people were indeed shocked and became much warier of things.

He thought he successfully broke the three Universal Civilizations' baiting plan, when his actions were actually all part of Han Xiao's plan.

Seeing that so many players believed this 'conspiracy' and gave up missions to transport the virus, Han Xiao knew that this measure of his worked. He smiled in satisfaction.

Depressed Prince was of great help, so he was thinking about taking a few minutes off his sentence. Although, this guy had no idea.

…

In the Ancient Star Desert, Planet Strange Gold did not belong to any civilization. It had been taken over by a few financial groups many years ago and modified into a neutral galactic port. Afterward, the Galactic Black Market had taken over and made it into a transit supply station for gray organizations. It was quite famous in the Ancient Star Desert.

Tracks of tons of gray organizations and wanted criminals could be seen there. Some gray organizations even had their headquarters or subdivisions set up there. Due to some sort of unspoken agreement and deals, the Galactic Civilization silently approved of the existence of gray transit stations like this and did not send out soldiers to wipe it out. Although places like this were extremely chaotic, it was not completely lawless. The big organizations in the black market would usually set the laws.

The organization stationed in Planet Strange Gold was a member of the black market managers—Black Index, a broker organization.

There were many kinds of black market manager organizations, such as mercenaries, armed dealers, miners, and so on. Among them, the ones who had the biggest power were the brokers. They took the high-class path, swinging between different civilizations and building very complicated connection networks. They provided protection and assurance for the other black market organizations.

The Black Index was one of them, and their business range was even wider. Using the name they had built for themselves over the years, they provided assurance for the hires and biddings done in the black market. At the same time, they also functioned as the intermediate exchange. They were basically the bank of the black market.

Safety of funds was always a problem for the gray organizations, and the Black Index provided security and confidentiality for all funds transferred through them. An outrageous amount of money passed through them every single day and spread through the entire Galactic Black Market. Their power was reflected clearly just from this.

Of course, this much power required an equivalent amount of strength to maintain, which was even truer in the gray world, where only the law of the jungle applied. The Black Index had plenty of funds, so they used a lot of it on building a powerful military force. At the same time, they also had a Beyond Grade A protector behind them. These factors made sure the Black Index maintained its superior position among the black market managers.

The upper echelons of the organization were called Indexers. Their leader was called the Chief Indexer, and below this leader were the Second Indexer, Third Indexer, and so on. There was a total of five vice-leaders, all the way to the Sixth Indexer, each in charge of a certain area.

Inside the Planet Strange Gold subdivision of the Black Index organization, the Third Indexer stood before the floor-to-ceiling window of his office and looked up at the starlight in the dark sky. He was frowning.

His aide-de-camp who was wearing an elegant silver-black uniform walked into the room, saw him like this, and asked curiously, "Third Indexer, what are you thinking about?"

"Nothing… I just suddenly don't feel at peace."

The Third Indexer massaged the bridge of his nose. His mind was wandering off a little.

As a hybrid Eternal, the Third Indexer had the special talent of having a very sensitive six sense. He could occasionally roughly sense certain bits of the future.

Since a few days ago, he had started to often lose focus and feel uneasy, like something bad was about to happen.

"I shall bring you some medicine to calm you down," the aide-de-camp said and was about to turn around to leave the room.

"No need, I'm fine."

The Third Indexer called him back, turned around, and asked casually, "Tell me, do you have anything to report to me?"

"Well…" The aide-de-camp took out a report and said seriously, "I've noticed some rumors, saying that the three Universal Civilizations have been secretly putting up hires on the black market as bait to capture black market mercenaries."

"Where did you hear that from? Rumors on the net?" The Third Indexer frowned.

"No, no, there are no such rumors on the network of the Ancient Star Desert. I heard about it privately from some people, so I did some investigations and realized that this rumor got spread out from nowhere. I feel that this might cause problems, so I came to report it to you…"

The Third Indexer shook his head and said, "Your source of information isn't reliable, nor is it trustworthy. As guarantors of the black market hires, although we do accept anonymous employers to put out hires, we still do some investigations. Things like this will certainly damage our name. Maybe we can endure it happening once or twice, but if someone plans to keep using our name to carry out this kind of plan, there's no way the organization wouldn't find out about it."

"You're right. I've worried about it unnecessarily." The aide-de-camp nodded.

"There's nothing wrong with being wary about things like this. It's a good thing."

The Third Indexer continued to look outside the window and said with a serious tone, "We're the lighthouse of the laws of the black market. One thing we rely on is our powerful strength, and another is the brand name and reputation we've accumulated over many years. The savages of the gray organizations trust in our professional ethics, and that's our core competitiveness. No matter what… even in the face of death, we can't break the rules of integrity, confidentiality, fairness, and safety. Otherwise, we'd be damaging the very foundation of the organization, as well as the laws of the entire black market."

"Understood." The aide-de-camp took these words to heart with admiration.

Swoosh!

As soon as the aide-de-camp said that, a remote communication image suddenly popped up beside the two of them. The panicking face of an observation personnel appeared.

"Bad news! The radar has detected that a dynasty fleet is approaching. They did not attempt to hide their movements. Their destination is clearly Planet Strange Gold, and we did not receive any prior notifications!"

The Third Indexer's expression changed with shock. His sixth sense was tingling even more intensely.

Usually, the three Universal Civilizations would never visit a gray transit station like this so openly. Today, however, the dynasty fleet suddenly arrived. It was clear they did not come with friendly intentions.

He thought of the Intelligent Plague instantly—there did not seem to be any other reason the dynasty would go to them.

Nonetheless, the Third Indexer was not one to panic in the face of emergencies. Very quickly, he calmed down and said with a deep voice, "Ask around. Who's the leader of this dynasty fleet?"

The dynasty was extremely powerful, sure, but he was also someone very important with a lot of power and strength, and he had a Beyond Grade A protector behind his back. Therefore, the Third Indexer was confident enough to speak with the dynasty.

Having thought of that, he had made up his mind that if the leader of the dynasty fleet was not high in ranks, he would not feel a need to welcome their leader, and he would be waiting there for their leader to come to him.

The aide-de-camp made some calls. Suddenly, his entire body shook. He gulped and said while shivering, "T-Third Indexer, the commander of this dynasty fleet… seems to be Black Star."

As soon as he finished his sentence, the Third Indexer's expression changed dramatically, and he instantly lost his cool.

Without saying another word, he rushed out the door while hastily making orders.

"Quickly, prepare a carrier for me. I'm going to welcome His Excellency Black Star at the dock!'

If it was an ordinary dynasty officer, the Third Indexer might have wanted to maintain his arrogance.

However, it was Black Star who had come, the person who made the strongest protector of the black market part of his collection. How dare he stay there waiting for Black Star to come to look for him?

…

The dynasty fleet entered the dock. As soon as Han Xiao stepped onto the dock, he saw the Third Indexer and his subordinates welcoming him respectfully.

The two of them met, and Han Xiao did not say much, only mentioning that he had a deal he wanted to make and told the Third Indexer to lead him to the conference room to speak.

Accompanied by the cautious Third Indexer, they entered the subdivision of the Black Index and sat inside the conference room.

After sitting down, Han Xiao looked into the Third Indexer's eyes and said slowly, "You're a smart person. You should know why the dynasty has sent me, so I'll just cut to the chase. The Black Index has provided assurance and guarantees for anonymous hires, which led to a lot of black market mercenaries transporting the virus in the Ancient Star Desert, increasing the risk of the virus leaking. Now, on behalf of the Black Star Army and the Crimson Dynasty, I'm requesting you to temporarily stop providing such services and publicize the information of these anonymous employers to aid us in capturing them."

"Impossible!" The Third Indexer rejected it without hesitation. "This goes against the purpose of the Black Index. We can never leak the information of our customers. We…"

Han Xiao interrupted him and said with a more serious tone, "Is the purpose of a black market organization more important than the ruling of the three Universal Civilizations? Or has the Black Index made up its mind to spread the disaster and cause the entire universe to be filled with death?"

The Third Indexer hastily denied that. "Of course not. We've just been remaining neutral. What we've been doing has not changed since the Intelligent Plague erupted. We're purely maintaining a platform…"

"Don't try to convince me with this kind of excuse." Han Xiao tapped the table slowly. "Your inaction means your approval of others leaking the virus. Your inaction is equivalent to helping the disaster spread. The current situation has no room for neutral parties. Be it me personally or the three Universal Civilizations, no one wants to see anyone being an opportunist during such a serious disaster."

Hearing this, the Third Indexer looked worried.

His bad intuition had come true. He felt that Black Star was using this as an excuse to take away the guarantor platform they had built up in the Ancient Star Desert.

If it was just Black Star alone, he would not be this powerless. However, Black Star had come under orders, which meant that he represented the three Universal Civilizations' attitude.

Sure, the Black Index's forces were spread across many Star Fields, but crushing it would still be a piece of cake for the three Universal Civilizations. Furthermore, the Ancient Star Desert was now in quarantine, so there was no way he could even seek help.

The Third Indexer did not want to give in, but he had no other choice. He could not even contact the headquarters while being in the Ancient Star Desert, so he had no choice but to bring up his background.

"Your Excellency Black Star, are you sure you want to do this? His Excellency Uru is behind us. He's a Beyond Grade A just like you…"

Han Xiao found it quite funny. "Yo, what's this? Are you trying to threaten me or something? That's quite brave of you. Even disregarding the fact that your protector is away and can't make it back here, so what if he could?"

The Third Indexer clenched his teeth, looked at the dynasty soldier beside him, and said, "I know what you're trying to do. You're trying to use this opportunity to infiltrate the black market and take control of some channels. The three Universal Civilizations now approve of your actions, but what happens when the disaster is over? They won't watch you reach out this far, so they will certainly take what you've obtained. Hence, whatever you're doing now, the three Universal Civilizations will always be the ones benefiting in the end. Why put in so much effort?"

"How dare you try to pick His Excellency Black Star and the dynasty apart!"

The dynasty soldier beside him was furious and instantly pulled out his firearm, pointing at the Third Indexer's head.

This time, Han Xiao raised his hand, signaling for the dynasty soldier to holster his weapon. He smiled and said, "You don't know me. Although I always chase after profits, I will never pick the wrong side on this kind of huge matter."

The Third Indexer clenched his teeth and continued trying. "The three Universal Civilizations are only allowing you to be in charge of this matter because they're using you. You'll be the one who ends up having beef with the black market organizations, and the three Universal Civilizations will be the ones taking the victory fruits after. Is the powerful Black Star willing to be used like this?"

"Hehe, fighting evil is everyone's responsibility, and I don't mind having beef with people because of it." Han Xiao smiled with mockery. "Furthermore, using each other is a more suitable way of saying it. It's still uncertain who'll benefit more from it in the end."

He had made up his mind on this matter. Rather than calling it a negotiation, it was more like a notification instead.

The Ancient Star Desert was now an isolated island. During the disaster, the illusion of equality was completely ripped away, exposing the dictatorship behind it. With the three Universal Civilizations backing him, he had nothing to fear.

In situations like this, other than those Galactic Civilizations under protection, the rest of the private organizations were all just food for the big sharks. They would face their demise if they refused to cooperate.

Seeing this, knowing that there was nothing he could do and no words would change the situation, the Third Indexer gave up, leaned back, and looked hopeless.

"I can't resist anyway. The connections the Black Index has in the Ancient Star Desert are all yours…"

Hearing this, the aide-de-camp looked at the Third Indexer with disbelief.

That's not what you said earlier. What happened to never breaking the organization's integrity and name even in death‽

Noticing the aide-de-camp's look, the Third Indexer threw back an angry look at him.

What, can't I bullsh*t?

Black Star is right here, I treasure my life very much. Go ahead and die for the organization if you want to!

Chapter 1107: Filling the Flaws of Science with Superstition

The Black Index's Planet Strange Gold subdivision controlled half of the Galactic Black Market's hires and funds in the Ancient Star Desert. Controlling this place meant that half of the black market's movements were being monitored.

In the main control room, the Third Indexer ordered the operators to open up the firewall and let Han Xiao inject his data needle, planting a ton of surveillance programs while looking at the documents behind recent anonymous hires in the black market.

The Black Index's internal database had records of the true identities of some employers, most obtained through investigation. As the intermediate guarantor, the reward of the hire would go through the Black Index before going to the mercenary. Therefore, following the source of the funds, it was not difficult to find the identities of the anonymous employers.

Han Xiao quickly copied the tons of documents the Black Index had accumulated in the quantum network. He glanced at the wary Third Indexer beside him and joked,

"You guys aren't as reliable as you say you are. Tsk, you've been secretly investigating the identities of those anonymous employers. These documents are all their weaknesses. Don't tell me you guys collected these for fun."

The Third Indexer wiped away the sweat on his forehead and said, "It's just to audit the reliability of the trade and assess the employer's integrity. We only collected this information but never shared it with anyone. As for weaknesses… ahem, well, we're in the black market industry, so we must have some leverage."

"Got it, got it. It's the black market. After all, no one is clean." Han Xiao chuckled.

The Third Indexer had no choice but to laugh together with Han Xiao, bowing and showing a lot of respect.

The dynasty fleet was right on this planet. The only thing he could do was to be obedient.

Han Xiao caressed his chin and said, "Speaking of which, that reminds me, I brought the dynasty fleet here, and you came to welcome me. There are a lot of people on this planet, so this news will get out sooner or later. There'll definitely be rumors saying you're being threatened by the three Universal Civilizations, which will lead to the mercenaries and employers lying low for a while, and the three Universal Civilizations' plan to lure out the uncertainties will end up being less effective."

"I-I suppose." The Third Indexer did not know how to respond.

"I think you should feel good about that." Han Xiao smiled. "You might even send people to spread the news on the black market, saying the Black Index is being forced to do this, warning the other black market members not to use the platform for hires. This way, the damage done to your organization's brand will be reduced."

The Third Indexer felt bitter. He did indeed think of that. Although he was forced to obey, he still wanted to control the damage.

"Don't worry, I won't stop you from doing that."

Hearing this, the Third Indexer was confused and asked, "Didn't you control us to secretly monitor the black market and lure out the uncertainties? If the news of us not being reliable gets spread on the black market and people stop using our platform, what's the point of you taking over?"

"Sigh, looks like you're very adept to identity changes and have entered the position of a partner very soon. You've even started to think for us." Han Xiao laughed and clapped.

The Third Indexer's expression became stiff. He was angry but did not dare to express it.

Han Xiao raised his brows, summoned the dynasty officer, and said with a smile, "Later on, split up the dynasty fleet to head to any gray transit station in the Ancient Star Desert where a black market organization is stationed. Remember to do it as openly as possible and let everyone see you."

Hearing this, the Third Indexer roughly figured out Black Star's plans.

"You're deliberately letting the black market know that the Black Index has been compromised. You'll then negotiate with every black market organization to create an illusion of the three Universal Civilizations having full control of the entire Ancient Star Desert black market so that most people will become suspicious and cautious, right?"

This way, even if the other black market organizations did not fall into Black Star's hands, with the Black Index as an example, those employers looking for confidentiality and safety would definitely no longer take the risk, fearing being exposed.

Black Star could certainly force all the black market organizations in the Ancient Star Desert to compromise, but he chose to take another path. From the way the Third Indexer looked at it, this was Black Star giving himself a way out. This method was not as aggressive and would not lead to Black Star offending all the black market organizations, so the three Universal Civilizations would not end up easily taking over the fruits of victory.

Some black market organizations might even think of it as Black Star holding back on them.

"I got it." The Third Indexer hesitated. "This method is indeed less aggressive, but there are both pros and cons…"

Han Xiao did not respond. He knew what he meant.

Aggressively taking over all the black market organizations was the best way to lure those uncertainties out. He would be able to capture a ton of people who were trying to cause trouble. Comparatively, although this method required much less effort, it would cause most people to be alarmed and not make a move.

However, from the way he looked at it, there was no way to capture all the uncertainties. No fish could survive in an absolutely clean pond.

As the saying went, for a high enough reward, there would always be someone willing to take the risk. If those black market mercenaries were not completely discouraged, someone would definitely be willing to risk it for the huge profits, which would lead to the Ancient Star Desert becoming a mess. In the end, the three Universal Civilizations would have no choice but to put a lot of effort into chasing after them. This was the con of the more aggressive method.

Furthermore, when more of these people were captured, the fact that the three Universal Civilizations had controlled the black market would still be exposed. Therefore, he might as well make it public in the first place to not give anyone the thought that they might be lucky enough to pull off a fluke, making them afraid of the consequences. This way, the plan would turn from luring out those who would cause a problem to preventing those people from appearing in the first place, reducing the number of people willing to take the risk from the roots.

Indeed, luring them out would be effective, but it would also produce more uncertainties. As the rulers, a more righteous method was more suitable for the three Universal Civilizations. Using dirty tricks like this might be okay once in a while, but it was not suitable in the long run.

Han Xiao put those thoughts aside, glanced at the Third Indexer who was looking very obedient, and said, "You're not bad. I thought you'd only compromise after a slaughter. I didn't think you'd be so understanding as to not even give me a chance to do that."

"… As long as you're satisfied," the Third Indexer replied with resignation.

"However, I do like you more when you are defiant. Come, show me again," Han Xiao joked.

When was I ever defiant?

The Third Indexer complained about Han Xiao's humor in his mind but still straightened his back as he was told on the surface.

This time, Phillip had completed filtering the documents and identified a ton of employers requesting to transport the virus.

"Report this list to the three Universal Civilizations. Have their troops cooperate with the operation to destroy these organizations."

Han Xiao glanced through it.

The data was very detailed. The employers were from all kinds of industries. For these people, he did not plan to hold back. While making them examples for the others, he could farm the Mission Rating of [Intelligent Plague] at the same time.

He searched through for a while and found an organization that hired Immortals multiple times. This was a black market arms dealer named the Kepel Financial Group. They had hired Depressed Prince too.

"I shall deal with this organization personally. Remember to publicize the execution process on the net."

On the dock of one of the Kepel Financial Group's Ancient Star Desert bases, cargo boxes were being loaded onto the ships. Kepel the Fifth was patrolling with his subordinates.

"How long before we can take off?"

"About two hours."

"Speed up as much as possible." Kepel the Fifth's tone was a little impatient.

About seven days ago, the dynasty fleet had visited the Black Index. This message was only spread out yesterday. All the anonymous employers who were giving out missions to transport the virus were appalled and instantly tried to save themselves.

Kepel the Fifth felt uneasy, too. Therefore, he decided to abandon this base and transfer his assets.

Currently, he was making his men empty the base.

While he was anxiously waiting, an observation officer sent him an urgent message.

"Alert, the exterior fleet has discovered a small Crimson Dynasty fleet approaching. We've sent a communication request but received no response."

"The three Universal Civilizations' men have come‽" Kepel the Fifth was startled. Together with a group of officers, he hastily walked to the window and looked out into cosmic space. A few scattered dynasty spaceships appeared in their vision.

"There don't seem to be a lot of people?"

"They don't look like they're here to fight."

Seeing this, Kepel the Fifth was slightly relieved.

Since there were so few spaceships, he felt like they were more there to ask questions or negotiate.

Having thought of that, Kepel the Fifth adjusted his clothes to look more formal. He then ordered with a deep voice, "Frigates, standby. Send a communication request in my name. I'll speak with them and see their intentions."

However, as soon as he said that, the dynasty spaceships stopped a distance away.

"Hmm? Why did they stop?" Kepel the Fifth was confused.

However, the next moment, countless machines appeared out of thin air afar, quickly assembling into an enormous human-shaped machine that was wearing a cape and holding a longsword in its hand. It was so enormous that even the entire base was smaller.

"That's…"

Before Kepel the Fifth and the others recovered from their shock, this enormous machine suddenly hurled the long sword forward, which easily sliced through all the frigates in its path like a hot knife cutting through butter, heading right toward the base.

At this instant, including Kepel the Fifth, all the people on the dock stopped what they were doing and stared blankly at the gigantic mountain-sized blade that was fast approaching.

Their minds had all gone blank.

Swoosh!

The Celestial Punishment Edge easily penetrated the Kepel base. The blue psionic storm on its blade turned the base wreckage into dust. It was like a firework.

As if it had met no resistance at all, the blade continued to penetrate into the desolate planet below the base, through the ground, and came out the other side of the planet. It had given this planet a hole that extended from one side to another.

The enormous amount of psionic energy left by the Celestial Punishment Edge caused irreversible chain reactions inside the planet. Lava rushed up, and red cracks started appearing on the surface.

The next moment, a blinding white light erupted. The entire desolate planet expanded from within and shattered instantly.

The shockwave from the explosion expanded, but the Mechanical Deity raised its Emperor's Cape and blocked the shockwave completely.

At the same time, it raised its hand. The Celestial Punishment Edge moved through the energy storm of the planet's explosion in an arc and returned to its hand.

"This thing is quite powerful."

Han Xiao somewhat understood why the Tyracles were so passionate about building equipment for the Mechanical Deity.

There was no other reason except for it being so damn cool.

After playing with the Celestial Punishment Edge for a bit, the Great Mechanic Han reluctantly deactivated the Mechanical Deity and returned to the ship.

"Run a scan to see if there's still anyone alive."

What's the point?

The powerful light of the planet's explosion reflected on the dynasty soldiers' pale faces. The cabin was dead silent, as if they could hear each other gulping in fear.

"Phillip, did you record that?"

"Yes, hum…"

"Upload it to the net, to intimidate those with ulterior motives and show them the consequences of what they might want to do."

Han Xiao waved his hand casually.

He did not plan to even speak with this organization. There was more than sufficient evidence. There was no point speaking, so he directly wiped them out with a slash to express his firm attitude.

After dealing with this small matter, Han Xiao waved at Harrison and the others, who were shivering by the side, signaling them to come over.

Harrison had just witnessed Han Xiao casually shattering a planet with his own eyes. The impact of it completely shattered his mental preparations for it before it happened. Even though he clearly knew Black Star was one of the strongest in the universe, he was still astonished.

Harrison's teeth were shaking. He cautiously approached Han Xiao and stuttered, "Y-Y-Y-Your Excellency Black Star, what can I do for you?"

"Why are you so nervous? I won't bite." Harrison chuckled and patted Harrison's shoulder. "Discouraging illegal dealings is about done, so looking for the virus core needs to be brought forward. I want to ask you, where do you think the virus core is hiding?"

"H-how would I know?"

"Don't be so nervous. Just make a random guess. Where do you think it's hiding?"

Harrison calmed himself down, regained focus, and cautiously said, "Previously, you said that the virus core is just a pre-designed program used to monitor the overall infection progress of the virus. This means that it is definitely exchanging information with the other viruses, so to hide itself, it can't possibly be the terminal of that information exchange, or it would have been found long ago. Therefore, I think that through recording all the routes the viruses are sending data through and finding the overlapping spots among them, that's where the virus core might…"

Han Xiao interrupted him and said, "The three Universal Civilizations thought of this long ago and have been doing exactly that. Each virus sends out a large amount of fake data every now and then. The routes are extremely complicated, and there are too many overlapping points. Therefore, there's no way but to filter them. However, not only is the location of the virus core very difficult to find, it seems to be changing randomly. This is why the three Universal Civilizations have not been able to find it."

"T-then I don't have any ideas and, unfortunately, won't be able to help you."

"No, I don't need your ideas." Han Xiao smirked. "Next time the three Universal Civilizations come up with the new set of overlapping points, I need you to choose some of them. What if you're lucky enough to find it right away?"

"Stop joking with me…" Harrison was anxious.

"I'm not joking. Think about it, you dug up an antique randomly, and it just so happened to be the source of such a dangerous disaster. From a certain viewpoint, your luck is through the roof."

Harrison scratched his head and realized that did make some sense.

Indeed, I always seem to have been quite lucky. No matter what I asked my family's financial group to invest in, it always ended up making money. If not because making money is too easy, I wouldn't have come out looking for excitement by doing archaeology…

Han Xiao did not know what he was thinking. Seeing that he was daydreaming, he gave him a few words of encouragement and started pondering in his mind.

He had a lot of faith in the Advanced Luck Glow. Even if it failed the first time, if he let Harrison try a few more times, the chances of succeeding were still much higher than others.

Furthermore, Han Xiao even planned to make a request to the three Universal Civilizations to contact the outside world, so he could look for Floating Dragon's old man Aesop to read some feng shui for him.

No matter how well the virus core hid, everyone was equal in front of luck and prophecy.

Since science did not cut it, he planned to make it up with superstition!

Galaxy Calendar Year 731 March 9th, Black Star visited the Black Index organization, which controlled the black market, as a Crimson Dynasty emissary.

The two sides carried out a friendly and peaceful meeting regarding the three Universal Civilizations' control of the disaster, successfully exchanging information. In the end, they happily came to an agreement.

The Black Index's Ancient Star Desert person in charge, the Third Indexer, expressed that be it a black or white faction, every powerful civilian organization had a responsibility to protect the universe. Preventing the Intelligent Plague from spreading was a duty every galactic resident should carry out. Hence, the Black Index was willing to fully support the three Universal Civilizations' operations.

March 17th, Black Star announced that the Kepel Financial Group had hidden the virus. He wiped Kepel out with one attack, shocking the other organizations.

With this incident as the signal, the three Universal Civilizations worked together and wiped out tons of private organizations that were suspected to have hidden the virus over the next month.

In April, the Crimson Dynasty fleet visited all the black market organizations in the Ancient Star Desert, seemingly gaining control of all the black market connections in the Ancient Star Desert.

Black Star upheld the rules of no negotiations and no compromises. He led his fleet on frequent attacks, reducing the number of smugglers by a large amount.

June 25th, the research group led by Manison created the first version of the special anti-virus and scanning tool, which was widely used.

In July, the Intelligent Plague was briefly under control. The three Universal Civilizations started to search for the virus' core.

Chapter 1108: Great Machinery Sage

Han Xiao's fleet had stopped at the Crimson Dynasty's temporary Ancient Star Desert military base to resupply and repair their armor.

Over the past few months, using the information he had gained through the black market channels, he had done a cleansing of the restless gray organizations in the Ancient Star Desert, creating an image of him being merciless. This successfully made the rest not dare to take the risk. They chose to obey and stopped touching the Virtual Mutiny Virus. Hence, the Star Field's situation was getting better.

While doing so, Han Xiao was also trying to find the virus core. He had let Harrison choose the overlapping data points multiple times with his Luck Glow.

However, for once, the Luck Glow did not work, and he was never able to find the virus core. Even old man Aesop could not 'prophecy' his way to the location of this thing.

He was in charge of cleaning out the uncertainties, while Manison was focusing on researching. Both sides had gotten some results. Currently, the Intelligent Plague was somewhat under control.

"… I thought you guys would be able to come up with the antivirus very soon. Turns out it took you months. Now this doesn't suit your level, Manison."

Inside the lounge for upper echelons of the military base, Han Xiao was chatting with Manison's remote projection while snacking on some kind of seed similar to the Chinese melon seeds.

Manison shook his head and said, "Analyzing the virus' code wasn't easy. Plus, we had to prevent the virus from erupting, so we had to go around the conditions that would trigger it. We had no choice but to be extremely cautious. That's why it took us some time."

Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanics could easily eliminate the Virtual Mutiny Virus, but the difficulty of turning their own ability into a tool that anyone could use was a completely different matter. For example, a man would be able to naturally walk and run, but if he was asked to build a robot that could do the same, he would definitely not be able to come up with it as easily.

"What are the three Universal Civilizations planning to do now?"

"The problem is still the conditions of triggering the virus eruption. In order to make sure it doesn't erupt, we can't cause the infection speed of the virus to plummet all of a sudden. Therefore, even if there are firewalls, we can't use them on a wide scale. For the time being, they can only be installed after all the infected nodes are cleaned. This is also the reason that despite the three Universal Civilizations' control, the Virtual Mutiny Virus has still infected more than half of the network nodes in the Ancient Star Desert over the past few months."

"If I recall correctly, cleaning out the virus on a large scale will also trigger it, right?" Han Xiao asked.

"Yes," Manison replied. "Therefore, the scanning tool the three Universal Civilizations have asked us to build can't be discovered by the viruses. They plan to secretly lock onto all the infected nodes by scanning them, then implant antivirus tools with precision to clean all the infected nodes simultaneously. Afterward, they'll install firewalls immediately to prevent repeat infections. This way, even if the virus ends up erupting, the damage will be minimized."

"Although this method is a little bit troublesome, it's safest."

Han Xiao had no objection to the three Universal Civilizations' plan. It sounded quite reliable.

However, he had a question in mind. In his previous life, the three Universal Civilizations should have done exactly the same thing, so how did it still turn into a disaster for the entire universe in the end?

Could it be because I've done my job too well and changed some unknown details? For example, someone should have transported the virus out but has been stopped by me?

Han Xiao put this question to the back of his mind.

Manison did not know what Han Xiao was thinking. He continued to explain the three Universal Civilizations' plan.

"Therefore, we have made various preparations. One is this plan to wipe out all the virus; the other is to locate the virus core. The virus core is the controlling terminal for most eruption triggers. As long as it's eliminated, the risk will be reduced even further, and we won't have to worry about the viruses erupting when we attempt to wipe them out."

"Do you guys still have no leads on the virus core?"

"It's hidden itself too well." Manison shook his head and did not say much.

Han Xiao snorted softly. He felt that old Manison was not telling the truth. However, there was no point exposing him. The two of them were competitors in this respect. Manison would not be so kind as to share clues with him.

Out of all the Beyond Grade A Mechanics who had come to help, all of them wanted to obtain the virus core to learn the full secrets of the Virtual Mutiny Virus technology.

Now that the pandemic was under control and the most dangerous period had passed, the competition revolving around the virus core had come to the surface. Even the three Universal Civilizations intended to compete for it.

Han Xiao knew that he would not be able to get any information from Manison, so he skipped this topic and said, "Now that your work is done, are you still planning to stay in the research department?"

"No, I'm planning to go and take a walk. One reason is to find clues about the virus core. Another is that I plan to go and take a look at the Machinery Faith."

"Machinery Faith?" Han Xiao's brows raised.

He had never forgotten that the two of them had conflicts of interest due to this religion. Manison was always in the position of the main god. He wanted to keep most of their faith to himself to maintain the [Key of Adeptus Mechanicus] bonuses.

For that, Manison had struck more than a decade ago and made Han Xiao suffer a slight loss.

Back then, he had chosen to use his soul talent of not competing. After that, he had been growing stronger while keeping a low profile, at the same time maintaining a decent relationship with Manison.

"What, you have some thoughts about it?" Manison sounded like he was smiling, but he was not.

"Humph, can't I?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

"Compared to about ten years ago, you have indeed improved. However, it's still too early for you to want to challenge me again," Manison said coldly. "Don't envy what's mine. We have quite a good relationship now; keeping things this way is good for you. Don't say I never warned you. I don't wish to see you have any contact with the Machinery Faith in any form."

Then, the green remote projection disappeared, and Manison had hung up the communication.

Han Xiao's face turned black. He was a little irritated.

What a b*stard this guy is, changing his attitude like flipping pages of a book.

Also, when did the Machinery Faith become yours?

Shameless!

Speaking of, it's already been more than ten years since I last fought him…

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and pondered.

He opened the interface, looked at the huge amount of EXP he had accumulated, and felt assured.

The Black Star Cup had been going on all this time, giving him bonus EXP for the past few months, which had stacked up to quite a huge amount. He did a slight calculation—it was roughly enough for him to level up from level 320 to between 335 and 337.

Just a portion of this much EXP would be enough for him to obtain enough Potential Points to max all his class knowledges.

After farming for so long, I feel like I can have a rematch with Manison…

Han Xiao had decided to take a step back more than ten years ago because he wanted to become stronger first. Now that he had improved, his restless mindset once again seized control.

The competition around the Machinery Faith was one thing, but to Han Xiao, the other reason was the main reason.

I'm not happy. I have to fight that old man!

Last time, I was weaker, so I put up with it, but it's never too late for revenge!

In the past, you came to me and bullied my Phillip. Now, I have reason to be confident, so it's my turn to initiate the challenge and see the difference in our strength.

Due to the existence of the Beyond Grade A Association, the strength difference between individuals also affected the weight of their words. Although Manison's term was still long, he could totally make some early preparations for the next election.

Also, it was because of the development union that he did not have to worry about Manison's retaliation. As the president, Manison had to set an example and not cause trouble secretly, or it would go against the purpose of the development union.

Although Manison provided some help to him during the attack on Hila, it was more of a win-win. To Han Xiao, favors and beef did not cancel out each other. He would repay Old Man Manison for what he did in the future at most.

All kinds of thoughts flashed past Han Xiao's mind. He brought up the ability list, selected a bunch of blueprint abilities, threw in EXP, and maxed out their levels. Notifications kept popping up on the interface.

You have maxed the level of one ability. You have received 1 Potential Point.

You have maxed the level of one ability. You have received 1 Potential Point.

Currently, Han Xiao only had three Ultimate Knowledges that were not at their maximum level. [Ultimate Mechanical Engineering] was at Lv.3, [Mechanical Life Tinder] was at Lv.4, and [Endless Material Science] was at Lv.2. They required a total of 144 Potential Points. Even though he still had some Potential Points left, he still had to max out more than a hundred abilities.

The more max level abilities he had, the higher the cost of leveling up the rest of the abilities, including even the low-level blueprints. Though, the cost did not increase as much as leveling up himself. This meant that although the players could utilize different levelling strategies, they would not have too much of an impact. They would still have to put in a lot of effort to receive more Potential Points.

His EXP gauge went down very quickly. Very soon, he had already spent more than half of it. When his remaining EXP was only enough for him to level up to 326, he finally had 144 Potential Points.

Although leveling up would also give him Potential Points, he did not want to wait any longer. He had tons of leeks and a continuous source of EXP, so being so calculative was not something he needed to do.

Furthermore, Han Xiao was also very curious as to whether Potential Points would still be of any use when all his knowledges were at the maximum level.

Looking at the 144 Potential Points, Han Xiao took a deep breath and spent them all on the last three Ultimate Knowledges.

You have leveled up [Ultimate Mechanical Engineering] to Lv.5 (Max)!

You have leveled up [Mechanical Life Tinder] to Lv.5 (Max)!

You have leveled up [Endless Material Science] to Lv.5 (Max)!

All 60 of your Class Knowledges have reached the max level!

You have received 1 [The First Sanctum] Ability Fragment.

You have acquired talent [Great Machinery Sage]!

[Great Machinery Sage]: +1.25 Total Machinery Affinity bonus multiplier; +3 levels to Mechanic Class related abilities (Not limited by the ability's max level); +40% production, enhancement, and repairing ability; +60% Virtual Technology effects; +15% Machinery basic attributes; +120% Machinery production speed; +3,000 INT.

Remark: "In the machinery territory, you're an all-knowing sage."

The current Potential Points in your possession and the Potential Points you obtain in the future can be turned into 'Awakening Points' at a 1:1 conversion rate.

Usage I: 1 An Awakening Point can be converted into 100 Free Attribute Points (Irreversible).

Usage II: 1 An Awakening Point can be used to level up one maxed level ability by 1 level (Irreversible).

Usage III: Awakening Points can be used to increase the awakening process of Unique Talent. The amount increased by every 1 Awakening Point depends on the level and grade of the Unique Talent (Irreversible). 100 Awakening Points can be used to activate the brief structure of a Unique Talent (Custom talent direction).

Usage IV: Awakening Points can be used to increase the grade of blueprints. The amount increased by every 1 Awakening Point depends on the level and grade of the blueprint (Irreversible).

Usage V: Awakening Points can be used to increase the progress of inventing a blueprint. The amount increased by every 1 Awakening Point depends on the level and grade of the blueprint (Irreversible).

Your [Ultimate Mechanical Engineering] has reached the max level. [Inspirational Creation] activated!

Woah! Han Xiao was thoroughly surprised.

[Great Machinery Sage]'s effects definitely matched how difficult it was to obtain it. Not only did it provide very comprehensive bonuses, but the bonuses were also all quite large. Its impact on his strength was probably on the same level as [Perfect Mechanical Sense], increasing his overall strength by about ten percent.

I wonder if the suffixes of the talents given when all class knowledges are at the max level is the same for all the classes…

The Magic Sage? Sounds fine.

The Psychic Sage? Now that sounds a little weird…

The Esper Sage? Hmm…

The Pugilist Sage? Forget it, the Muscular Sage is definitely much better.

The talent was within Han Xiao's expectations, but the new use of Potential Points surprised him. No player in his previous life could level up all their abilities to the max level. This was a first even for him.

His Potential Points were now Awakening Points.

He carefully read its uses. The more he read it, the more excited he got. Compared to the one and only use the Potential Points had, the uses of Awakening Points were much more diverse.

Converting them into Free Attribute Points and increasing the upper limits of his abilities were clearly very practical and needed no further explanation, but what he was more impressed by were the other three functions.

Increasing the blueprint's grade seemed to be able to give him a stable stream of Gold blueprints.

For example, if he kept throwing Awakening Points into just an ordinary low-level pistol blueprint, given enough Awakening Points, this blueprint might turn into a Gold blueprint!

And the type of blueprint would not change too much. It would only turn from a gunpowder pistol into a portable Planetary Obliteration weapon.

The Awakening Points could also be used to increase the progress of inventing a blueprint, which could be used together with [Inspirational Creation].

[Inspirational Creation] had been gathering dust in the interface. The prerequisite for activating it was max level [Ultimate Mechanical Engineering]. The effect of this ability was to use EXP to assemble multiple blueprints into one or more improved or fused blueprints, with no upper limit on the number of blueprints. At the same time, a choice could be made for the improvement path of the fused blueprints, such as attack, defense, or support.

This ability made inventing blueprints more stable and ensured a result. It was also the only way the players in his previous life could invent Gold blueprints. However, the chances of doing so were extremely low. Most of the time, one would only obtain the brief structure of a Gold blueprint or Inspiration Fragments, which he could use Awakening Points to increase the progress of.

The last use of Awakening Point was what the Great Mechanic Han liked the most—it could be used to fuse Unique Talents!

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled as he mumbled, "Old Manison, Sorokin, and the others might have obtained their Unique Talents this way."

Chapter 1109: A Secret Only One Person Knows

One Unique Talent for a hundred Awakening Points, this cost was certainly high. However, at least it gave him a clear path. Han Xiao did not trust his luck at all. If he only relied on his luck, he probably would not have a wisp of a Unique Talent even in a hundred years.

He had a guess that the way of customizing would be probably the same as how he created his own Race Talent back when he advanced into Beyond Grade A, by selecting his preferences then randomizing from those given conditions. The Unique Talent obtained after fusing would only have a brief structure. He would need to spend more Awakening Points to activate it.

Potential Points turning into Awakening Points after all class knowledges were at max level was probably the same with other Mechanics such as Manison.

The difference was, unlike him, Manison and the others could not freely choose what to use the Awakening Points on.

Therefore, since the other Mechanics could not decide where to use the Awakening Points, they were probably random. He guessed it would probably feel like a sudden flash of insight for them.

Although the cost is quite high, at least it's a stable way to obtain Unique Talents.

Han Xiao was quite content. He had been eyeing this for many years, and now he had finally seen some hope.

However, the quality-price ratio of it was still uncertain. A hundred Attribute Points was equivalent to ten thousand Free Attribute Points, and his Intellect right now was not even thirty thousand despite it being his highest attribute. If he used all those Awakening Points on Free Attribute Points, it would be a huge improvement for him. He would only not make a loss if he were to get a Molding Talent level Unique Talent.

However, since it would be a Unique Talent, its effects would probably be decent. After all, its effects had to match how difficult it was to obtain it.

The Great Mechanic Han still remembered Sorokin's Unique Talent [Swindler—Sorokin], which gave him a direct twenty-percent bonus just on his Intellect and Mystery attributes, along with a bonus seventy-five percent Esper Ability strength and four levels to all his abilities. It was extremely powerful.

Old Man Manison's [Virtual Technology Innovation—Manison] gave him a 1.75-times multiplier on his Virtual Technology abilities, on top of his 'Indestructible Mechanic Empire' technology.

Both of these were at the Molding Talent level.

You never know until you try it. Although it's quite costly, I'll still have to get one and see how it is.

He had just leveled up more than a hundred blueprint abilities and spent all the Potential Points, so his current EXP inventory was not enough to get him another hundred Awakening Points.

Alas, Awakening Points… what a suitable name. Here comes another bottomless pit for EXP. Let's just think about it after my Promotion…

Han Xiao shook his head. His main goal of maxing the level of all his class knowledges was that one extra God's Trait Transformation Point during Promotion.

Now that he had completed that achievement, the Promotion at level 340 became his top priority again.

Other than these changes, the interface also mentioned that he had obtained another Ability Fragment of [The First Sanctum].

The Great Mechanic Han had already found a pattern. Whenever he overcame a certain threshold of the Mechanic class, he would receive a [The First Sanctum] fragment.

The first piece came from when he activated God's Trait Transformation, the second came from the first Universal Treasure he built, the third came from the fifth stage of his main class' God's Trait Transformation, and this was the fourth.

I can't wait to see how many fragments it takes to make it whole. Better not tell me it's a hundred.

Overall, he was very satisfied with the bonuses that came with maxing the level of all his class knowledges. It had given him a new path to grow. This was the biggest difference between him and the other Beyond Grade As—his growth path was crystal clear.

At the same time, with [Great Machinery Sage], he had more confidence in challenging Manison.

Last time, I lost in the virtual world; this time, I've got to fight him in the real world.

Han Xiao was looking forward to it with high morale.

This mindset could be simply explained as: "Stopped, the rain has; stopped, the wind has; now I think, I can do it again!"

Du du du!

While Han Xiao was getting familiar with the changes in his body, someone knocked on his door. Harrison walked in.

Over the past few months, Han Xiao had upheld his belief of not wasting any resource and did not let Harrison get away with doing nothing. Even though this guy was still guilty, Han Xiao did not mind and gave him a job as his temporary secretary.

Other than to find Harrison something to do, this was also because he wanted to have him around so that benefitting from his Luck Glow would be more convenient.

However, only from the results, not only did he not benefit from it, he even somewhat neutralized it.

Of course, the Great Mechanic Han would not admit this. He strongly believed that it was just that Harrison's Luck Glow did not have a good quality.

Feidin's Luck Glow still turned out to be the best. It remained unaffected no matter how much of a burden he was.

Seeing that Harrison had walked in, Han Xiao closed the interface and asked casually, "Anything to report?"

"Your Excellency Black Star, the dynasty fleet has told me to tell you that they're going to temporarily leave your team and go back to their usual groupings to execute other missions."

"What happened?" Han Xiao asked curiously.

"The captain has told me that this is a mission the dynasty upper echelons gave. Something has happened with a Star System civilization, and it's not suitable for you to deal with."

"What are the details?"

"I brought the information regarding the incident. Please take a look."

Harrison took out a set of data and displayed it on the virtual screen.

Han Xiao quickly looked through and understood.

In the past few months, the various civilizations of the Ancient Star Desert had come to understand the big picture and cooperated fully with the three Universal Civilizations' operations on the surface, not causing any problems like the black market once did.

However, when the three Universal Civilizations announced that the antivirus was complete, there seemed to be civilizations that felt that the pandemic was already under control and there would no longer be any dire consequences, so they started to stir things up.

There were three Star System Civilizations who were involved—the Tiger Race, the White Hair Race, and the Ferians. They were not transporting the virus but instead were suspected of using the virus to attack their enemies.

The Tiger Race and the Ferians were in the same Star System. Their territories were right beside one another. They were old rivals and often had conflicts with each other. The White Hair Race was in another Star System nearby, next to the Tiger Race but not the Ferians. Their relationship with the Tiger Race was relatively distant.

This was what the situation was roughly about. Not long ago, a machinery rebellion occurred on one of the important administrative planets of the Tiger Race. Those machines were infected by the Virtual Mutiny Virus, and because they had been disconnected from the network for too long, the trigger condition for the virus was met, and these machines were modified by the virus to hurt life forms.

The virus outbreak was only limited to this group of machinery. They were not large in number, and they could not connect to the internet either, so the other nodes of that planet were not affected. Therefore, the guards of the planet easily annihilated this group of machines. However, there were still civilian casualties.

After an investigation, a rather believable cause of this disaster surfaced on the network—that this group of machines were used by the Tiger Race to study the Virtual Mutiny Virus, and they accidentally lost control of them, which led to this disaster.

After this message got out, the Tiger Race civilians were in an uproar. Public opinion went out of control, and they all turned on their regime. The impact kept getting bigger.

The Tiger Race hastily said that this was just a rumor, that they did not study the virus at all. They said that these machines were hidden on the planet by an unknown force, who had calculated the day for the virus to attack to deliberately frame the regime and damage their credibility.

The civilians who were enraged felt this was nothing but excuses, so the Tiger Race had no choice but to request the three Universal Civilizations to judge it.

From the private report Han Xiao received, the Tiger Race explained to the three Universal Civilizations that this might be a conspiracy of the Ferians or the White Hair Race. The Tiger Race claimed that not only did both of those suspects want to frame them, but at the same time, the real culprit wanted to make the other suspect get the blame and stir up conflict between the Tiger Race and them, while they sat on the sidelines and benefited from it.

Both the White Hair Race and the Ferians had motives, but the Tiger Race was not completely trustworthy either. Hence, the three Universal Civilizations sent people over to investigate. Currently, the situation was still quite blurry.

The Star System Civilizations were protected by the Peace Treaty, so the dynasty did not let Han Xiao interfere with it. In this respect, the three Universal Civilizations did not allow any other organizations other than them to be the bullies.

The black market became obedient after what I did, but now the civilizations have started to cause trouble, I see…

Han Xiao frowned. Although this was not his responsibility, he still felt that something was not right.

He understood that the Ancient Star Desert being in lockdown had put the various local civilizations on alert, especially the Super Star Cluster Civilizations. The three bullies had lost their credibility during such crises long ago, so these civilizations had definitely prepared for the worst and gathered leverage. However, this was not helpful to the big picture at all.

I'll still have to deal with the virus as soon as possible. It can't wait. I shall use Bold Explorer one more time.

Han Xiao left the room and entered the warehouse.

Walking into the room, he saw the triangular device that had once stored the Virtual Mutiny Virus technology lying there immediately.

The dynasty had studied it but come up with no results. Seeing that Black Star had asked for it, they allowed Han Xiao to keep it with him.

Lately, as long as [Bold Explorer] was off cooldown, Han Xiao would use it on this triangular device.

Sadly, he had only seen a ton of scattered images; none were of any value. He had only found out part of the virus' origin at most.

The machinery civilization he saw from the first time he used Bold Explorer was the creators of the Virtual Mutiny Virus. This was indeed a weapon. The very purpose of building it in the first place was to use it on the unknown civilization that used the Planetary Obliteration weapon to annihilate this machinery civilization.

The program of the virus was set to killing life forms, and the machinery civilization was clearly not in range. It was like a high-level war weapon that dealt no damage to their kind.

This machinery civilization, or more of an intelligent civilization, was the same as an artificial intelligence civilization. All of its citizens were artificial intelligence lives, only more advanced.

These machines roaming the streets were all shells carrying intelligent lives. They were basically their carriers for walking in the real world. They designed their shells themselves, so there were hardly any two machines that looked the same.

Through using [Bold Explorer] time after time, Han Xiao had found out about some special language and symbols of this artificial intelligence civilization. However, after cross-referencing it, there were no related records in the three Universal Civilizations' database at all.

Either this artificial intelligence civilization was too ancient and even the three Universal Civilizations did not know about it, or it was an advanced civilization in the unexplored universe.

No matter which it was, it proved the fact that the source of the Virtual Mutiny Virus was a materialization phenomenon brought by an information state disturbance. Basically, it was a 'mirage' that interfered with reality.

Hope I can see something useful this time.

Han Xiao had Harrison beside him. He took a deep breath and prayed in his head to be blessed by the Luck Glow before placing his hand on the cold surface of the triangular device.

Buzz!

The next moment, the scene in his sights changed. He had come to a bright lab.

He looked up, and his eyes constricted with surprise.

In the middle of the room was the triangular device that was still not closed, showing the safe within it. Beside it was a group of mechanical lives who looked like researchers. They were operating their mechanical arms carefully and placing an almost transparent light-blue sphere of electrical sparks inside the device.

Is this when the Virtual Mutiny Virus was first created? Finally!

Han Xiao suppressed his joy and carefully observed this light blue sphere of electrical sparks. Tiny strings of electrical sparks swam in the air like a powerful electromagnetic field.

… This is the virus core?

Shouldn't it be a bunch of virtual data? Why is it a mass of electromagnetic energy?

Han Xiao was confused.

A monotonous electrical voice suddenly sounded. A mechanical life researcher by the side moved the camera to aim at him and said, "Experiment introduction: The Domino Virus, able to infect the quantum network and rewrite the fundamental logic of artificial intelligences. The current program is to kill all organic life forms.

"Raw material: One thousand mutated artificial intelligence lives with individual consciousness wiped, leaving only data structure and computing power. After 165 failures, the Domino Virus was successfully created. The virus' initial state has extremely high stealth, infiltrative, and infective abilities.

"Virus core: Pre-designed program with no individual consciousness. As the control center, it follows the logic given and controls the Domino Virus, monitoring the infection progress and activating the virus at a suitable time. It also has the ability to self-evolve. When the opponent has invented a targeted firewall, the virus core will automatically analyze the data and find the flaw with its strong computing power, continuously updating and enhancing the viruses to carry out a new round of infection.

"Remarks: From the second-generation virus onward, all viruses are active by default. Once infected, they will immediately rewrite the target's logic without an incubation period.

"Also, the virus core uses a lot of technology such as Virtual Soul, Bio-electricity Simulation, Electromagnetic Field Reformation, and so on. It has two forms. It can either exist as a virtual soul that lives in the quantum network or leave the quantum network at any terminal and enter the material world as an electromagnetic field life form.

"As the fundamental virus core is a virtual soul, when in the electromagnetic field state, it can infiltrate the quantum network at any time without coming into contact with any nodes. Due to this ability, the virus core has an extremely high escaping and hiding ability, as well as mobility.

"If used properly, one Domino Virus can shatter the majority of armed forces of a galactic civilization, causing the target's technology to regress many generations. Due to its extreme power, it requires caution when used. Currently, the Domino Virus is sealed up. Without authority, do not use…"

Han Xiao's eyes slowly widened.

He felt that his fragile mind had received ten thousand points of damage.

If not because he saw all this through [Bold Explorer], no one in the entire universe would have known the truth of the Virtual Mutiny Virus!

I'm the only one who knows all this now. Everyone else still has no idea!

At this time, a thought appeared in his mind.

Something's going to go wrong!

The three Universal Civilizations' plan isn't going to work!

This thing is tougher to deal with than we thought!

Chapter 1110: Countermeasures

At this time, the image of [Bold Explorer] stopped, and his vision returned to the warehouse.

He lifted his palm from the cold shell of the triangular device, stood in place, and looked at the device in silence.

He remained silent and did not move at all. Clueless as to what was going on, Harrison sensitively felt that the atmosphere had gradually become heavier, so he cautiously asked, "Your Excellency Black Star, did something happen?"

"…Nothing." Han Xiao regained focus. He glanced at him and then walked out of the warehouse with wide strides. Harrison quickly followed after him.

"Go do your stuff. You don't have to follow me."

"Oh, sure."

Like he had just been spared his life, Harrison quickly left.

Although Black Star did not do anything, just being beside him made Harrison feel extremely pressured.

After getting rid of Harrison, Han Xiao returned to his room and thought of the secrets he had just seen. His mind started working fast.

The Virtual Mutiny Virus's real name is the Domino Virus, it seems. What a terrifying weapon of war. Any organization that gets their hands on this technology will have the absolute upper hand in the information war…

He finally understood why the Intelligent Plague still swarmed the entire universe in his previous life. It turned out that it was not only because some people did not obey the three Universal Civilizations, but the three Universal Civilizations could not stop the Domino Virus' invasion.

It was not because their technology was inferior, but they did not have enough information and got caught by surprise.

After all, who would ever think that the Virtual Mutiny Virus worked this way?

If not because he had seen the virus' true identity from [Bold Explorer], he would probably have been in the exact same spot the three Universal Civilizations were in, still seeing the virus core as just a data program.

According to common sense, the virus core was supposed to just be the switch that monitored the entire infection progress. Hence, the three Universal Civilizations thought that they had nothing to be afraid of because they had already come up with the antivirus.

Of course, they had no idea that the virus core had the ability to update and evolve on its own. What they had under control at the moment was just the first-generation virus. As long as the core was not dealt with, there would still be the second generation, the third generation, and so on. Furthermore, there would be no incubation period next time; the virus would directly cause the machinery to rebel.

Not only was its infectiousness more horrifying than expected, but the virus core's ability to escape was also astonishing. It was not limited by its data state and could even enter the material world, forming an electromagnetic field as the body to carry itself and switch freely between the virtual and the real world. It was not afraid of being locked in the network at all.

As the foundation of its existence was a virtual soul, the virus core did not need any physical node to enter the quantum network. It was similar to how Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanics could enter the quantum network anytime they wanted. It would only need a node as the exit when materializing, meaning that it could teleport between the various nodes using the quantum network.

No wonder I couldn't find any traces of the virus core over the past few months. It's probably not because Harrison's Luck Glow isn't good enough, but it simply can't be caught on the network.

This ability was similar to his Void Dimension Jump. To the virus core, the quantum network was like another secondary dimension it could enter any time it wanted.

This artificial intelligence civilization probably did not reach the Universal Civilization level, since the three Universal Civilizations had the ability to analyze the Domino Virus completely. However, this needed time. Therefore, when facing this kind of weaponized virus, there would always be a period of time when there were simply no measures to deal with it.

The specialties of every civilization were different. There would also be some civilizations that would invent some new technology. For example, the Kunde Race's Spacetime Splicer. The three Universal Civilizations were inferior in the virtual virus technology aspect. After all, even the citizens of this civilization were artificial intelligence life forms, so this was clearly their strongest suit.

Wait a minute, if the three Universal Civilizations successfully defused the Intelligent Plague in my previous life, the virus core was definitely dealt with, so the three Universal Civilizations would have certainly obtained this technology… But why did they not use it when fighting the World Tree Civilization?

Han Xiao had some suspicions.

Could it be that… the virus core did not end up in the hands of the three Universal Civilizations in the previous life but somehow got obtained by someone else?

The next moment, the image of an old man appeared in the Great Mechanic Han's mind…

Mechanic Empire Manison!

This b*stard was the most suspicious!

One could not blame Han Xiao for thinking this way. Manison gave him too strong of an impression as someone who would do something like this.

Furthermore, the original material of the Domino Virus was mutated artificial intelligence life forms, and Manison just so happened to be in control of an artificial intelligence civilization.

It was horrifying to even think about it!

Han Xiao hastily shook his head, left these thoughts behind, and pondered.

The three Universal Civilizations made a lot of mistakes and learned a lot of lessons before finally understanding how the Domino Virus worked. Now that I've seen the truth in advance, I can skip that process and come up with prevention measures!

Having thought of that, Han Xiao was relieved.

In his previous life, the three Universal Civilizations had no choice but to learn through mistakes. Now that he, someone who had already watched the 'instruction manual' was there, the same thing did not have to happen again.

Maybe, the source of the virus might even be dealt with in the first generation. This way, the virus would have no chance of causing an outbreak, and the damage would be minimized!

When looking at it this way, the butterfly effects he had brought seemed to lean more toward the positive side.

The main issue now is convincing the three Universal Civilizations to change their plan of killing the virus on a large scale. If the virus core isn't dealt with, no matter how many viruses they kill, it won't make a difference. The virus core's ability is very tough to deal with, so I'll need the three Universal Civilizations' cooperation to deal with it…

Its ability to self-evolve was the most terrifying one. As long as that was dealt with, the rest would not be too much of a problem.

He was not afraid of the virus core escaping from the Ancient Star Desert. The quantum network of this Star Field was in lockdown. It was like an enormous LAN network, so it could not receive any feedback from the viruses within the Ancient Star Desert from outside it.

Even if the virus core really got out, it would still have to come back and log in to this sealed network to monitor the overall infection progress of the Ancient Star Desert.

This meant that even though the virus core could teleport in the quantum network, its range was limited to the Ancient Star Desert.

As for whether it would go out and spread the virus seed, Han Xiao was not worried either. Although the three Universal Civilizations lacked information, they were not useless. In order to prevent the virus from getting out, they were also doing large-scale scanning in the outside world.

If the first-generation virus infected the outside world, the three Universal Civilizations would notice it very quickly. There was no need for him to worry.

After analyzing for a while, Han Xiao had some ideas. He summoned Phillip and said, "Contact the three Universal Civilizations' pandemic command center as well as the other Beyond Grade A Mechanics for a meeting. Tell them I've made a huge discovery about the virus core…"

After receiving Black Star's invite, the three people in charge of the department, including Sidreun, and all the other Beyond Grade A Mechanic dropped their work and arrived at the Intelligent Plague Pandemic Command Center's conference room in the form of remote projections. They were all there to hear Black Star's discovery.

As soon as Han Xiao's remote projection appeared, Sidreun could not wait and asked, "Black Star, have you found the virus core?"

"Not yet, but I've made a shocking discovery."

Hearing that Han Xiao did not find the virus core, the people present were both disappointed and glad, followed by the curiosity of the huge discovery Han Xiao spoke of.

"What did you discover?"

"Here's the thing…"

Han Xiao cut to the chase and directly explained the rough mechanisms of the virus core, mainly emphasizing its ability to transform freely between the virtual and the real world, as well as its ability to self-evolve.

The threat of the Domino Virus was too high. Working together to defuse the pandemic was the top priority at the moment, so he did not plan to keep anything to himself.

After hearing what Han Xiao said, everyone present became silent. They looked at each other and did not even know what to feel.

Seeing this, Han Xiao continued and said, "Therefore, your plan to kill the virus on a large scale won't work. The threat of the Intelligent Plague will only be removed when the virus core is found, so I suggest you take action immediately…"

This time, Sidreun interrupted Han Xiao and said with a strange expression, "Black Star, I'd like to ask… where did you obtain this information from?"

The rest of the people present had the exact same thought. They all stared closely at Han Xiao.

They had to be doubtful. This information was way too detailed… so detailed it almost seemed made up!

Are you messing with us?

It's not impossible given how cheeky you are!

This matter is huge, and there's no room for anyone to play tricks. We have to confirm the authenticity of the information. How can we just believe you if you don't show us some proof?

"I knew you'd say that." Han Xiao was not surprised at all and went on to explain, "Actually, I discovered the virus core's traces in the quantum network not long ago. I was just about to try to track and capture it when it disappeared from the quantum network without any signs, and the lead I had ended there… I'm a peak Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanic, yet it could still disappear into thin air right under my nose without me having any idea of how it did it. Some of you surely know how difficult it is to do that. That's when I started suspecting that it's not just a data program."

"Then? How did you discover this information?" Sidreun asked.

"Your documents should have recorded that I have the ability to passively see the future. A few days after I noticed that the virus core isn't as simple as we thought it was, I had a vision and saw the future. I saw how the Intelligent Plague erupted and how it killed countless lives. At the same time, I saw the true identity of this virus core." Han Xiao shrugged. "So, if you're asking for proof, I really can't provide any."

"That's… you're making it difficult for us."

The various people in charge from the three Universal Civilizations all looked troubled.

It was not that they did not trust Black Star, but foresight was indeed inaccurate sometimes. This matter involved the safety of the entire universe. It was way too risky to bet all their chips on a prophecy without any real evidence.

Han Xiao had no other choice. He did not have any real evidence, so what he said was certainly not going to be convincing enough. He could only use his ability of foresight as an excuse. After all, [Bold Explorer] was not something he could really explain, and it was not even as convincing as prophecies.

Nonetheless, although what he said lacked any real proof and was not convincing enough, with his current position, even if the three Universal Civilizations' people would not believe him immediately, they would still definitely find ways to prove or disprove what he said. He did not have to do too much explaining.

In the end, if what Han Xiao said was proved to be false, the three Universal Civilizations would undoubtedly trust Han Xiao less in the future. However, before that, they would not instantly take Han Xiao's words as false.

After so many things had happened, the name, reputation, and respect Han Xiao had accumulated in the universe was more than enough to have the three Universal Civilizations take his suggestions seriously.

At this moment, Manison slowly said, "I feel that Black Star's foresight does make some sense. In fact, I discovered the virus core's tracks some time ago. It also disappeared right before my eyes, and I suspected that it was not just a data program."

Hearing this, Han Xiao's eyelids twitched.

Him saying he had found traces of the virus core was completely made up, but Manison was most likely not making it up.

I knew it. This old b*stard really did make progress but never said anything about it. If not because I tricked him today, he would never have publicized this information on himself.

Phooey! You say I don't have enough resolution, but you're even worse, hiding such key information!

The people exchanged looks and digested this impactful piece of information.

In the end, Sidreun coughed and said, "No matter what, we'll check out the content of His Excellency Black Star's vision. This is a very important piece of information."

While saying so, he secretly looked at Manison with derision.

The strongest Mechanic in the universe? How come you did not discover as much information as Black Star when the two of you had the same experience? Learn from him!

Manison looked directly ahead and acted like he did not notice Sidreun's gaze.

This time, Kant said worriedly, "If the Virtual Mutiny Virus is really as Black Star says it is, we're in big trouble. The firewall we've come up with this month will be useless before the next generation of the virus. By then, the disaster will sweep across the entire universe."

"Who in the world invented such a horrifying virus technology? Aren't they afraid of it biting themselves in the foot?" 'Mechanical Catastrophe' Francisco wondered.

"Whether what Black Star said is true or false, we'll still have to come up with a plan." The dynasty's ally Quantum Demon showed his support.

Han Xiao spoke again with a deep voice. "That's right. It doesn't matter if my foresight is accurate or not. It won't hurt giving it a try."

That's true… The people in charge from the three Universal Civilizations exchanged looks and nodded.

"What plan do you have then?"

"I wouldn't call it a plan. It's just a rough idea."

Han Xiao paused and looked around. Seeing that everyone's attention was on him, he said slowly, "The mobility of the virus core is too high, so it's very difficult to catch it. However, it still has limits. It can enter the quantum network anytime, anywhere, but when it leaves it and materializes, it has to choose a terminal node as the exit. This might be our opportunity.

"In order to receive feedback from the rest of the viruses, the virus core will return to the quantum network once every so often. This time, we really might have to cut off the network on a large scale and reduce the number of terminal nodes in order to restrict the range of the virus core's ability to teleport within the quantum network. This way, when the number of exits is reduced, we can station people at every node and set up traps.

"The people stationed at each node have to be Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanics with the knowledge of 'Virtual Paramount'. This is because after the virus core materializes, it doesn't have to come into contact with any node in order to re-enter the quantum network. Therefore, the chance will only last for a short instant. At the instant the virus core materializes, the Beyond Grade A Mechanic will use 'Virtual Paramount' to lock up the virus core's virtual soul so that it can't escape its body temporarily, then capture it together with its physical body.

"The technology to seal the virus core already exists. That safe prevents the virus from leaking, so it can certainly suppress the virus core's virtual soul and prevent it from entering the quantum network. As long as we parse that triangular container, we can obtain this targeted technology…"

Hearing this, the people all looked at Han Xiao with weird expressions once again.

Not to mention the feasibility of this plan of yours, just the fact that the people stationed at the nodes have to be Virtual Mechanics who have the knowledge of [Virtual Paramount], aren't you being too obvious?

Virtual Paramount is an ability only Divine Throne Mechanics of the Virtual branch can obtain, so clearly only peak Beyond Grade As. You're one, Manison is another, and that's it.

So, you're saying that only you guys can compete for the virus core. Even the three Universal Civilizations have to stand aside?

Are you really not tricking us?

Manison, however, smiled and fully approved of this plan.

"Black Star is right. To maintain peace in the universe, we are more than willing to step up. How many terminal nodes are there to set up traps for? How about this, I'm willing to deploy fifty million spare Lord's Avatars, ensuring that I can advent in any location the virus core appears. Is that enough?"

Chapter 1111: Manison: I Lack a Sense of Security

As soon as Manison finished speaking, the entire conference room went silent.

Everyone turned to Manison simultaneously.

You pulling our legs?

Han Xiao almost forgot to breathe. He sized Manison up with a suspicious look.

"You really have fifty million Lord's Avatars?"

"Maybe I exaggerated it a little," Manison joked.

Now that makes sense. Lord's Avatars are not mechanical soldiers. How can you build that many? I don't even have five thousa… ahem, fifty thousand spare Lord's Avatars.

Secretly relieved, Han Xiao asked subconsciously, "So, how many do you really have?"

"48,001,052… Oh, it's 48,001,054 now. Just built two more while we spoke."

"…"

The world went silent.

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. He was a little lost and completely did not understand why.

"Wait, I can understand no matter how many mechanical soldiers you've built, but what's the point of building so many Lord's Avatars? You can only descend on one at a time. How are you going to utilize all of them?"

"Oh, I lack a sense of security," Manison replied. "No harm building more."

The world went silent once again.

You're the damn Mechanic Emperor, lack a sense of security? I f*… okay, that's an indisputable reason.

Other than the word shameless, the people present could not find any other word to think of.

All Han Xiao wanted to do was blast off Manison's head.

You're showing off your wealth, right? You must be showing off your wealth!

Close to fifty million Lord's Avatars, are you an animal? How wealthy can you get‽

You're trying to take over all the ambush locations, aren't you? You think you're mighty just because you're rich‽

Noticing Black Star's almost overflowing resentment, Manison calmly smiled and gave him a look.

That's right. I'm mighty because I'm rich. Thanks for the assist.

Han Xiao clenched his teeth and sent Manison a private message.

"Stop messing around. There's no point in building tens of millions of Lord's Avatars other than it being a waste!"

"Hehe, you're too young. The Mechanical Race doesn't have much, but it never lacked machinery…" Manison smiled and softly stroked his beard before adding, "And money."

F*ck, almost forgot you were born rich!

Damn rich people!

Han Xiao ground his teeth secretly.

"I came up with this plan. Shouldn't you show some sincerity at least? How about giving me ten million Lord's Avatars."

"My avatars are my size, not like you can use them. What do you want them for?" Manison raised his brows.

"I can melt and rebuild them. The material cost for ten million Lord's Avatars isn't low."

"Sure, exchange them for some Spacetime Amber."

"F*ck off!"

Han Xiao instantly cut off the private conversation.

This old man is always trying to get my Spacetime Amber. Bad!

While the two of them made faces at each other, the person in charge from the three Universal Civilizations also looked back and forth between them with strong suspicion.

One of you is the president of the Beyond Grade A development union, and the other is the vice president…

Are the two of you putting on an act together?

Sidreun coughed, forced out a smile, and said, "We appreciate Your Excellency Mechanic Emperor's generosity, but the plan has yet to be finalized. You don't have to be in such a hurry…"

"You're right." Manison nodded. He casually waved his hand, signaling that he was just casually making a suggestion and that they could continue their previous conversation.

Sidreun then turned to Han Xiao and said with a deep voice, "Your Excellency Black Star, your idea does indeed seem good, but its feasibility still requires more discussion. Firstly, we have to make sure that the virus core has returned to the quantum network for us to cut off network connections on a large scale and limit the range of its exits. But how will we know when it has logged on to the network? You must know, those viruses don't have a fixed time for sending feedback data. We have no way of knowing when the virus core will be online.

"Secondly, as of now, we can't even lock onto the virus core's data pattern and aren't able to trace it on the network. If it remains in the quantum network, will we just not be able to find it?"

"Hence, this was just a rough idea. The details still need to be decided. However, it should be feasible," Han Xiao said.

"These problems all have a way of being solved. Since we know that the virus core is a life form and have its details, we can use that as an anchor and use prophecy spells to search the time it will log on to the network," Kant added.

"As for the data pattern of the virus core, I can provide some details," Manison said. "Although I didn't catch it, I recorded the traces it left behind when it was in the quantum network. With that as the clue, we can do cross-referencing, and we should be able to lock onto its data pattern."

The people present discussed ideas for a while and gradually filled in the details. They all felt that this plan was worth trying.

This time, Sidreun brought up the last issue.

"I have one last question. The participants of this operation might not have to know Virtual Paramount. Every Beyond Grade A should have the ability to capture the virus core, and the chances will be higher if all the Beyond Grade As here take part in it."

He did not believe the nonsense Han Xiao said at all. Beyond Grade As should all have the ability to capture the virus core. There was no way Virtual Paramount was a requirement. That certainly had to be Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor's conspiracy.

"I have no objections. I'm glad to be of help." The rest of the people present all agreed.

Of course you have no objections. What objections will you have since you will have an opportunity to obtain the core… Han Xiao complained in his mind.

"Then it's decided," Sidreun said with a serious tone. "This plan still requires approval from the upper echelons. The three of us all have to report it. The results should come very soon, and it'll most likely go smoothly. This operation still needs you guys, the Beyond Grade As, so I hope you're all well prepared. The safety of the universe depends on you."

…

Deactivating the remote projection, Han Xiao's vision returned to his office.

He casually knocked on the table and pondered.

All the Beyond Grade As would be working together to capture the virus core, and every single one of them wanted to get their hands on the core. Hence, choosing the ambush location was the top priority.

This was a matter of probability. The more avatars one had, the higher the chances of meeting the virus core. In this respect, no one could compare with the Mechanic Emperor.

Comparatively, Han Xiao's spare Lord's Avatars were very few. It was not because he lacked money, but to him, there was not much of a point building too many of them. He would only be able to descend on one avatar at a time no matter what.

It was clear old man Manison had ulterior motives for building so many avatars. He was probably planning to take over countless planets one day.

Humph! What an ambitious b*stard!

Manison probably has more Lord's Avatars than the number of trap nodes. He will definitely come into contact with the virus core, so he's basically unbeatable. While the rest of us can only rely on luck…

Han Xiao massaged the bridge of his nose.

The number of people stationed at each location was not limited. Manison would basically be everywhere, so there was no way of dodging him.

When the three Universal Civilizations have decided on the trap nodes, I'd better let Harrison help choose the ambush locations…

If my luck fails me and I don't end up meeting the virus core, I'll just live with it.

However, if I do meet the virus core, Manison's avatar will most likely be around too. I'll have to compete with him, and it definitely won't be just a verbal negotiation.

I'll just have to improvise…

If he had any advantages at all, it was that he did not have to care about whether the virus core was dead or not.

The others all wanted to capture it alive and parse it for the full Domino Virus technology, while he had the [Intelligent Plague] mission, which would give him a related talent if he eliminated the virus core personally. Given the specialty of the Domino Virus, the related talent would most likely have something to do with Virtual Technology.

Although he would lose the opportunity to obtain the full technology this way, thinking about it, if the three Universal Civilizations or other Beyond Grade As obtained such a powerful virtual virus, it might not be a good thing. Furthermore, even if he obtained it, it would be a hot potato. Countless people, including the three Universal Civilizations, would have their eyes on him at all times.

However, the Domino Virus technology could also become a powerful weapon against the World Tree Civilization.

Han Xiao was stuck in a dilemma.

Never mind, it's too early to think of all this. I'll first have to make sure I meet the virus. Only then will I have the chance to compete with Manison…

He focused his thoughts.

Anyway, this would be a huge operation, so the preparation stage would last quite some time, meaning he had sufficient time. He could add some production lines and produce as many Lord's Avatars as possible to be stationed at more locations, increasing the chance of him meeting the virus core.

…

"This information is from Black Star?"

Meanwhile, the remote projections of the three Universal Civilizations' leaders gathered and listened to the report from Sidreun and the other two.

Right after the meeting hosted by Black Star ended, the three monitors contacted their three leaders through the one and only coded channel that was connected to the outside world to explain the operation plan, hoping to get approval.

After hearing it, Urranrell crossed her hands before her chest and slowly said, "If what Black Star said is true, he'll be a great hero of the explored universe who saved it from a disaster. Without his prophecy, we'd all have to pay a bloody price to discover the truth of the Virtual Mutiny Virus."

"Hmm, the brief structure of this plan came from him too. If we catch the virus core because of it, Black Star will indeed be a hero to the entire universe who changed the disaster of a future he saw in the prophecy." Bader expressed his compliments too.

"Black Star is indeed worthy of merit." The church's pope agreed too.

Putting aside their beef in the past, both the Federation of Light and the Arcane Church recognized and appreciated what Han Xiao did in the battle against the Intelligent Plague. He acted very reliably and contributed a lot.

Having thought of that, the three of them looked at each other and nodded.

"We shall approve of this operation. We allow you to deploy the resources in the Ancient Star Desert to execute this plan. Don't disappoint us."

"Understood," Sidreun quickly replied.

The church's pope suddenly said, "One more thing, do make sure that the virus core ends up in our control in the end. We can't let any non-direct members obtain it."

"That's right. The Virtual Mutiny Virus is a weapon of war. It's too dangerous. We must not let this technology get leaked, or the order of the universe will be threatened."

Bader agreed and added, "Especially Black Star and Mechanic Emperor. If a peak Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanic gets this technology and improves it, it might become something even more dangerous than the Intelligent Plague."

Even though Manison was the Federation of Light's ally, Bader knew what was more important.

Although they all wanted this technology, the three of them clearly understood that preventing a fourth party from obtaining this virus technology was more important.

In the eyes of the three Universal Civilizations, they had to have a monopoly on this kind of extremely powerful weapon of war. Only then would it be beneficial for the entire universe.

…

Somewhere in the Ancient Star Desert, a small civilian transport fleet had arrived at a desolate planet.

This was a legitimate galactic transportation company. It was not large and did not have much of a name for itself. It only operated on a few fixed routes. Its business range was limited to between several Star Zones of the same Star System. There was a small desolate universe belt there. Due to its size, the advanced civilizations did not set up any stargates. Hence, there were quite a number of long-distance transport companies that filled this gap.

The transport fleet slowly came to a stop in this planet's orbit.

"Let's resupply here. There are fuel resources on this planet. We're going to collect some."

Inside the main ship, the senior captain, who had worked in this transport company for many years, gave the order.

Suddenly, an observation officer said, "Captain, the radar shows that this planet is shrouded by a strange electromagnetic storm."

The captain was surprised. He moved to the porthole and saw that the atmosphere of this desolate planet was filled with flickering light-blue electrical sparks. It looked like a looming electromagnetic shell.

"That's weird. I've run this transportation route for decades and stopped god knows how many times on this planet. When did this appear here?" the captain murmured and looked at the radar again.

The more he looked at the electromagnetic field structure, the more he felt it looked familiar.

"The structure of this electromagnetic field…" the observation officer said with hesitation. "Why does it look somewhat like the bio-electrical network of the neurons' movements in the brain of a living life form?"

The captain was startled. When he looked at it more carefully again, the structure of this electromagnetic field totally looked like a brain that was enlarged countless times.

"Could it be alive? Is it an electromagnetic field life form‽"

The captain was surprised. This kind of life form had always been rare. They could be sold to collectors with special tastes at quite a high price.

Having thought of that, the captain immediately ordered, "Quickly, try to capture it!"

However, as soon as he said that, the electromagnetic storm shrouding the planet suddenly dissipated into thin air like it had never appeared. There were no signs of it on the radar too.

The members inside the cabin were all startled.

"Am I tripping‽"

The captain rubbed his eyes with shock.

Chapter 1112: Trap and Pursuit

On the Star Arc Civilization's mother planet, the upper echelons were having a discussion in the conference room.

"The three Universal Civilizations sent us a notification not long ago, demanding that we be ready to shut down all the quantum network base stations on all our planets any time. What's this about?"

"Isn't the Intelligent Plague already under control? Did something happen?"

"Or are the three Universal Civilizations plotting against us again?"

The upper echelons' expressions were stiff. They were full of suspicion.

Initially, when the three Universal Civilizations announced that the antivirus had been created, they thought the Intelligent Plague was basically dealt with. Hence, their attention was focused on the fact that the Ancient Star Desert was still in lockdown. They felt that the three Universal Civilizations might use the opportunity and do something to them afterward, so they had been on alert 24/7. It was like they were suffering from delusions.

The three Universal Civilizations' sudden order to tell them to be ready to cut off all the quantum network connections in their territory made the Star Arc Civilization even more suspicious. They almost thought that this was a signal of the three Universal Civilizations' attacks on them.

This time, it was not cutting off their communications to the outside world but shutting down the quantum network in their territory, which meant that their galactic society foundation would be shut down. In the interstellar era, large civilizations like them completely relied on the immediate exchange of information through the quantum network to rule and manage their planets.

Shutting that down meant that they had to abandon their ruling over their territory temporarily. It was no wonder they were worried.

The civilization's leader knocked on the table and silenced the room. "The three Universal Civilizations sent the same announcement to the other civilizations too. We're not the only one."

Hearing this, the others all nodded with relief.

"Then it should still be related to the Intelligent Plague… What have the three Universal Civilizations been doing lately?" an official asked.

The person in charge of the intelligence department raised his eyes and said, "The three Universal Civilizations' troops are stationed separately on various planets. Those Beyond Grade A Mechanics are making strange movements too, dispatching their mechanical troops to those planets. They seem to be up to something big."

"All the Beyond Grade A Mechanics are acting?"

"Yes, all."

"What do you think they're doing?"

"I don't know the details, but it sure looks a lot like they're setting up an encirclement."

"Hmm…"

The civilization leader pondered for a moment and slowly said, "Cooperate with the three Universal Civilizations' arrangements. For the time being, investigate what the three Universal Civilizations and those Beyond Grade As are planning to do. Pay close attention. Don't ignore any moves they make. I want to know what their goal is."

…

In the Flickering World development union headquarters on Planet Finn, the remote projections of various Beyond Grade As gathered for the routine plenary meeting.

Some of the seats were empty, mostly Beyond Grade As who were summoned, including the president and the vice president seats.

"Speaking of which, Mechanic Emperor and Black Star have already missed quite a few meetings. I wonder how they're doing in the Ancient Star Desert," someone casually said. This topic quickly sparked discussion.

"The Intelligent Plague in the Ancient Star Desert has lasted for many months. No news has gotten out. What's the situation now? Is the disaster under control?"

"The Star Field is under lockdown. I can't get any information either. Any of you know what's going on?"

Since the three Universal Civilizations evaluated the Intelligent Plague as a universal disaster, the entire universe was paying close attention to the Ancient Star Desert. However, since leaking any information was forbidden, they did not know the situation in the Ancient Star Desert.

The Beyond Grade As present were all curious too.

"Hey, Hila, anything from your army commander?" A Beyond Grade A turned and looked at Hila, who rarely spoke.

"No." Hila gave the simplest response.

She was also a member of the association. Since Black Star could not attend the meetings, she acted as the representative of the Black Star Army.

Tolaen curled his lips and said, "Humph, Black Star might have already been taken out."

"Are you itching for another beating?" Hila said with an expressionless face.

Tolaen gave a creepy smile and said, "The way I see it, the three Universal Civilizations calling all the Beyond Grade A Mechanics over was a conspiracy to begin with. Think about it, both the president and the vice president are Mechanics. Wouldn't they be able to easily achieve what they've been wanting to do to us this way?"

The allies of the Arcane Church all looked at him with speechless expressions. Whose side are you really on?

"Stop talking nonsense. You'll be held accountable for the things you say," a direct member of the church said with a displeased tone.

"My bad, I always say whatever I want to say." Tolaen snorted.

Hila did not bother with him, but she was indeed a little worried.

All the other Mechanics only sent their avatars there; Black Star was the only one whose original body had gone over.

The Ancient Star Desert was in lockdown. If the three Universal Civilizations really wanted to do something to Black Star, that place would instantly turn into a death trap. Hila did not trust the three Universal Civilizations from the bottom of her heart. Although the King suit could teleport Han Xiao out anytime, it was not enough to make her not worry.

On the other side, Secret Master's eyelids trembled uncontrollably.

As a protector of the black market, he was more interested in the Ancient Star Desert's situation than the others.

Ever since the Star Field had gone into lockdown, all contact with the black market over there had been cut off. A lot of the businesses there were under his protection and had always given him a lot of profit. Some were the Beast Ancestor's businesses that he had just taken over not long ago.

After having no contact for so long, he had absolutely no idea how his businesses were doing.

I wonder how the black market of the Ancient Star Desert is faring… Secret Master pondered.

…

According to Han Xiao's operation plan, the three Universal Civilizations did a lot of preparations over more than a month. They dispatched fleets to be stationed at all the trap node planets. Most of their time was spent on traveling and waiting for the Beyond Grade As' mechanical armies to arrive at the locations.

Since this was a Star Field level network, there were quite a number of trap nodes that spread across the various Star Systems of the Ancient Star Desert. The trap nodes the three Universal Civilizations had chosen were mainly those territories that were not easy to control with just orders or some crucial spots.

Every terminal exit had a Beyond Grade A Mechanic and the three Universal Civilizations' fleet around it, and Manison's Lord's Avatars were at all of them.

In this time, Han Xiao had also built a batch of specially made Lord's Avatars, but it was still not enough. He decided to compromise and stationed only his mechanical troops at every spot.

As for the Lord's Avatars, he placed them at the locations carefully selected by Harrison and hoped he was lucky enough.

The target of [Lord's Descent] was not limited to specially made Lord's Avatars. It could be used on even normal mechanical soldiers, only not at full power and with a full set of abilities. Therefore, even though any Beyond Grade A Mechanic would be able to set up an ambush at all the locations, they could only be a bystander at most, and none had the advantage Manison had. After all, there was no way they could compete with Manison's Lord's Avatar if they descended on ordinary machines.

Therefore, the other Beyond Grade A Mechanics were all planning to do their best to force the virus core to materialize at one of the locations their Lord's Avatars were at.

Due to how stealthy the virus core was, there was currently not a scanning tool that anyone could use. Only Beyond Grade A Mechanics could track the virus core on the network. Although some of them were not specialized in the virtual area, as long as they had learned the [Virtual Creator] Ultimate Knowledge, it was enough.

In order to improve everyone's virtual ability and range, the Federation of Light provided a large-scale strategic device—Super Range Virtual Brainwave Enhancer.

This was equipment exclusively for Mechanics. It improved one's virtual ability in many ways, drastically increasing the range. It could be fully utilized by Beyond Grade A Mechanics.

The size of this device was enormous, like a spherical, silver galactic fortress. Its exterior looked like it was assembled through plates. There were clearly visible gaps between, and it was not smooth at all.

The inside of the device was very empty. In its heart, all the Beyond Grade A Mechanics formed a circle and hovered in midair. They were ready.

The remote projections of the three Inspectors, including Sidreun, appeared in this circle. Sidreun said with a serious tone, "Guys, the mechanical troops are all deployed. There are only thirteen minutes to the time when the virus core will go online according to the prophecy. When the time comes, we will cut off the network immediately and make the Ancient Star Desert a trap. Please act according to the plan. We're relying on you; you must catch the virus core."

The people nodded. Although this was a huge responsibility, everyone there was someone who stood at the top of the universe, so they did not feel pressured.

The first step of the operation involved them tracing the virus core after the trap was set, preventing it from hiding. It was like catching a chicken inside a cage.

With the data pattern Manison had provided and the bonus of the Super Range Virtual Brainwave Enhancer, they could track the virus core for as far as they wanted and not worry about it escaping.

This time, Kant said with a smile, "This should be the first time all the Beyond Grade A Mechanics in the universe have worked together. I think this will be written down in history."

Hearing this, many people present laughed.

Indeed, all the people at the top of the Mechanic class working together was something worth writing about in the history books.

Han Xiao glanced around and curled his lips.

Humph, you're all laughing now, but when we fight for the virus core later, you'll all beat each other up without hesitation.

I hope Harrison's Luck Glow works this time and the virus core ends up meeting my Lord's Avatar…

Not taking part in the conversation, Han Xiao prayed in his mind.

The people went silent to stay focused. Time passed minute by minute.

Finally, when it came to the last minute, Sidreun looked at the time and said with a deep voice, "Guys, let's go!"

…

In the quantum network vision, the Ancient Star Desert was an illuminated Star Field. Countless bright nodes formed a sea of light, and countless data streams connected the nodes, forming an extremely complex 3D network structure.

These data connections that looked like strings were the foundation of the galactic society.

At this time, a stream of light suddenly appeared outside one of the data links.

This stream of light looked like a cluster of extremely intricate data. Countless symbols flowed on its shell. This was what the Domino Virus' core looked like. It was in the form of an artificial intelligence life form.

The next second, the virus core came into contact with the firewall of this data link. Its shell instantly assimilated with the firewall, easily getting through the alarm system, and infiltrated this link. It then moved along with the data flowed, capturing the feedback data in the network.

Ka!

At this time, a large portion of the bright Ancient Star Desert in the quantum network vision suddenly became dark.

Countless data links broke off, and countless nodes extinguished simultaneously. The sea of light became much smaller.

Buzz!

At the same time, more than a dozen powerful consciousnesses arrived in the quantum network, scanning through the remaining quantum network area like nothing could hide from them.

The next moment, a consciousness locked onto the virus core.

Data streams came together and formed a silhouette of light before the virus core. Kant's virtual soul smiled at it.

"Found you…"

At this instant, the virus core's program quickly came up with a measure and immediately fled!

Through the data link, the virus core changed its form multiple times and fled to a place that was countless nodes away.

However, suddenly, a data stream tornado appeared in front of it.

"Are you playing hide and seek?"

The data streams formed Quantum Demon's face. It was intently staring at the virus core.

Without hesitation, the virus core turned around and fled again, hoping to find a location and hide in the quantum network.

However, no matter how much computing power the virus core spent on coming up with disguises, it would still end up meeting a Beyond Grade A Mechanic every time. It was forced to keep changing direction. It looked quite similar to someone who was panicking.

Han Xiao, Manison, Kant, Judith, and the other Beyond Grade A Mechanics showed up one after another, stopping the virus core in its path.

The encirclement started to shrink around it.

At this time, the virus core suddenly stopped fleeing. It entered one of the nodes and disappeared without a trace.

"It has materialized!"

Inside the real world, Han Xiao's original body's eyes sparkled.

The terminal exit that the virus core had chosen seemed to be a planet where the Machinery Faith was.

That was one of the ambush locations his Lord's Avatar was at!

Buzz!

At the same time, powerful Mechanical Forces appeared around every Mechanic in the Super Range Virtual Brainwave Enhancer.

Multiple consciousnesses traveled in the cosmic space and headed to the planet this node was at!

Chapter 1113: Confrontation and Negotiation

In the Ancient Star Desert, Planet Magnetic Cloud was one of the gathering grounds of the Machinery Faith. Its ground was yellowish-black, and heavy bases in the style of the Machinery Faith stood on the surface neatly, forming a ring-shaped industrial city. Around it were open mines with countless large industrial cranes. The streets of the city were well connected in all directions, all flat gray roads. Convoys of carriers rode past the pedestrians on the sides of the street wearing heavy kinetic armor one after another.

At the heart of the ring-shaped city was a tall mountain. It was sliced flat in the middle as a platform, where the temples were. On top of it was a floating island releasing a gentle artificial light.

The Machinery Faith had many followers and factions. It had no strict rules and mostly centered around the Grand Priest and the various bishops, forming fleets that traveled the universe looking for planets to migrate to. Their goal was the planets' mines and the machinery wreckages underground, accumulating them or selling them. Therefore, most of the planets the Machinery Faith visited were just temporarily strongholds. They were somewhat like a wandering religion.

The Machinery Faith did not have many fixed strongholds. Some were the subdivisions of different factions, some were long-term gathering and residential areas of the believers such as Planet Magnetic Cloud, and some were holy grounds recognized by all the believers.

Now, the heavily armed fleet of the three Universal Civilizations hovered above Planet Magnetic Cloud. The believers on the ground, however, were not surprised. They only occasionally glanced above and then got back to what they were doing.

The three Universal Civilizations had already contacted the Machinery Faith. This kind of loose organization with religious factors was always hard to manage. The three Universal Civilizations did not trust in the Machinery Faith's ability to execute their orders, so they just stationed their fleet there and used it as a trap node.

Currently, on the open platform at the top of the mechanical temple, the Grand Priest who was wearing the bishop armor looked up at the fleet above and softly murmured.

The priest beside saw this, approached him, and asked, "Grand Priest, are you worried about the three Universal Civilizations' fleet?"

The Grand Priest shook his head and said, "We're just a civilian organization that obeys the law. We've never had much contact with the three Universal Civilizations, so they won't do anything to us. I'm glad that the three Universal Civilizations are here."

"Glad?"

"Yes, ever since the Intelligent Plague erupted, the fanatics in the religion have been growing by the day. Not only have they been studying the Virtual Mutiny Virus privately, but they even wanted to spread it. This completely goes against the Machinery Faith's neutral stance; their twisted faith will bring disaster to the religion sooner or later. Now that the three Universal Civilizations have come, they've indirectly kept those fanatics obedient," the Grand Priest mumbled.

Thinking back, it still felt quite heavy.

After the three Universal Civilizations invented the antivirus, there were even some fanatics who attempted to improve the virus and crack the antivirus so that the Intelligent Plague would continue. These madmen strongly believed that this was a great artificial intelligence revolution.

Therefore, left with no choice, he dispatched the Guards of Faith and locked these people up. However, this idea remained and was still spreading around this gathering ground.

"Hmm, maybe…" The priest paused momentarily. "Even now, I still don't understand why the three Universal Civilizations are temporarily using our gathering ground."

"It seems to be related to the Intelligent Plague. I don't know much either…" The Grand Priest shook his head.

Before he finished his sentence, the radar in his armor suddenly reacted.

"Abnormality detected in the planet's magnetic field. A vortex has appeared, coordinates…"

The Grand Priest was startled. He turned and looked at the magnetic field vortex together with the priest beside him.

The magnetic field of Planet Magnetic Cloud was very special. The armor of the Machinery Faith believers here was equipped with specially made monitors of the magnetic field. At this time, they all heard the notification from the radar. The people on the streets all stopped and looked in the same direction.

They quickly switched to Electromagnetic Vision so that they could clearly see the movement of the magnetic field. In their vision, in the sky far away, the magnetic field seemed to have formed a tornado, and bright light sparks appeared out of nowhere, quickly forming an energy field.

Right at this moment, something happened!

Boom!

Bright meteors suddenly flew out from the three Universal Civilizations' fleet one after another, quickly heading to the location of the electromagnetic vortex.

Although these meteors were not large in size, they all gave off an astonishing energy presence, dragging extremely bright electrical tracks behind them that left long-lasting marks on the pupils of those watching. Those meteors made thunderous sounds while moving, as if the sky was collapsing.

"What is that‽"

Including the Grand Priest, all the Machinery Faith believers on Planet Magnetic Cloud were shocked.

At this time, the first batch of meteors arrived at the electromagnetic vortex's location and all stopped. After the flames around them disappeared, their appearance as machines appeared. They were all Lord's Avatars of the various Beyond Grade A Mechanics.

Manison was the quickest. He looked up and glared at the electromagnetic vortex, and it stopped moving for an instant. Then, he raised his hand and grabbed toward it. The electromagnetic field at the vortex's center was grabbed by him, and it entered into a mini triangular container the size of a human head.

The next moment, the abnormal electromagnetic vortex disappeared. The wind and the rain stopped, and the sky became bright again, as if the electromagnetic tornado just moments ago was only an illusion.

"Are those the Lord's Avatars of Beyond Grade A Mechanics‽"

Seeing this, although the Machinery Faith believers still had no idea what was going on, they were all instantly overjoyed and thrilled.

In their eyes, this many Beyond Grade A Mechanics appearing was the same as Gods descending.

However, before they could be surprised, the situation changed drastically again.

Suddenly, the other Beyond Grade A Lord's Avatars behind Manison attacked him all at the same time.

Boom boom boom!

Explosions erupted in midair and illuminated the faces of countless Machinery Faith believers.

The next second, Manison's Lord's Avatar flew out from the explosion and was surrounded by the others.

Seeing this, a flash of shock appeared in the eyes of every believer.

These Beyond Grade As are going to fight here? Then aren't we witnessing a 'Battle of Gods'‽

…

Ten seconds prior…

Inside the three Universal Civilizations' fleet outside Planet Magnetic Cloud, mechanical troops of the various Mechanics hovered. Some mechanical troops were surrounding their own Lord's Avatars.

The instant the virus core escaped the quantum network, all of their consciousness arrived. The eyes of the mechanical bodies lit up one after another.

"Target locked!"

As soon as Han Xiao arrived, the radar's notification sounded beside his ear.

At the same time, a black silhouette landed from not far away. That was Manison's avatar, and it rushed to the virus core's material body instantly.

That old man is fast!

This thought flashed past his mind in an instant. Han Xiao was just about to use his ability, only to realize he could not use any teleportation abilities such as the Void Hyperdrive.

His pupils constricted, and he understood what was going on. Without further ado, he instantly followed after Manison's avatar and fell toward the planet surface. Behind him were many meteors, all avatars or troops of the others.

Bang!

They passed through the atmosphere. Their high speed gave them a burning flame coat.

Han Xiao stared at the target closely. The electromagnetic vortex enlarged in his sights as he quickly approached.

The virus core had just escaped the quantum network and was gathering electromagnetic energy to form its body, only to realize a group of Beyond Grade A Lord's Avatars approaching. It gave up materializing and attempted to head back to the quantum network to flee.

However, in an instant, a dense electrical light shot out from Manison's eyes. He had activated [Virtual Paramount]!

Weng!

The virus core's virtual soul was instantly locked, unable to escape its shell that had yet to even form fully.

Manison's movements were smooth without any hiccups. He quickly took out the specially made containment device and sucked the virus core in.

This containment was specially made to suppress the virus core's abilities. It could perfectly contain it. As long as the virus core was caught in it, it would never escape.

Han Xiao's pupils constricted. Old Man Manison got it!

However, the next instant, the other Lord's Avatars that followed attacked at the same time. Highly dense beams passed him by and headed right toward Manison's back.

Boom!

Manison had expected this. Layers of shields appeared and blocked the bombardment, causing violent explosions.

Using this force, he quickly got away from the others, at the same time turning toward them, with the containment that carried the virus core still in his hands.

The others surrounded and confronted Manison.

"Be careful. If you guys destroy the container, my efforts will have gone to waste."

Manison was not angry at all and spoke calmly.

A direct member of the Federation of Light, Defender Romo, said with a deep voice, "Manison, hand over the virus core. You should know that this kind of thing can't be leaked."

The remote projections of the inspectors including Sidreun appeared. He said with a solemn tone, "That's right. Your Excellency Mechanic Emperor, you're a sensible person. The three Universal Civilizations will certainly reward you generously for capturing the virus core, but this thing cannot remain in the hands of someone else."

"Hehe, you don't have to be so nervous. After I'm done studying it, not only will I hand turn the virus core over, I'll even share the technology I've obtained through it."

Manison was very casual and did not panic at all.

Han Xiao did not speak. He looked around and nodded secretly. This was completely within his expectations.

In his previous life, the person who obtained the virus core had probably obtained it secretly. Now, however, the situation was completely different. The virus core was a hot potato. No matter which Mechanic possessed it, they would instantly be in a difficult situation and become the target of the rest of the Mechanics. At the same time, the three Universal Civilizations would certainly ask for the virus core from them.

The battleships were of no help in capturing the virus core, so why did the three Universal Civilizations deploy fleets at the trap nodes? Clearly, they were not there to deal with the virus core but to deal with them, the Beyond Grade A Mechanics!

The Lord's Avatars present all had short-range hyperdrive abilities. Han Xiao even had Void Hyperdrive, but no one used it. This was because the fleet had activated spacetime stabilization anchors at the trap nodes long ago, preventing anyone from escaping.

And this was the exact reason Manison stayed to talk, or he would have escaped the moment he succeeded.

The only way to leave with the virus core was… to fight a way out!

However, although the three Universal Civilizations and the other Mechanics wanted to take away the virus core, they were worried about destroying the container, so they all held back.

The three Universal Civilizations hoped to take back the virus core from Manison through a negotiation. They were even mentally prepared for Manison to ask for an outrageous price.

"Mechanic Emperor, the Virtual Mutiny Virus is a strategic weapon that can threaten the entire universe. It will only be safe in the hands of the three Universal Civilizations. We won't allow any risk to exist, so no matter what, we have to take the virus core today. You should know the severity of this matter."

The inspector of the Arcane Church's tone was firm.

Manison did not respond instantly but looked at the avatars of the other Mechanics. He then said slowly, "See that? Anyone who gets the virus core will have to face this. Are you guys still planning to fight for it?"

"Honestly, I don't have a lot of interest in the virus core. After all, I'm not a Virtual Mechanic… However, I wouldn't mind exchanging this for more good stuff." Kant chuckled.

"Don't look at me. As long as I get the virus core, I'll regain my freedom, so I'm on the side of the church," Mechanical Catastrophe Francisco said.

"I'll fight for something with all I've got as long as there's a chance… Teacher, you taught me that." 'Mechanic Empress' Mornisa's tone was calm.

Everyone expressed their attitude. Their reasons were different, but they all had the same resolve.

In the end, Manison's eyes stopped on Han Xiao.

"Black Star, what about you?"

Han Xiao did not answer it directly but replied with a mocking tone, "You didn't ask around just to chat, did you? Are you stalling for the time, or are you trying to find a temporary ally?"

Hearing this, Manison smiled. "Black Star, you know me well… That's right, I need an ally to deal with this tough situation together. You and I both know the situation the Beyond Grade As are in. We're on the same side. I plan to study the Virtual Mutiny Virus not only for its technology but also to add a layer of insurance for the Beyond Grade As. If you're willing to help me, I won't mind studying this technology together with you."

Everyone looked at Han Xiao with different emotions.

Han Xiao was not convinced at all. He casually said, "Sounds good, but I have a feeling you'll go back on your word."

"Hehe. You might not believe me, but I need someone to take this risk together with me. Two people having this technology suits my interests more, so this time, I will keep my word."

"Tsk, that's all words. No matter how good they sound, they're just that."

"Then, how do you want me to prove it?"

Han Xiao pointed at the container in Manison's hands, smiled, and said, "Since you're willing to study it together with me, who's holding the virus core won't make a difference. Give the device to me. I'll take the risk, and you'll help me to get out of this. That way, I'll believe that you're sincere and not just toying with my feelings."

"I'm okay with that, but will you be willing to study it with me when it's in your hands? How can I be sure you won't go back on your words?" Manison asked the same thing.

"As you just said, I need someone to share the pressure too." Han Xiao shrugged.

Manison stayed silent for a few seconds. As the atmosphere became heavier and heavier, he finally spoke slowly and shocked everyone.

"Since that's the case… then why not?"

Chapter 1114: The Choice of the Era

At the same time, what was happening on Planet Magnetic Cloud was being broadcast live to the Central Galaxy through a military coded channel. The leaders of the three Universal Civilizations were monitoring events in real-time.

Seeing this, the three of them were all silent.

Bader took a deep breath and slowly said, "Manison… we've given him too much freedom. We can put up with other things, but this time, he crossed the line."

The church's pope said, "He always ignores our warnings, provoking our authority time after time, and now even wants to acquire a strategic intimidation weapon. He says he's fighting for a form of insurance for the Beyond Grade As, but he's just trying to make us fear him so he can be on the same level as us. He'll definitely also use this to threaten us for more things in the future. The possibility of all that happening has to be eliminated at the roots."

"I seem to recall that Black Star has a similar ability to the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device. If he works with Manison and takes the virus core, he'll be able to teleport out immediately…" Bader turned to look at Urranrell, who was silent, and said with a more serious tone, "As long as he leaves the scene with the virus core, we'll assume that the Virtual Mutiny Virus has already been obtained by Black Star… So, Your Excellency Dynasty Ruler, what are you planning to do?"

Urranrell stayed silent for a while before saying, "Now isn't a good time for a cleansing. The Flickering World is in development, and the Super Star Cluster Civilizations are a threat. If we force Black Star and Mechanic Emperor to turn on us, they might go to the Super Star Cluster Civilizations with the Virtual Mutiny Virus in their hands. That's going to be a real threat, so we should try our best for things not to come to that."

"That's right. With the Super Star Cluster Civilizations, now indeed isn't a good time to have a cleansing… However, our compromise and tolerance should have a limit, and we can't step behind that line," Bader said with a deep voice.

The church's pope said with a grave tone, "Maybe having a trump card to protect their safety is a sensible demand of the Beyond Grade As, but we can't ignore how much of a threat this is to our rule. I know that if Black Star or the Mechanic Emperor acquire the virus technology, we'll still be able to maintain a peaceful relationship with them as long as we don't push them too hard, and things won't end up in the worst scenario. However, it will still be a hidden threat. Can we close our eyes and act like all this never happened just because it won't show its dangers for the time being? We did not get to where we are today by having illusional hopes in others!"

Urranrell frowned and shouted, "Do you have any idea what you're talking about? You're talking about a war that will involve all the advanced civilizations in the entire universe, a cleansing that will last for decades or even a century. Do you not know the consequences of that‽ Do you want to go back to the exploration era‽"

"It won't come to that. We're already the absolute rulers. No one can stand above us. Maybe this will be the most chaotic time since the start of the Galaxy Calendar, but it will make sure all our obstacles are cleared. It's better than watching our enemies grow so powerful that we can't get rid of them…" The pope's tone was calm.

"What about the threat of the Super Star Cluster Civilizations?"

"If the Super Star Cluster Civilizations want to use the Virtual Mutiny Virus technology, we'll announce this to the entire universe. It'll be the best reason to start a war with them. 'The Super Star Cluster Civilizations have ignored the safety of the universe and attempted to use such a dangerous weapon; to maintain order, we have no choice but to wipe them out.' This will be an opportunity to shatter all the Super Star Cluster Civilizations. Although both sides will end up suffering, nothing else will be able to shake our position afterward… After our enemies are eliminated, we'll have more than enough time to deal with internal matters."

Urranrell bit on her lips and squeezed out the words from between her teeth. "Stability above all."

The church pope was unconvinced. "Our bottom line doesn't allow provocations."

The atmosphere became tense. Disagreements were common in such meetings.

Seeing the two of them argue, Bader looked left and right with a strange expression.

The always aggressive Crimson Dynasty shockingly spoke about stability today, while the usually cheeky Arcane Church suddenly became a war fanatic‽

Bader was at a loss.

He suppressed his shock, coughed, and said, "That's very decisive of you, Pope. Since the Dynasty Ruler doesn't agree with the more aggressive approach, maybe we can do it another way. Let's say the Mechanic Emperor and Black Star succeed, we can temporarily compromise with them on the terms of them having to deal with the Super Star Cluster Civilizations. When they're both wounded, we can come in and clean the two sides."

"Too assumptive." The church pope shook his head. "If the Mechanic Emperor and Black Star acquire the technology, they definitely know the risks they'll take by eliminating one of their potential customers. Otherwise, the leverage they have will lose its biggest threat."

"Things are still not clear yet," Urranrell said with a heavy frown. "Black Star has yet to agree to work with the Mechanic Emperor. He's a smart person. I believe he will make a choice that's beneficial for the peace of the universe."

The church pope coldly said, "But what if? The federation once trusted the Mechanic Emperor too much as an ally, which led to him pushing the boundaries and gradually getting out of our control. With such an example, is the dynasty still planning to continue to protect Black Star for the sake of not offending him? A choice has to be made between the big picture and allies; unending fawning will only make the other party think you're weak."

Hearing this, Urranrell closed her eyes, only opening them again after a while. Her eyes were emotionless when they opened again.

"By then, I'll have my measures."

"Such as?"

"That's not for you to worry, Your Excellency!"

…

On the other hand, the confrontation was still underway on Planet Magnetic Cloud.

As soon as Manison said that, everyone present was startled. They did not think Manison would be willing to pass the virus core to someone else.

Han Xiao was shocked too. He was just mocking Manison and testing him. He did not think Manison would really agree to it.

Hearing this, Han Xiao hesitated and did not respond instantly. He started to think quickly in his mind.

Manison wants to work with me, not only to shift the target to me but also because of the teleportation ability of the King suit. Of all the people here, I'm the only one who can leave this place with the virus core easily. Old Man Manison is strong, sure, but even he isn't very confident in fleeing from here, which is why he has chosen me…

Han Xiao pondered. This body was a Lord's Avatar that did not have the King. Nonetheless, he could summon a spare one from the Dimension Factory, so it was not an issue.

Manison is killing two birds with one stone. If I agree and leave with the virus core, I'll instantly become the target of everyone, while Manison won't have to fight for a way out after throwing the hot potato to me. Instead, he got himself out of the equation, and I'll face the most pressure from the three Universal Civilizations.

If I break my promise after acquiring the technology, not only will I have to endure the pressure alone, but I'll also have to suffer the consequences of breaking my promise. Not speaking of offending Manison, my name among the Beyond Grade As will plummet for sure. Therefore, he's certain that I'll need an ally, so he knows he'll most likely still get his hands on the technology, and he's willing to gamble on it…

Han Xiao clenched his teeth in his mind.

He's playing these dirty tricks again!

The two of them did not chat privately but openly. Manison's intentions were clear; he wanted to shift the target of the conflict, and everyone understood that. However, some people still panicked.

Seeing that Han Xiao was about to be convinced, the dynasty's inspector yelled loudly, "Black Star! You have to think carefully about what you're doing!"

He had to panic. Although the spacetime was stabilized, Black Star was the only one who could just teleport out.

Although the two of them could run but could not hide, if the three Universal Civilizations could not retrieve the virus core on the spot, it would cause tons of problems afterward.

The Beyond Grade A Mechanics changed their positions and stood apart from Manison and Han Xiao.

This time, Manison raised the contained virus core, stared at Han Xiao, and said, "Black Star, I've always had high hopes for you. You should know that this will become the amulet for the Beyond Grade As. We have the same philosophy. Leave with it. Our future is in your hands."

"Bullsh*t. Although you're the association president, you still don't have the right to make this kind of decision on behalf of all the Beyond Grade As. No one needs you to plan the future for them." Kant turned to Han Xiao and said, "Black Star, don't get tricked by him. Not only will possessing the virus core not give us insurance, but it will bring us a disaster."

Han Xiao hesitated.

His philosophy was not the same as the Mechanic Emperor's. He wanted to interfere with the Calamity of the Supers so that the explored universe could preserve more strength to deal with the World Tree Civilization in the future.

Manison wanted to make the Beyond Grade As stronger, making everyone in this Grade his shield. Another goal of him attempting to acquire the Domino Virus technology was most likely to make the other Beyond Grade As more united around him and see him as their leader.

In Han Xiao's previous life, Manison most likely was the one who got the Domino Virus. However, he did not use it during the World Tree Civilization war. His ambitions showed from that—since he still did not expose his trump card even when the explored universe was threatened by an outside enemy, he clearly wanted to use it on the three Universal Civilizations.

Han Xiao looked around and saw the expression on everyone's face.

Is the Domino Virus really an amulet? Who knows? It might be a death invitation.

How can the three Universal Civilizations possibly be willing to be restricted by someone? If I threaten them with this as leverage, I won't receive compromises but, more likely, the three Universal Civilizations' resolve to eliminate their enemies no matter the cost.

Most of the time, the three Universal Civilizations would think about the big picture, but this did not mean that they would compromise without limits. Strategic weapons would only achieve a balance of power when the power of the two sides was on the same level in the first place. However, if one side's power overwhelmed the other, it was tough to imagine they would allow an outsider to use a weapon that could threaten them to demand things.

If he obtained the Domino Virus technology, he would be able to cause huge damage to the entire universe if he wanted to and make the galactic society go back multiple generations. He might feel this meant that the three Universal Civilizations would have no choice but to choose to tolerate and compromise with him… However, this would be the exact source of the three Universal Civilizations' resolve to eliminate him.

Even if he did not think of causing trouble, people could change, and the three Universal Civilizations would not be willing to take that risk.

From Han Xiao's perspective, the three Universal Civilizations allowing them to possess the Domino Virus technology did not seem like a big deal. After all, as long as everyone held back, it seemed like no one would suffer any losses. It looked like a small issue not worth all the trouble.

However, this was only his mind playing tricks on him, telling him he might get lucky. In truth, the three Universal Civilizations had lines that could not be crossed. They could tolerate others being greedy, but they would never allow anyone to threaten their positions as the absolute rulers.

In this situation, if he ignored their warnings and took the virus core away, no matter what he said afterward, the three Universal Civilizations would still assume he was thinking of overthrowing their rule.

If things really turned ugly, Han Xiao did not think the other Beyond Grade As would be standing on his side.

He knew very well that everyone had their own plans. His call only got so many responses before because it suited their interests. However, no one was ready to turn on the three Universal Civilizations. By then, there would definitely be more people who would choose not to be involved than people who chose to take this path to the end.

By that time, he and the Mechanic Emperor might be seen as the cancer of society. Most of the time, the majority represented the society they were in.

Also, the impact of things turning completely ugly would show in all areas. The Black Star Army's territory in the Flickering World would be retrieved; the civilizations would no longer provide any resource channels; the civilian financial groups would terminate their partnerships; the army's funds and accounts would be frozen, and the army would not be able to purchase any resources; countless army soldiers would quit and leave; the army's business would shrink dramatically… The three Universal Civilizations would only have to make a simple announcement for all this to happen. All the benefits he was enjoying from the advanced civilizations would be gone forever.

Everyone was a member of the galactic civilization. There would certainly be extremely few people who would be willing to fight against the three Universal Civilizations on the Black Star Army's side.

After all, most people were just ordinary people. No one could blame them for putting themselves first.

Han Xiao's eyes flickered. He stopped joking around and said with a deep voice, "You're putting me in the gamble."

"I'm thinking about the big picture." Manison's tone was calm.

Han Xiao stayed silent for a while before suddenly moving.

Buzz!

Void energy erupted and shrouded this area. Everyone there felt like they were in a swap and could not move freely.

Void Prison!

Due to the spacetime stabilization device, the strength, duration, and range of this ability all decreased drastically, but it was still barely enough.

In this area, only Han Xiao's movements were unrestricted. He flew past the encirclement around and instantly came before Manison, grabbed onto the virus core and immediately moved aside.

"Black Star!"

As Void Prison ended, everyone came and surrounded Han Xiao this time.

Everyone's eyes landed on him with all kinds of complicated emotions such as anger, worry, anxiety, and many more.

Outside the crowd, Manison looked at Han Xiao and said, "Looks like you've figured it out. You're a smart man. Don't disappoint me."

"Black Star, don't do anything stupid." Sidreun and the inspectors were shocked.

Han Xiao did not respond to anyone. He looked at the virus core in his hands carefully, softly rubbed the container, and made sure it was the real thing.

With so many Beyond Grade As around, the possibility of it being swapped without getting noticed was nonexistent.

With the virus core in his hands, he felt as if he was not holding onto a physical object but the fate of countless people in this universe.

The direction of the era and the path it would take might be all decided by his one decision.

This time, Han Xiao looked up at the nervous eyes of everyone and slowly said, "Before taking the bet, one has to see the risks first. Sorry, I might have made a not so right decision. It's just that I suddenly recall something a woman once said to me…

"She said… this universe has an end no matter how enormous it is, but ambition has no limits."

Right after he said that, under the shocking look of everyone, Han Xiao's Mechanical Force erupted and flowed into the container.

The Mechanical Force was mixed with a virtual soul attack. It completely wiped both the virus core's physical body and soul.

Ka-cha!

He shattered the metal shell with his fingers. The empty container turned into pieces and fell to the ground.

At this moment, it was like everything froze.

Everyone watching, including the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations who were watching the broadcast, were all completely astonished.

Everyone had a lot of guesses in their minds, but not a single person had thought of what just happened.

Black Star destroyed the virus core?

He's mad! Why did he do that‽

Even if you don't want it, you didn't have to destroy it!

A bright light suddenly appeared in Manison's eyes, and a terrifying energy flowed in his body like a tsunami.

His deep voice echoed around word by word.

"What! The! Hell! Have! You! Done!"

Chapter 1115: Twin Gods Advent

The lightning snaked wildly around, flickering with arcs of electricity as the energy fluctuations blasted around with the force of a hurricane. The Beyond Grade A avatars and machinery present were all blown away and retreated.

Han Xiao was blown back a short distance, and he immediately stabilized himself, staring at the other party.

Manison was entwined with a brilliant golden arc of Mechanical Force, releasing an astonishing aura. His pinnacle Beyond Grade A energy was fully released, and even though this was just an avatar of his, Han Xiao felt a heavy sense of oppression.

Manison's eyes flashed as he locked onto Han Xiao, repeating his question.

"Do you know what you just did‽"

"Are you angry?" Han Xiao did not bother to explain, only indifferently replying.

"I'm very disappointed in you. You definitely understood what sort of chance you just gave up! Why did you destroy the virus core‽"

"Eradicating the Intelligent Plague is the goal of our trip. I just did my part… and on the first day I arrived, I told you this. It's my generation's responsibility to prevent the universe from growing more chaotic, but you didn't seem to take it seriously."

Manison hovered in the air, his tone not revealing any surprise or joy. "It seems like my understanding of you is still insufficient."

"Many people don't even understand themselves, let alone say that they understand others… Mechanic Emperor, you think that we're the same kind of person, but in fact, we're not."

"Since things have reached this point, there's no need to say any more. Since you disappointed me, you should know how this will end today!"

Manison's Mechanical Force soared up to the sky, piercing through the clouds, and connected to his machinery in outer space. His voice boomed out.

"Let me see just how much ability you have!"

Just as his voice sounded, a black wave of machinery passed through the atmosphere, shooting out a dense beam of light as they fell from the sky like a meteor shower toward Han Xiao's position.

"My thoughts exactly!"

Han Xiao's left fist slammed upward toward the sky in a fanfare of light. An arc-shaped psionic protective shield unfolded in the air.

The dense cluster of light beams hit on the protective shield like a heavy downpour hitting the leaves on a plantation. This was accompanied by crackling explosions.

Han Xiao's Mechanical Force also rushed upward to the sky, summoning his machinery on standby in outer space.

The machinery acted instantaneously and broke through the atmosphere. Manison's troops immediately shifted their targets, exchanging fire with Han Xiao's troops at a high altitude. The crisscrossing beams gave off a mysterious glow in the skies.

Han Xiao and Manison's avatars were not idle either. They quickly drew close to each other in a collision.

Boom!

Just like a comet hitting the earth, a bluish-gold circular shock wave exploded at the center of their impact.

The two figures exchanged attacks hundreds of times, entangled as they rose into the air.

Boom!

Alloy rubbed against alloy, releasing countless electric sparks, and shock waves constantly formed at the point of their impacts.

…

Just as two of them started fighting, the other Beyond Grade A avatars and troops on the scene immediately diverged from each other, running off to the side to watch without getting involved.

Seeing Black Star fighting against the Mechanic Emperor, everyone then recovered from the shock of Han Xiao destroying the virus core.

"I really didn't expect… that Black Star would do this." Maximiler was surprised.

"By doing this, he has put an end to the possibility of any organization obtaining the complete technology of this Virtual Mutiny Virus. Neither us nor the three Universal Civilizations can restore this technology now. He was too impulsive. Now no one has obtained anything from this trip," Mornisa complained.

"Impulsive? In my opinion, he's the one who is the calmest and most rational," Sun Hunter replied. "While doing this will cut off our hope of obtaining the virus technology, from the perspective of the universe and the bigger picture, this was a selfless choice."

Kant nodded, speaking emotionally. "Come to think of it, we did not lose anything, nor did the three Universal Civilizations. The only ones who truly lost were Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor. The Mechanic Emperor has been made a fool of, and his position is making the three Universal Civilizations feel a certain degree of danger from him. As for Black Star, he has relinquished the possibility of obtaining benefits.

"If I was in that position, I would definitely not have destroyed it. I would have negotiated with the three Universal Civilizations in exchange for a lot of benefits. Yet Black Star was able to give up on those benefits to choose to destroy the root cause of this disaster. This should be the most beneficial to universal peace… I always thought of Black Star as a pure profit-seeker and didn't expect him to do such a thing. Maybe I was wrong all along."

"That's right…" Judith sighed. "Our understanding of Black Star seems to be too limited. Turns out, he was not such a profit-seeker."

Everyone was in a complicated mood. At this moment, the image of Black Star rose rapidly in their hearts since they did not expect him to perform such a noble move.

Even Jackornitz and those who had some enmity with him had to admit that their impression of Black Star had risen a notch.

While the hope of restoring the virus technology was lost, no one was too disappointed even though they thought it a pity. In fact, they heaved a sigh of relief. This was an outcome they could all accept.

In fact, everyone had this vague worry in their heads as to what would happen after the three Universal Civilizations obtained the Virtual Mutiny Virus. Everyone present was a mechanic, and the Virtual Mutiny Virus would be the most lethal to them. The Virtual Mutiny Virus would pose a huge threat to their Class, which would cause their entire profession to enter hibernation.

In contrast, destroying the virus core was a wise choice. From this point of view, most of the people present were not against Han Xiao's choice and even thought of it as a compromise that would benefit the Beyond Grade As.

They just did not know if Black Star had thought about all this when making a decision.

"Then, what shall we do now?" One of the neutral Beyond Grade As stared at the fierce battle unfolding. "Are we going to intervene?"

"Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor have deep conflicts, as they were originally the President and Vice President of the Development union. This is a dispute over their chosen paths. Let's see how it goes." Kant paused for a while before continuing. "Uh… the dynasty's fleet seems to have switched off the spacetime stability anchor."

…

After fighting for a while, Han Xiao and Manison noticed the release of the spacetime anchor and suddenly broke apart, confronting each other at a higher altitude.

Their machines stopped fighting, returning to the positions of the two, guarding their own avatars.

"Your strength has improved very quickly," Manison said indifferently. "It's just that, without burning your potential, you're still not my opponent."

"Try me."

Han Xiao casually threw back the ball. He maintained his focus, his fighting spirit soaring.

After Black Star's Godlike Battle, the outside world recognized Black Star to have two fighting styles. One would be the regular form, and the other was the explosive form caused by burning his potential.

Han Xiao did not have the ability to 'burn his potential'. He had already obtained the [Mechanical Great Sage] skill as well as a few stacks of the God's Trait Transformation skills. In addition, he had managed to draw several powerful specialties after the attack on Hila. His strength at the moment was considerable, enough to give Manison a run for his money.

However, it was still an undeniable fact that the Mechanic and Machinery abilities of Manison were well above his own.

The Mechanic Emperor had a higher level and God's Trait Transformation level, as well as more mechanical abilities and talents. The quality and quantity of his own machinery were incomparable to Manison's.

Han Xiao had intended to challenge Manison, but because the two of them were only present with their avatars, he would not activate his Character Summon Cards immediately. After all, both of them were Army Style Mechanics, so their fight would be over who had the most troops. A winner would not be easily decided.

From their previous exchange, he had discovered that Manison's clone was not easy to fight. His opponent had taken preventive measures, and not only were his armor and shields strong, his melee skills were also good. The longer one lived, the more versatile one got.

Old Man Manison was still a pinnacle Beyond Grade A, and his HP would not be too low. Furthermore, it was more normal for a Mechanic to use an avatar to fight rather than the main body… with Han Xiao being the only exception.

At this moment, Manison spoke with a chill in his voice. "It's been a long time since I last used this move… Black Star, you're worthy of me showing my true ability."

As he spoke, he waved his hand.

Buzz!

His secondary dimensional army box burst open beside him, and the boundless army of machinery descended, covering the sky.

"Come on, who's afraid‽"

Han Xiao immediately saw through the Mechanic Emperor's intentions and also opened his secondary dimensional army box. Countless mechanical soldiers rushed out, surrounding him.

The size of their mechanical troops continued to soar and quickly covered the sky. On one side was the pitch-black machinery representing Black Star, whilst the other had the white gleaming troops from the Mechanic Emperor. The two sides faced each other far away, separated by a strip of sky, as though that was the dividing line.

The machinery then started to converge on their avatars, quickly forming a huge mechanical structure.

Boom!

The next moment, two Mechanical Deities, one black and one silver, descended on the world!

The black Mechanical Deity was holding a black war halberd, wearing a huge robe, its body wrapped in the blue glow of psionic energy.

The silver Mechanical Deity held onto a purple trident, wearing a cloak and armor, its entire body flashing with golden arcs.

The two Mechanical Deities faced each other, and countless various mechanical soldiers stood by their sides.

"Mechanic Emperor!"

"Black Star!"

The sound waves swept across the entire planet.

The halberd slashed down, and the trident stabbed forward, as both Mechanical Deities simultaneously wielded their weapons.

Their huge bodies seemed to move slowly, but the actual movement was so fast that time distorted around them.

The halberd hit the edge of the trident, and the two Universal Treasure weapons locked onto each other.

Clank!

A resounding clash echoed in everyone's soul, causing a frightening tremor.

An eye-piercing glow appeared at the position of the strike, suddenly blooming and turning into a silvery white lightning as it extended infinitely toward both ends.

At first glance, this looked like a glowing cut, searing the retinas of the countless people watching, as though the impact had torn apart the black backdrop that was the universe!

At the same time, at the Machinery Faith Colony on the surface, be it the believers or the priests, all of them turned their heads up to stare blankly at the sky, watching the two Mechanical Deities engaging in an earth-shaking 'Divine Battle'.

Seeing Black Star swing his war halberd toward the publicly recognized Machinery Faith leader, every believer of the Machinery Faith was stunned.

To see the Mechanical Deities that they worshipped fighting before their very eyes, only one sentence could describe their current feelings…

"Baby, come out and look at God."

…

At the same time, in the flagship of the Crimson Dynasty nearby, the commander, who had gone out to answer an emergency call, hurried back to the bridge at the command room and loudly ordered, "The Ruler has issued her orders. Immediately intervene in the battle and open fire at will!"

The members were dumbfounded. Gazing at the battle between the two Mechanical Deities, as well as the frantically rising energy fluctuations, they subconsciously asked, "Which one… do we help?"

Pa!

The commander raised his hand, slapping the back of the guy who asked this nonsensical question as he raged, "You f*cking tool, help the black one!"

Chapter 1116: The Full Firepower of the Strongest Mechanic

The aftermath of the collision between the two Mechanical Deities stirred up the atmosphere of the planet, forming a huge vortex. The clash between the weapons constantly released sparks of electricity, distorting the viewers' perception of space.

The Mechanical Force was akin to a neural network, circulating around the body of the Mechanical Deities, turning the huge mechanical structure into a part of one's body.

The Celestial Punishment Edge collided against Manison's trident again and again, setting off circles of energy shock waves that were visible to the naked eye. They swept across the sky of the planet, raising an endless gale.

The earth was disturbed to the point that sand and rocks were flying around, with every inch of the ground cracking, and even the Machinery Faith Colony seemed to be teetering on the edge of collapse.

Because the body of the Mechanical Deity was too large to completely display their fighting prowess on the planet, the two fought as they ascended higher, leaving the atmosphere and making outer space their battlefield. Their secondary dimensional army boxes were still sending out troops, and the scale of the battle continued to expand.

Clank!

As the purple trident stabbed at him, Han Xiao blocked it by holding the halberd horizontally, and the majestic energy wrapped along the trident collided with his psionic shield, causing it to continuously flicker.

In the channel, Manison's voice sounded out. "Celestial Punishment Edge? That's a weapon I threw away long ago."

"It all depends on who is using the weapon." Han Xiao's eyes focused, and he squeezed the handle and twisted. Psionic energy burst out, and he took the chance to flick away the trident.

However, the trident vibrated and shot out a phantom copy. Under the assistance of the force field guidance, the rebounding force was converted into a propelling force. The trident only bounced back slightly before it stopped and shot back with an even faster speed.

Han Xiao took a defensive position, resisting Manison's concentrated attacks whilst his thoughts ran fast, analyzing the current situation.

My Celestial Punishment Edge's blueprint came from the Federation of Light, and Manison likely understands the characteristics of this weapon. But I have a limited understanding of the weapon in his hands, so I need to play defensive and test the waters some more…

The lethality of a Universal Treasure weapon far exceeded its ordinary counterparts, so the Mechanical Deities chose to engage in close combat. Only in this manner could they break through each other's thick shields with only half the effort.

Old Man Manison had rich combat experience, and while Han Xiao did not know if he possessed any Universal Treasure level Space Wonders, he definitely had quite a few Universal Treasure mechanical devices, much more than Han Xiao himself.

The trident, as well as the cloak and armor his deity possessed, were definitely at the level of Universal Treasures, but it was unknown just how many more he had.

Activating his Mechanical Deity meant that Manison was going all out. Han Xiao had no doubt about his opponent's endurance. If he was unable to utilize the Mechanical Deity for an extended period of time, he would not lay down all his cards at the start.

Both Manison and I are here with our avatars, and both sides are using Mechanical Deities. It is impossible to easily crush the other's avatar, so it will become a battle of attrition against whose troops are better…

Thinking about this, Han Xiao glanced at the interface.

Just as the two of them started to attack each other, a new mission appeared on his interface.

[Mechanic Emperor Manison—Mechanical Deity Battle!]

The mode of the mission was the same as the other missions that involved challenging Beyond Grade As. He could complete the mission so long as he held on for a certain period of time. The rewards were also similar, having Character Summon Cards and getting to randomly draw a skill.

This was within Han Xiao's expectations. With the three Universal Civilizations present and so many Beyond Grade A onlookers, the influence of this battle was definitely not small and was bound to trigger the mission. Both of them would also not be able to distinguish victory and defeat for a while, so completing the mission was basically a given.

Last time, it was only battling in the Virtual World. This time, fighting him in reality, I can finally see what it's like when Manison goes all out.

Han Xiao suddenly felt the attacks cease and saw that Manison had retreated a step back, in a stance to gain momentum.

The trident was placed by his side, and its blades started rotating rapidly like a drill bit. The golden Mechanical Force was highly compressed on the tip of the blade, shining with a strong, dazzling light akin to a small sun. As the blade rotated, the psionic energy was drawn into it and swirled along, producing a psychedelic effect similar to a water vortex.

Han Xiao's senses were ringing in alarm, and the machinery under his control began to fire at Manison. However, layers of diamond-shaped psionic shields emerged on the surface of Manison's Mechanical Deity, blocking out all the concentrated fire of the machinery.

Whoosh!

Manison's figure suddenly blurred, and he accelerated in an instant, the shining trident thrusting out so quickly it turned into a gold and blue beam.

Han Xiao held the halberd horizontally in defense and raised his Emperor's Cape to generate a powerful shield.

Ka!

The trident was once again blocked by the halberd.

However, the golden blue piercing light continued unabated, shooting out from the main blade of the trident to pierce through his Emperor's Cape, hitting the abdomen of his Machinery Deity.

Swoosh!

It tore through his abdomen, disappearing into the distance and leaving a huge penetrating wound in Han Xiao's Mechanical Deity. All the parts within the beam were annihilated into molecular-grade fragments, and the edges of the wound showed fiery red melting marks.

What a powerful penetrating force! Han Xiao's heart was shocked.

In terms of just strength, this trident was indeed higher than the Celestial Punishment Edge. It was not just because of the blueprint but also because the Mechanic Emperor's creation was of a higher quality and possessed stronger Mechanical Force bonuses, which served as a multifaceted suppression.

With just a thought, the surrounding mechanical soldiers stopped fighting, turning around and converging on him as they transformed into parts to supplement the gap in his Mechanical Deity.

The Mechanical Deity itself was already a structure composed of a large number of machines. As long as there were no fatal injuries and one had enough energy and machinery, they could recover from all sorts of injuries.

Manison was about to seize the opportunity to pursue his attack, but at this moment, a sudden change occurred.

Dense beams of dark energy shot out diagonally, blasting into Manison's troops and exploding the shields of countless mechanical soldiers, disrupting the formation.

Both of them stopped moving, glancing toward the source of the attack. The third party that fired was the fleet belonging to the Crimson Dynasty, its countless battleship weapons constantly firing toward the Mechanic Emperor's troops.

The dynasty came to aid me?

Han Xiao had the thought in his heart but did not find it a surprise.

With the Mechanic Emperor as a negative example, Han Xiao destroying the virus core was considered good behavior in the eyes of the three Universal Civilizations, increasing his positive image by a lot. While the virus technology would not be made available, it was indeed an acceptable result.

Under such a premise, when the dynasty saw that his own relationship with the Mechanic Emperor had soured, they naturally had to express their stance. Rationally, they could not just sit back and watch idly as an ally that had completed a feat beneficial to the peace of the universe fight alone. Thus, their probability of intervening in the battlefield was almost guaranteed.

However, the attitudes of the other two civilizations were more ambiguous, sitting by the sidelines with no intention of interfering.

The federation was not ignorant of Manison's position, but it was another thing to show support to him now. After Manison just demonstrated his intention to hide the virus and antagonize the three Universal Civilizations, the federation obviously could not provide support at this time, so they sat on the sidelines and watched the dynasty attack their 'ally'.

As for the church, this was not their business, so they happily sat at the side with popcorn.

The three Universal Civilizations' troops that were stationed at the trap node were mainly there to prevent the Beyond Grade A from absconding with the virus, so they naturally possessed some measure of combat capabilities.

While the spacetime anchor was now lifted, allowing the mechanics to summon troops on a large scale, and only the dynasty was currently shooting at him, Manison still could not afford to take them lightly.

"Annoying flies."

Manison gestured with his trident, and a portion of the mechanical soldiers emerging from the secondary dimensional army box split off, forming an array to exchange fire with the dynasty's fleet.

The Army Style Mechanics were the Supers best suited for interstellar warfare. If it were any other profession, they were bound to be restrained by the suppressive firepower of the fleet. However, mechanics were able to take out a part of their soldiers to fight on their own, minimizing the restraining abilities of the fleet.

If they wished to cause considerable interference to the Mechanic Emperor going all-out, the scale of the dynasty's troops had to be hundreds if not thousands of times larger.

Han Xiao understood that this was a short reprieve granted by the dynasty and immediately repaired the damage to his Mechanical Deity.

At this moment, Manison turned toward Han Xiao.

"Black Star, you seem to have grown once again. I've been watching you for a long time. The more battles you go through, the faster your growth. Is this the basis for your confidence?"

"Have you not battled for too long a time, to forget that running your mouth is to give opportunities to your opponent?"

Han Xiao did not hesitate, and his Celestial Punishment Edge lashed out.

The psionic energy converged into a biting blue blade of light, slashing toward Manison's body. The highly concentrated energy resembled a bright half-moon sapphire.

Manison, however, remained motionless. The Universal Treasure cloak on his body suddenly shook, and a spherical white shield covering his entire body popped out, giving off a hazy texture like a cloud of flowing white smoke.

The light blade from the Celestial Punishment Edge hit the white shield, and the smoke on the surface of the shield suddenly accelerated, turning into swirling patterns. The sapphire-colored light blade suddenly shattered, turning into motes of light and scattering into the sky.

The next moment, the energy spots seemed to be drawn and absorbed by the shield, and the now discolored shield was swallowed and retracted into the armor of the Mechanical Deity, converted into energy to supplement the consumption of the Mechanical Deity.

Absorbing damage to replenish energy?

Han Xiao's eyes turned solemn.

"I was very interested in your Indestructible Body, and there are many similar abilities and magics in the universe, but none of them have reached to a degree comparable to yours. Thus, I specially researched into this and explored your ability principles through your battle videos. I finally created this Universal Treasure level equipment that is dedicated to the Mechanical Deity, imitating part of your abilities," Manison faintly said. "It seems like the actual combat effect is quite good."

Han Xiao felt his head ache, secretly envious of Manison.

The Mechanic Emperor could research and create his own Universal Treasure, unlike me, who had no idea what to do before I unlocked Awakening Points!

Just craft what you're lacking in. This is the true style of a proper mechanic!

At this moment, Manison slowly commented, "Black Star, you're still too green. I've seen many talented Mechanics in my life. Before they were taught a lesson, they always thought that the strength of their talent could make up for the lack of accumulation. I once taught this lesson to many of them, and right now, I shall also teach you the same lesson. A Mechanic needs to settle down and accumulate. Time is our greatest source of strength!"

His voice echoed loudly in the wide area communication channel. At the same time, a different type of troop burst forward from his secondary dimensional army box.

This special unit possessed many different individuals. Some were luxuriously equipped special mechanical soldiers, while others were luminous energy beings. The combat power of each individual was amazing, and they killed their way into the battlefield as though unafraid of death, sweeping aside all of Han Xiao's mechanical soldiers.

And when these individuals were killed and destroyed, there was no need to utilize skills such as [Waste Modification]. Their bodies automatically regenerated, and they went back into battle without any reduction in strength.

The moment these troops entered the battle, it overturned the entire situation, gaining an absolute advantage.

Han Xiao's pupils shrank as he recognized the origin of this unit.

Manison's Aces—the Indestructible Mechanic Empire!

Without waiting for him to observe, Manison's Apostle Weapons led the army, smashing into the battlefield from the other direction, causing huge casualties to Han Xiao's troops.

Han Xiao took a deep breath.

Glancing roughly, he could tell that there were at least forty to fifty Apostle Weapons present!

This meant that Manison's [Apostle Life Creation] skill had broken through the upper limit by forty to fifty levels at least!

In this violent clash, the scale of troops which Manison released accounted for about seventy percent of his total, and all of them were under the Mechanical Force bonuses. Manison still looked at ease, his Mechanical Force completely covering all the soldiers.

Assuming that one point of Mechanical Force for Han Xiao could give bonuses to ten soldiers, Manison's Mechanical Force could aid over twenty-five!

This difference was not only due to Attribute, Talent, and Skills but also because of the gaps in their equipment.

Han Xiao personally saw Manison pulling out four more Universal Treasures dedicated to his Mechanical Deity from the secondary dimensional army box. All of the equipment types were different, not only allowing the Mechanical Deity to be armed to the teeth but also expanding its size. After using all these treasures, Manison's Mechanical Deity increased significantly in strength.

Some Class-specific Universal Treasures would provide a certain increase to its user. For example, Han Xiao's King suit could provide additional Machinery Affinity bonuses. Manison's equipment was similar with all-round enhancements to his Mechanical Force and his body.

At the same time, Han Xiao realized that he had also been invaded on a virtual level. Manison had summoned Finette, the ancestor of the AI civilization, and allowed it to perform a Virtual Intrusion with a large group of Virtual Life Forms to fight with Han Xiao on a virtual level for control of the machinery.

"Old man, you really have a lot of methods…"

Just as Han Xiao had this thought, a flash of light appeared in front of him. He only saw the afterimage of Manison's fully equipped Mechanical Deity, slamming down with the trident.

He hurriedly raised his halberd to block, but the shock wave penetrated his body, jarring his ears with the sound.

Clank!

The terrifying force was transmitted along his arms, and the countless built-in shock absorbers were instantly scrapped. Large pieces of his outer armor cracked, and Han Xiao's Mechanical Deity appeared to be full of cracks.

If he had not obtained the [Machinery Control Master] from Jackornitz, gaining an additional thirty-five percent efficiency bonus for his Mechanical suits, Han Xiao doubted that the arms of his Mechanical Deity would still be intact.

Manison, however, did not slow down in his attacks. Taking advantage of Han Xiao's stun, the newly-equipped Universal Treasure wing-type self-automated Planetary Obliteration Cannon shot out a thick psionic beam with a diameter of more than a hundred meters.

Boom!

Han Xiao was blown away by the Planetary Obliteration Cannon, and his shield shattered under the continuous attacks. Manison followed, chasing after him, his trident spinning rapidly as it shot out waves of light, continuously dismembering the opponent's Mechanical Deity.

The Mechanic Emperor had shown his true mettle, fully opening up the Mechanical Deity, machinery, and the Virtual layer, a three pronged attack!

Seeing this situation, the Beyond Grade A avatars on the sidelines avoided the aftermath of the battle, feeling the powerful suppressive aura of Manison flooding the area. They chatted quietly in their channel.

"It's been a long time since I've seen Manison go all-out. It's still so terrifying…" Kant recalled some bad memories.

"The Mechanic Emperor is still the Mechanic Emperor." The Sun Hunter's voice was subdued.

'Mechanical Catastrophe' Francisco shook his head. "It's different from the battle in the Flickering World. This time, it's an internal battle between two pinnacle Beyond Grade A Mechanics. Black Star is completely suppressed. Luckily, it was his avatar that came this time."

The man in question, Han Xiao, who was being beaten up, did not know that he was a topic of conversation for the audience.

He was trying his best to resist Manison's frenzied attack, gritting his teeth secretly.

F*ck, old man, you're really good at fighting!

You're really forcing me to 'explode'!

Chapter 1117: You Pay to Win, I Cheat, We All Have a Bright Future

Manison showcased his full firepower, and with his P2W[1] method of strengthening his foundation, he quickly occupied an absolute advantage and completely suppressed Black Star.

This scene also fell into the eyes of the Machinery Faith believers who were watching the battle on the surface of Planet Magnetic Cloud.

"Am I dreaming? I can see the descent of two Mechanical Deities with my very own eyes in my lifetime."

"Quickly record it. No one knows when the Mechanic Emperor last went all out. This is precious first-hand data!"

"Why did the two of them start fighting?"

"It seems like a challenge. Black Star's situation doesn't look good."

"The Mechanic Emperor is still the Mechanic Emperor, having occupied the highest position in our faith for so many years. Black Star is still too young. It's unknown what will happen in the future, but right now, how could he be an opponent for the Mechanic Emperor?"

"Black Star set a historical record a while ago, and I thought that he had already arrived at the same level as the Mechanic Emperor. Now it seems like he's still lacking in accumulation."

The onlookers were extremely excited. As enthusiastic fans of the top mechanics, they considered the experiences of each pinnacle Beyond Grade A their precious heirlooms. While they did not know the reason for the battle, this did not prevent them from discussing the fight.

While their settlement was threatened by the aftermath of the battle, few of the believers were willing to leave.

In their opinion, as long as they could watch the magical battle of the Mechanical Deities with their own eyes, it was nothing to bear some risks in return. If not for the fact that the land only reached this high, they would have moved even closer to them.

On the top floor of the Machinery Faith temple, many of the priests looked at the virtual screen in front of them, which showed the image of Han Xiao and Manison in outer space.

"Both Deities have moved away from the battlefield, but the settlement might still be in danger. Grand Priest, should we evacuate the organization's followers?" one of the priests softly asked.

The Grand Priest in question was staring at the screen quietly, for fear of missing any second of what the image showed. He watched in fascination and did not even turn back as he said, "Wait, let me watch it for a while more."

By the side, someone muttered, "While I don't understand why they started fighting, there should be no suspense in the result. Both parties are here as avatars, and they're only fighting based on machinery abilities. In this regard, Black Star is indeed below the Mechanic Emperor."

"It seems like that."

The various priests also nodded. Having seen the situation, the majority would regard it as so.

However, no one would be disappointed over this, because in the eyes of the Machinery Faith, this was a normal situation, a given.

However, the situation suddenly changed, and the energy readings at the edge of the screen suddenly soared.

The Grand Priest was taken aback.

"Black Star's energy fluctuations… suddenly spiked‽"

…

At the same moment, the three Universal Civilizations were also watching the live broadcast of the battle between the two. The flashing lights on the screen reflected in the faces of the trio.

The Arcane Church's Pope turned to glance at Urranrell. "Your Excellency, Black Star doesn't seem to be in too good a state."

"It's expected." Urranrell was calm. "We never hoped that Black Star would fight with the Mechanic Emperor. He has amazing potential and needs more time to strengthen his foundations, even if his growth always exceeds expectations. It's still too early for him to fight against the Mechanic Emperor head on."

"However, the first to release the spacetime anchor was your dynasty's fleet. It seems that you wish for them to fight with all their strength instead," the Pope joked.

"You're mistaken. Since the virus has been resolved, of course the blockade should be lifted. We cannot forcibly retain the avatars of the mechanics. We opened the blockade in hopes that the Mechanic Emperor would leave, but it seems like he wishes to show his strength in front of us," Urranrell solemnly replied.

Her order to close the spacetime anchor was not an arrogant decision. Urranrell was aware that Black Star could leave the area at any time even under the restraint of spacetime, but in her opinion, Black Star did not do anything wrong. Destroying the virus core was an act beneficial to the universe, so why should he run? The one that should be running was the Mechanic Emperor.

"It's understandable that after being made a fool of by Black Star, the Mechanic Emperor would definitely retaliate." The Pope glanced at Bader.

Bader continued staring at the screen, silently telling them to just continue chatting among themselves whilst he acted as the backdrop.

Seeing this, the Pope knew that Bader was not going to talk about the Mechanic Emperor for the time being, so he withdrew his gaze and continued. "However, Black Star is not on the Mechanic Emperor's level. It is likely he will lose."

"We don't wish for Black Star to have conflicts with the Mechanic Emperor right now, but since they have started fighting, the dynasty will support Black Star to the end. There's no need to back down," Urranrell decisively stated.

In terms of their stances, the three Universal Civilizations were on Han Xiao's side, but they did not deny the fact that the Mechanic Emperor was still more powerful.

Furthermore, Black Star was only using his avatar, so losing to the Mechanic Emperor was not unacceptable. After all, Black Star's age was but a fraction of Manison's, and his future potential was promising.

Just as the trio were thinking of that, an abnormality appeared on the battlefield.

Han Xiao's energy reading suddenly skyrocketed, climbing to an astonishing level.

The three of them were startled.

"Black Star's switched modes? He's burned his potential again‽" Bader was stunned.

The Pope was dumbstruck.

"This is too impulsive. Does he need to struggle like this…"

The fact that Black Star had two modes of fighting was no secret. His regular mode would not be able to defeat the Mechanic Emperor; this was something the trio knew well in their hearts. But they also understood that Black Star's fighting prowess would only peak when he burned his potential.

Black Star had utilized his burning of potential to shock the entire universe during his Godlike Battle. Whether such a form could match up to the Mechanic Emperor, no one knew.

Urranrell's expression was not too good. Black Star's actions were once again out of her expectations.

He could obviously utilize a slow and methodical approach to develop and accumulate his foundation, but he just had to burn his potential to explode in strength. She was unable to accept such an approach.

Didn't you already burn your potential once? You still want to burn more? How much more potential do you have to waste!

Black Star was the dynasty's ally, and she had high hopes for him. The position he had taken was also in line with universal peace. Now that Black Star had burned his potential, it was a loss to the dynasty.

In her rational judgment, this move would no doubt be a loss in blood, but in an emotional sense, she appreciated the never-say-die attitude of Black Star.

The choice Han Xiao had made lived up to the trust she put in him. Whichever way she looked at Han Xiao now, she found it very pleasing to the eye.

…

Clank!

The trident once again cut open the shield provided by the Emperor's Cape and drew a deep line on the abdomen of Han Xiao's Mechanical Deity. Many mechanical parts were dug out, and the body of the Mechanical Deity now was scarred with defects.

The surrounding mechanical soldiers wanted to come over to repair the wounds, but they were all blocked by the troops of Manison. They could not overcome the blockade of the combination of the Indestructible Mechanic Empire, Apostle Weapons, and the Mechanical Life troops.

The performance of his machinery was suppressed by the Mechanic Emperor on almost all fronts, with only his attack power being stronger than the latter. This was all thanks to his [Legendary Battle Technique], which was not something to be trifled with. It was only that the majority of the attacks were being absorbed by Manison's Indestructible Mechanic Empire, which was not afraid of destruction or damage.

The legend of the Indestructible Body had long been spread through Galaxy, and because Manison had no idea if this also applied to Han Xiao's avatar, all his attacks were concentrated toward the non-critical parts of the Mechanical Deity, aiming to destroy the majority of Han Xiao's machinery in the shortest time possible.

At this moment, Han Xiao was finding it difficult to resist, and the thoughts spun rapidly in his head.

If this continues, my Mechanical Deity will be cut apart piece by piece. Manison has the advantage now, and if I were to allow him to attack so unscrupulously, it will greatly consume my machinery. I have to stop being forced into this passive state…

The large number of Universal Treasures had greatly enhanced Manison's combat power.

His own foundations were not solid enough. If he wished to bridge this gap, he could only do his best to improve his attributes, especially Intellect, which would directly affect his Mechanic class's abilities.

Opening the interface, Han Xiao saw that he had accumulated quite the bit of experience over this past month or so while the three Universal Civilizations were preparing for this operation.

He originally wished to hoard it until he could promote, but the plan could not keep up with the changes. The experience urgently needed to be turned into combat prowess.

Han Xiao did not hesitate, taking out most of his experience and using it to upgrade his blueprints on a large scale in exchange for more Awakening Points.

His current accumulated experience was not enough to gain a hundred Awakening Points, which did not meet the conditions of obtaining a Unique Talent. However, Han Xiao's purpose this time was not to generate Unique Talents but to replace his Awakening Points with Free Attribute Points in order to pump them into his Intellect. In that instant, his Intellect attribute rose by almost 8,000 points!

He had also accumulated more than 4,000 Free Attribute Points, and after placing 1,000 into his Endurance, allowing it to break through the 15,000 point threshold, he placed the remaining 2,000 points into Intellect.

Adding both together, his own Intellect attribute skyrocketed by more than 10,000 points in total, breaking through the 30,000 threshold and approaching 40,000!

This was his fastest increase in history!

After completing this delightful step, Han Xiao did not hesitate to start activating his Character Summon Cards.

_____________________

[Mechanic Emperor Character Summon Card—The Ancient Ones]!

Effect: +20% INT, +10% MYS, +2 to all Skill levels, last for 24 hours.

[Nero Character Summon Card—Perfect Mechanical Sense]!

Effect: x1.4 Machinery Affinity, Grade of Mechanic equipment that receive Mechanical Force bonuses are temporarily increased by 1 – 2 tiers (highest quality will not exceed Pink Grade), +4 to all Mechanic Skills.

_____________________

However, Han Xiao did not stop here. He activated [Polar Channel Flow—Blood Rage], and his HP value plummeted.

At the same time, the additional effect of [Advanced Strengthened Life] came into play. For every forty percent of his HP lost, his attributes all temporarily increased by ten percent!

Since Manison will not hit me, I'll hit myself!

He also had talents such as [One Against the World], which gave him an eleven percent bonus to all attributes, and [Battlefield Wisdom], which gave him a fifteen percent bonus to Intellect… Han Xiao took out everything he had.

Old Man Manison has a solid foundation?

What's scary about that?

If you know how to P2W, then I can just cheat!

We're evenly matched in this regard!

This wave of bonuses came into play in an instant, and a powerful force surged throughout his body. The energy fluctuations Han Xiao was releasing suddenly skyrocketed.

Manison keenly noticed the change in Han Xiao and was shocked.

"You…"

Before he could finish speaking, Han Xiao turned his defense into offense, knocking the trident aside with an elbow and slashing the Celestial Punishment Edge down diagonally.

A highly compressed psionic energy enveloped the blade, drawing a blue trajectory line.

Swoosh!

The power behind this slash exceeded the upper limit of which the blue protective shield could handle and broke through the defense.

The blade suppressed the trident before embedding itself deep within Manison's battle armor.

The next moment, the psionic energy wrapped around the blade caused a violent explosion!

Manison's offensive was interrupted, and a huge portion of the Mechanical Deity's body was slashed away. A huge wound was left in the chest of his battle armor, left by the eruption of the psionic energy. A large portion of his outer armor was torn and corroded.

This was the first time Manison had been repelled since the fight began.

The one-sided battle was instantly turned around by Han Xiao!

"Eat a few more of my blades!"

Han Xiao pressed the advantage, slashing out in rapid succession to seize the battle rhythm.

The combat capability of Han Xiao's Mechanical Deity was enhanced in every respect, and the gap in their combat capability was shortened. Han Xiao was no longer suppressed.

His increase in Mechanical strength was reflected in his surrounding mechanical soldiers. The Black Star troops experienced an increase in their combat power, successfully breaking through the blockade of the Mechanic Emperor's troops, approaching Han Xiao to repair the damage to his Mechanical Deity.

Manison finally stabilized himself, and while waving his trident to counter Han Xiao's attacks, he spoke on the wide area channel with astonishment.

"You burned your potential again‽"

"Think what you want. How's that blade taste?" Han Xiao laughed.

"… You're ruining your talent!" Manison's tone turned cold.

He originally only wished to teach Han Xiao a lesson but did not expect him to burn his own potential in retaliation.

To consume his future potential to fight a battle with their avatars was a foolish act from Manison's point of view. Even if this battle involved factors such as prestige or speaking rights, it would still be a loss-making business.

He was puzzled by this. Maybe their ideals were different, but he did not think that Black Star was such an impulsive person.

He had no way of knowing Han Xiao's thoughts. Since he was willing to waste his potential, Manison was also happy since they were all competitors.

However, while he sneered at Han Xiao's approach, he had to admit that the combat power Han Xiao displayed in his mode was extremely strong, which allowed him to immediately recover from his disadvantage.

If he did not go all-out, he would definitely suffer!

Moreover, Manison felt that the increase in Han Xiao's combat power this time was higher than the first. This discovery surprised him.

What is this? Can burning your potential even be trained‽

Also, since when was Polar Channel Flow so strong? How did I not know about this?

What is behind of Black Star's explosive ability? How is the effect so good and yet unknown‽

Feeling the surge in Han Xiao's aura, Manison was both surprised and suspicious.

[1] [Annotation text missing] Back

Chapter 1118: A Just Cause Enjoys Abundant Support

The flames of war blazed in outer space, and the two Mechanical Deities, one white and one black, collided into a blur. The exchanges between their weapons continued to explode outward in shock waves.

Psionic energy collided with psionic energy, and metal crashed against metal!

Surrounded by their huge mechanical armies, which hovered around them like crows, they fought tirelessly. The entire area was filled with molten metal caused by the high-intensity energy rays, which would rapidly cool and condense into weird-shaped metal blocks. Some fell down to the surface of the planet, while others turned into space debris, orbiting Planet Magnetic Cloud.

It looked as though two gods that could penetrate the sky and earth were leading their respective armies to engage in a battle of the universe.

This burst by Han Xiao allowed him to obtain a significant amount of combat power. His Intellect rose by almost forty percent, and his degree of Machinery Affinity also skyrocketed. With the twenty percent increase from Manison's Character Summon Card, it only further magnified his strength.

According to his calculations, these tens of thousands of Attribute Points in Intellect enhanced his Mechanic abilities way beyond his rewards from the attack on Hila mission. It could be said that this was the current peak state of Han Xiao!

Because he did not have the time to familiarize himself with his newfound strength, Han Xiao's control over his power was not as fine as it should have been. However, this still gave him quite the confidence, and riding on the increase in his senses, he adapted a pure offensive style.

The sharp glint of a blade flashed continuously as the Celestial Punishment Edge twirled in Han Xiao's hands. Every slash he made was heavy and unrelenting, fierce and ruthless. He seemed to be embodying the spirit of Guan Yu[1], killing his way through with reckless abandon.

His boosted Mechanical Force controlled the Mechanical Deity to become even more agile than before. The Celestial Punishment Edge in his hands seemed to exude an even higher amount of strength, breaking through the shield around Manison and leaving gaping wounds in his armor.

While Manison was surprised at Han Xiao's combat power after his boost, it did not affect his performance. With the support of his six Universal Treasure Equipment, his trident endlessly counterattacked, poking large and small holes in the body of Han Xiao's Mechanical Deity.

Both sides suffered from various injuries, being evenly matched. Only these two figures could be seen traversing the starry sky, taking the universe as their battlefield. The trident and the halberd crossed dozens of times in an instant, blasting out electrical arcs.

While it seemed like they were simply fighting each other in close combat, the two parties were actually mixing their melees with a lot of advanced technology. Force fields, electromagnetic pulses, and energy conversions were merged seamlessly. In addition, there were also countless control-type mechanical devices exerting their effects. Various restrains were wrapped around each Mechanical Deity like a spider web, restricting their actions.

At the same time, they also maintained their artillery bombardment, with countless muzzles around their bodies spewing high-energy beams like a torrential downpour blasting into each other's shields, creating fireworks.

This seemed to paint a beautiful picture, but it was full of an energy that could destroy the world.

The Mechanic Emperor's Apostle Weapons were too powerful in combat, having a huge advantage in the Mechanical Army fight. Han Xiao could only continue to pull out his troops from the secondary dimensional army box, using numbers to make up for his lack of advanced combatants.

The battle gradually approached a climax, and under the countless excited and shocked gazes, the two fought in outer space for quite a lengthy period, unable to extricate themselves.

Swoosh!

Han Xiao's blade condensed and swept across, slashing into Manison's neck and slicing three quarters of the way through, almost beheading the Deity.

At the same time, the trident pierced through Han Xiao's head, scattering countless broken machinery.

The two Mechanical Deities, however, acted like they were unaware of the injuries. They raised their hands, grabbing the opponent's weapon that was embedded in their bodies before pulling it out. They raised their legs and kicked toward each other's crotches. Their moves were at least ninety percent synchronous with each other!

While they shot backward, both parties simultaneously raised their hands, throwing their weapons at the same time.

Both their huge weapons shot through the air, colliding halfway before bouncing apart.

The trident slammed down toward the planet surface, landing in the wilderness with a loud bang, printing an outline on the planet's crust.

The Celestial Punishment Edge spun off course and smashed into the battlefield of the mechanical armies, wiping out countless soldiers on both sides.

At this moment, Manison's figure suddenly flickered and disappeared as he warped through space. The next moment, he appeared behind Han Xiao, and a bright light shot out from his waist.

A silver-colored short sword was pulled out its sheath, and the sword drew an upward arc. The light of the sword swept across Han Xiao's waist, instantly bisecting the Mechanical Deity.

Han Xiao reacted quickly, turning his upper body to whip his arm condensed with psionic energy toward Manison. It broke through the shield, and the remaining force slammed into Manison's head, beheading it and throwing it out toward one of the three Universal Civilizations' fleets. It was smashed into pieces by the intercepting fire from the fleet.

At the same time, Han Xiao's severed lower body disintegrated, re-transforming into mechanical soldiers, which once again integrated back with the Mechanical Deity.

The Celestial Punishment Edge, which had been sent off course, stopped in midair before flying back as though being pulled by an invisible rope, forcing Manison to retreat as it circled around before landing back in Han Xiao's hands.

Another Universal Treasure.

Seeing Manison take out another weapon, Han Xiao felt bitter in his heart.

His Emperor's Cape had the effect of strengthening the internal structure of his Mechanical Deity, but the short sword sliced through it easily. It had to be Gold Grade equipment.

The fact that his foundation was insufficient was already a sad issue, but after fighting for such a long time, the Mechanic Emperor was still so fierce and lively, not showing any signs of weaknesses. His reserves were unfathomable, and his endurance also surprised Han Xiao.

It stood to reason that so long as a lot of energy was consumed, the number of bonus stacks would decrease, resulting in a temporary decline in status and attributes.

Because he had the ability to convert HP to energy, he had always stayed at the peak, but this old man seemed to have eaten Viagra, for him to be able to maintain this state for such a long period of time!

While the old man also managed to come out with equipment that would allow him to convert damage to energy, Han Xiao discovered that there was a limitation to this piece of Gold Grade equipment. There was a cooldown required after each absorption, unlike his own talent which was effective anywhere.

Thus, maybe Old Man Manison possessed some kind of talent that would allow him to retain his energy bonuses but at the cost of a reduction in strength. That sort of ability was rare but not unique.

But this was not the main point. Han Xiao was surprised to discover that not only did Manison's strength not drop, it was even slowly rising.

He's probably the same as me, having talents to continuously obtain bonuses in battle… He's worthy of being the top powerhouse in the universe, just as difficult to handle as myself.

Han Xiao ground his teeth.

Even after fighting for so long, they could only be evenly matched. Attempting to expand on his advantage would only cause him to be blocked by Manison time and again, as if he was some spring that could not be completely compressed.

Fortunately, the same was true for Manison. Neither was able to suppress the other.

The time for the Character Summon Cards is ultimately limited, and I cannot keep this state up forever. Manison's attributes are also slowly climbing, and if we continue to fight, the situation that I finally stabilized will be reversed once more… Damn, it's usually me who kills the enemy after a protracted battle. Now I've finally met someone who can last longer than me.

Han Xiao analyzed the grim situation, but his mood was actually quite relaxed.

It was a lonely thing to not be able to find an opponent. It was rare to also face a strong enemy that required him to utilize all his moves. He had fought heartily and comfortably, venting all his energy on the Mechanic Emperor.

Furthermore, he had managed to witness Manison's combat power to estimate the gap in their strength, which was not small at all.

In fact, the hit-and-run tactics were still effective against Manison. While his avatar might be durable, it was in no way comparable to himself. The problem was that the other party had deeply hidden himself within the Mechanical Deity, and he could not damage the other party in any way. As long as he did not shatter the Mechanical Deity, there was no way he could hurt his opponent's avatar. This was something he needed to pay attention to. In other words, he was now obtaining experience on how to deal with Manison.

As all sorts of thoughts flashed through his mind, Han Xiao spoke in the wide-area communication channel.

"Mechanic Emperor, we're evenly matched, and there won't be any results even if we fight for the next ten days. Are you sure you want to continue?"

"You're thinking too much. I don't think you can hold on for so long," Manison replied blandly. "This should be your current peak, but you're at most only able to fight evenly with me. How long can your burst mode last?"

"Never counted, but it should last till the end of our fight."

Since no one knew of his details, Han Xiao just made up a lie calmly.

"So, you wish to fight a protracted battle with me?" Manison let out some emotionless laughter, as though scorning Han Xiao's confidence. "How much of your machinery can you waste? Is it even a fraction of mine?"

"Isn't it just money? It's not like anyone here lacks cash." Han Xiao smirked.

While he spoke this manner, the Great Mechanic Han had to still admit that the old man had a stronger ability to make money.

He wished to test out his strength against Manison, not to show off his accumulation.

Han Xiao also did not forget that Manison still had some Beyond Grade A 'collectibles' in his hands, which were not used. They had probably not come out because this was not a good time to use them, since he did not wish to show them off in front of the three Universal Civilizations.

In other words, this might not be Manison's true strength.

While their growth models had a difference of heaven and earth, there was one thing that Han Xiao agreed with—the importance of accumulation to a Mechanic.

Were Manison's attributes higher than his? That remained to be seen, but his opponent definitely had much stronger machinery compared to his. That was due to his accumulation over the years.

The Mechanic class was different from all the other professions. Even when everyone reached a bottleneck in power, the Mechanics could ignore the bottleneck and improve their own combat power through manufacturing, research, and development of machinery. Thus, it could be said that P2W was the root behind all the powerful Mechanics!

This gap is not small at all… Han Xiao shook his head.

While he considered himself affluent, compared with Manison, who was filled with Universal Treasures, he suddenly looked a lot more shabby.

In this manner, the difficulty of me defeating Manison currently is too high. Manison wants to beat me in order to maintain his face, so I have to draw with him at least. It is impossible to retreat or escape, or else I will lose all credibility…

Just as Han Xiao was thinking of which trump card he should utilize, the situation on the battlefield changed once more.

A different group of machines suddenly broke into the battlefield, attacking Manison's troops at the same time, separating the battlefield and preventing the two forces from fighting.

A dozen streams of light flew from the distance, stopping between the two as they faced Manison.

Han Xiao and Manison looked at the dozen or so figures, which were the other Beyond Grade A avatars originally watching the show.

"Mechanic Emperor, let's stop here," Kant said.

Manison glanced at the others, slowly asking, "You all are helping him?"

"Black Star doesn't need our help. There's no clear winner now, and even if you fight for a month, the battle likely won't end." Kant deliberately spoke using the wide area channel. He chuckled. "It's impossible for the three Universal Civilizations and us to be here watching you for a month, so we'll consider today a tie."

"Tie?" Manison's tone sank slightly.

"Isn't it so?" Kant smiled as he replied.

Manison narrowed his eyes. "And if I wish to continue fighting?"

"We are also people that take our dignity seriously. Since we have spoken, we will act." Kant laughed. "If you don't give us face, then I'm sorry, but we can only join you for a couple of rounds."

Just as he spoke, all the Beyond Grade As collectively took a step forward. While they did not say it clearly, their intention to protect Han Xiao was clear.

Want to touch Black Star?

You'll have to do it through a gang fight!

Seeing this, Manison sank into silence.

The battlefield was at the Machinery Faith temple, so he naturally wished to suppress Han Xiao. While Han Xiao's burst mode was strong, it was only temporary. If they continued fighting, he was confident in winning.

However, the situation caused his plans to fail.

The battle between them was interfered with, and Manison could naturally see what they intended to do. They wished to create a situation where it was a tie, forcing him to accept this instead of fighting for a win.

After thinking for a bit, he understood the reason.

Manison raised his head to look at Han Xiao, speaking in a somewhat complicated tone.

"This is really… a case of a just cause enjoying abundant support."

Having spoken, he did not intend to stay, collecting all his troops and recalling his avatar, cancelling the Lord's Descent skill before leaving.

No matter how confident he was, he did not plan to challenge all the Beyond Grade As present.

Seeing this, Kant laughed before looking at Han Xiao.

"Alright, this matter is over."

Han Xiao was a little surprised. "I thought you'd continue spectating. Why did you suddenly help me?"

If the dynasty aided him, he could understand this. But why did the mechanics from the federation and the church also stand up for him?

Could it be that my heroic act of destroying the virus core convinced them to forget their grudges?

Sigh, blame me then, for inadvertently failing to restrain my inner charm, infecting and influencing them too much.

[Mechanical Catastrophe] Francisco snorted coldly. "Don't over think this. We're not doing this for you."

"You could have fought for over ten days, so how could the three Universal Civilizations continue to keep watching? Thus, they asked us to interfere and end the battle."

"Then that's weird. Couldn't you have done that earlier? You had to wait till we reached this stage?"

"Hehe, it's not just an order. All of us were quite happy to see the Mechanic Emperor suffer a little," Kant said in a tone full of schadenfreude.

Alright, I understand now…

The majority of people present had been bullied by Manison before but could only hold in their anger. Seeing Black Star's brave performance, they felt that they could take the opportunity to attack Manison, so they chose to intervene.

The result of deliberately promoting a tie was the small revenge for this group of people. This would shake the Mechanic Emperor's position as the main deity for the Machinery Faith, building momentum for Black Star.

As long as the record was set, Black Star would be able to disperse the firm belief in the Mechanic Emperor among those of the Machinery Faith, allowing Manison to suffer. Of course, the premise of doing so was that Black Star had to be able to withstand the Mechanic Emperor. If Han Xiao kept getting beaten up, then this group would not have deliberately chosen the best time to help him.

Intervening in the battle was not just because of orders but also a decision from their hearts.

As for whether or not there was a factor of admiration due to Black Star's actions, only they themselves knew.

Once Han Xiao understood this, he also sighed in relief.

Indeed, the more people you have close relations with, the more benefits you obtain.

Ignoring how Manison has lived for so long and has a wide range of contacts, in the eyes of the Beyond Grade A Mechanics, the Mechanic Emperor's image is worth very little. He's offended too many of his peers in the Beyond Grade A realm!

As the saying went, 'a just cause attracts much support; an unjust one finds little'!

[1] [Annotation text missing] Back

Chapter 1119: Poaching People

After Manison withdrew, the operation to deal with the Virtual Mutiny Virus core was finally settled.

Han Xiao dismissed his Mechanical Deity, putting away the combat troops. He only left a few maintenance teams to cooperate with the three Universal Civilizations in cleaning up the battlefield.

While he and Manison had deliberately moved away from the battlefield to prevent the troops from firing in the direction of the planet, the aftermath of the battle still had a considerable impact on Planet Magnetic Cloud.

The earth seemed to have been sanded down by a file, and its 'skin and flesh' that was filed down turned into sand and dust in the sky. From outer space, the surface was full of traces of falling objects as well as pits and ravines, of which the most conspicuous was the ravine left by Manison's trident, transforming the wilderness into a large group of rift-like valleys.

The settlements of those in the Machinery Faith were affected to a certain extent, and their protective shield was dim, but it was not wiped out. It was just that there was a violent earthquake that caused a large number of buildings to collapse, as well as sinking the surrounding terrain by one or two meters. The city shrouded in the shield suddenly became an island.

Seeing this, Han Xiao had an idea and piloted his Lord's Avatar down to the settlement.

Everyone had gone over to chase and kill the virus core, and the battle had happened straight after. While they all noticed the Machinery Faith on Planet Magnetic Cloud, there was no time to contact it. Now was the best time.

Manison had warned them before that he did not wish to see any other Beyond Grade As contact the Machinery Faith, but now that he had completely disregarded Manison, Han Xiao naturally did not care about his warnings.

Han Xiao slowly descended, stopping in the air directly outside the protective shield.

The other Beyond Grade A Mechanics also swiftly approached.

Han Xiao did not restrict them; he was no Mechanic Emperor.

After a few seconds, the shield opened automatically, and Han Xiao and his group landed on top of the temple in the middle of the settlement. All the priests formed a circle around them in excitement.

"Look, it's a Mechanical Deity, in the flesh!"

"So many Beyond Grade A Mechanics. I really want to touch them."

"Do you think that they will allow us to take photos with them?"

Many of the priests whispered among themselves in fanaticism.

This should be heaven!

On an ordinary day, it was only the Mechanic Emperor that would contact them, and none of the other Beyond Grade As would come over, as though they had no interest in the Machinery Faith, making them feel as though these Beyond Grade As looked down on them.

The priests normally did not take the initiative to come into contact with the objects of their faith, and each individual would have their own idol of worship, so the interaction was limited. Getting to see so many living Beyond Grade A Mechanics in person made everyone happy, excited, and cautious. They wished to jump upon them but were also afraid of making their 'gods' unhappy.

In the end, it was the Grand Priest that took the initiative to greet everyone.

"I'm the Grand Priest of this Machinery Faith colony. Beyond Grade A Mechanics, I welcome you on behalf of the Machinery Faith."

Han Xiao knew how to interact with them, choosing not to say anything about the scene nor give any self-introductions. He directly glanced at the collapsed buildings in the distance, asking in a tone like a commander asking over their subordinates.

"I fought a really fierce battle with the Mechanic Emperor just now. Are you guys still alright?"

"We're fine. We all have heavy armor as protection, and the residents have already taken refuge in the flying vehicles. There were no casualties, so the loss of the city is nothing since we can always rebuild it."

Seeing Black Star's concerned attitude gave the Grand Priest a great boost to his spirits. His expression was one of joy.

My idol is concerned for us!

I have no more regrets in this life!

"It would be better for you all to shift to another planet. The damage done to Planet Magnetic Cloud is quite serious, and there might be natural disasters in the future," Han Xiao said with concern.

The Grand Priest vehemently shook his head. "No, no, no, we're going to stay here and pay tribute to the traces of battle that you and the Mechanic Emperor have left."

With Planet Magnetic Cloud already beaten to this state, a normal person would choose to move to another planet, but those of the Machinery Faith were not ordinary. They believed that having witnessed a fight between Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor, Planet Magnetic Cloud had become some sort of 'Divine Battlefield', which possessed a lot of commemorative meaning. They could not wait to pray to it every day.

What, moving? Out of the question!

"In this case, that's fine too. Since I'm already here, let me help you guys." Han Xiao pointed at the air, and a virtual screen unfolded, showing a 2D map of Planet Magnetic Cloud. He said in a kind tone, "I'm to blame for your residence being destroyed, so choose a location. I'll help you guys to build a new city there."

Many of the priests immediately opened their eyes wide, not daring to believe that such a superior being was actually so benevolent.

"We don't dare. How could we trouble someone like you to do such a small thing?" The Grand Priest hurriedly declined the offer.

"Don't be so polite. We're considered a family. I've always known of the existence of the Machinery Faith and heard that you guys worshipped me as a god. While you have never contacted me before, you respect me as a god, so I shall not be stingy with succor."

Han Xiao did not beat around the bush, directly using the 'I'm a reliable backer, so just lie on my huge and assuring chest' logic.

Hearing that, the Grand Priest could not help but feel a little moved. Their beliefs would not be transferred because of material interests, but they also did not find it necessary to reject their god's divine bestowal.

Everyone discussed it a bit before choosing a location for their new settlement.

Glancing at it, Han Xiao discovered that it was the rift created by the trident. He was not surprised and deliberately smiled. "Very good, this area was the spot that the Mechanic Emperor's weapon landed after being deflected by me."

Hearing this, the priests present all had their curiosity dug out.

They had been watching the battle between the two Mechanical Deities and discovered that they had stopped fighting halfway. Later, they heard Kant speak on the wide area channel, saying that both of them were tied. Manison left soon after, and because everything had happened so quickly, the priests were still in a state of confusion.

"Your Excellency, why did you and His Excellency Mechanic Emperor start fighting? What happened in the end? Er… if this is sensitive, then I apologize for my offense."

The Grand Priest could not help himself from inquiring about it. While he knew it was somewhat abrupt, he felt the itchy to sate his curiosity.

"It's no secret and will be made public sooner or later anyway. There's no harm in telling you guys. You've heard of the Virtual Mutiny Virus, right?"

"Yes, yes."

All of them nodded like chickens pecking.

"That plaything isn't any ordinary virus but rather an information systems weapon with a core controller. It has the ability to continuously evolve and upgrade itself, and it can even phase in and out between the virtual and physical world. Us Beyond Grade A Mechanics responded to the call of the three Universal Civilizations to cooperate and kill it," Han Xiao briefly explained.

The eyes of the priests were open wide in shock. Only at this time did they realize that the Virtual Mutiny Virus that plagued the Ancient Star Desert for many days was actually such powerful technology.

The Grand Priest was immersed in Han Xiao's narration, hurriedly asking, "Did you succeed?"

"We caught the virus core, but we had a conflict in handling the issue. Manison, regardless of the risk, wished to keep the core and research the technology behind it on his own. For the sake of universal peace, I took the virus core and destroyed it, angering the Mechanic Emperor. He wanted to teach me a lesson, so we had a fight. I'm embarrassed to have affected you."

Han Xiao was speaking the truth, but he slightly changed the details to highlight Manison's 'disregard for the safety of the universe'.

Kant and the others glanced at him, knowing that this was him trying to discredit the Mechanic Emperor, but no one stopped it as they were happy to see it happen.

"Then the result…"

"Just as you heard, it ended in a tie. Both the Mechanic Emperor and I do not know of the outcome, and he felt that if he continued to fight, he likely would not be able to beat me, so he ran away and did not continue fighting with me."

Kant and the others once again glanced at Han Xiao before nodding along.

Not bad, keep this up. Continue to smear his name. Don't stop.

"No wonder…" The Grand Priest sighed contentedly, like a reporter who had gotten his scoop.

From the start, Black Star was suppressed by the Mechanic Emperor, and the situation was only reversed after he burned his potential. However, the Machinery Faith only recognized the result. Regardless of whether Black Star had burned his potential or not, as long as his Mechanic abilities produced the desired result against his enemy, they would recognize that Black Star and Mechanic Emperor had tied. They placed the two on the same level now and could not wait to advertise it in their sect and share the gossip.

At the same time, the Grand Priest felt a little regretful.

While he did not belong to the zealot faction, it hurt to hear that such powerful technology like the Virtual Mutiny Virus had been destroyed by Han Xiao.

However, he admired this feat even more. Black Star clearly had the core of the virus at his fingertips, but he cared for the common people and eliminated any opportunity for any organization to obtain this technology from the roots itself for the sake of the universe. This was an admirable act.

As for the Mechanic Emperor, he wished to study this virus in order to master the weapon. The safety of the ordinary citizens was not within his consideration. While the Grand Priest could understand the Mechanic Emperor's approach, he felt that his bearings were inferior compared to Black Star. Subconsciously, the image of the Mechanic Emperor was no longer so tall and mysterious, and the image of Black Star grew much more.

Rumors could always be distorted, and it was more likely that the information revealed by these bigshots would be more reliable… Many of the priests thought that way.

Han Xiao and his party thus promoted his battle record of achieving a tie and, in the process, discredited the Mechanic Emperor, allowing this group of Machinery Faith members to vigorously publicize it in their internal networks, reducing Manison's believers.

The Machinery Faith only believed in the strong, and they did not have any diehard fans. With a record as evidence, it was not difficult to poach people.

To achieve their goal, Han Xiao and the rest had a conversation with the believers, deepening their impression of them in the Machinery Faith. They then left the planet, dispelling their Lord's Descent and only leaving the construction machinery to build the new settlement for the Machinery Faith.

…

"The Mechanic Emperor has withdrawn."

The three Universal Civilizations' leaders looked at each other the moment the live broadcast screen ended.

"While there were some twists and turns, the operation was largely successful, and the threat of the virus core has also been resolved. Black Star's intelligence was correct, and he also went to great lengths for the operation to succeed. If it were not for him, we would definitely have suffered a huge loss. This achievement could be said to have turned tide, and he should be rewarded," Urranrell said.

Bader and the Pope nodded in agreement. This was a disaster that threatened the whole universe, so they let go of past grievances for the time being and reward those who had contributed.

"Furthermore, in order to destroy the Mechanic Emperor's plan, Black Star had to burn his potential and fight. We should compensate him," Urranrell said again.

Bader secretly screamed out the word 'shameless', and he retorted, "This isn't too justified. Handing over the virus core to us would also have ruined the Mechanic Emperor's scheme, but Black Star did not do this. Perhaps it is out of his consideration to maintain the order of the universe, but it could also be his distrust in us. We are not of the same mind. So, the reward is justified, but the compensation isn't."

"We can't end it like that." Urranrell shook her head. "Black Star ruined the virus core based on his own considerations. This might be a case of a wise man looking after his own hide, but he indeed cut off the source of the disaster. Through this behavior, we can finally catch a glimpse of his vague position… that he chooses order above everything else. While Black Star might not be one of our direct members, but based on his position, he is consistent with our interests and should be awarded more trust."

Bader frowned without replying.

Seeing this, Urranrell solemnly continued. "In fact, we have not lost this technology even with the destruction. The monopoly of the virus technology was just to prevent leakage. With our own strengths, we can already naturally suppress the explored universe, and without this technology, we're still the overlords, but there will be one less variable that can threaten the entire universe."

She made no attempt to hide the fact that she wished for Black Star to obtain more benefits. Bader looked as though he wanted to speak, but the Pope suddenly spoke.

"We need to consider how to deal with the Mechanic Emperor. His current position is extremely dangerous to us, and if Black Star had not revealed the specialty of the virus' core, he would have hidden it in his intelligence.

"Manison's appetite is growing larger. While he did not succeed this time, he has already revealed his ambition. We cannot tolerate him doing whatever he wants, so we have to find ways to weaken him, such as his businesses, status, his believers in the Machinery Faith, and his speaking rights in the development union. We have to choose a candidate to go against him, repeatedly stealing his resources."

"And the person you're suggesting is Black Star, huh?" Bader was a little unwilling.

"That's right. He's the best candidate. While he is not of our direct line, his position is worthy of our trust as he will not do anything to disrupt order. It's better to make Black Star bigger than the Mechanic Emperor, who is unscrupulous. It would be best for Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor to compete, causing a division. If Black Star can lead the Development union, that would be even better. We will not have to worry about those Beyond Grade A people creating any sort of radical collective behavior."

After they exchanged their opinions, a consensus was reached.

For Black Star, not only did they have to reward him, they also had to vigorously promote his deeds throughout the universe. This would build an image for him to compete against the resources of the Mechanic Emperor, as well as to promote the correct values that were conducive to their order.

As for the Mechanic Emperor, they had to suppress him hard, no longer allowing him to be so unrestrained.

Apart from other things, they had to first lock down that old thing's main body. Manison was no Black Star, so his true body was his fatal weakness.

…

His vision shifted from his Lord's Avatar and returned to his main body.

Han Xiao slowly opened his eyes. He was still within the virtual brainwave amplifier, and the consciousness of the others did not return to their avatars there. He was the only one in this space.

"I finally solved the virus core problem."

Han Xiao opened the interface, and the special requirements that required him to destroy the virus core by hand showed a completed sign.

However, the entire [Intelligent Plague] mission was not over yet. All rewards for this mission would not be handed out until the three Universal Civilizations had eliminated all the first-generation viruses within the Ancient Star Desert.

As for the [Mechanic Emperor Manison - Machinery War] mission, that could be turned in. He and Manison had fought for half a day, allowing him to reach the highest evaluation.

Since Feidin, Nero, and Ames were not around, he could only look for Harrison.

After taking a trip out to meet Harrison and giving him a good rub under the other party's confused and terrified gaze, Han Xiao clicked on the reward settlement with a satisfied look. He glanced past the experience and Character Summon Card rewards, looking directly at the skill extraction interface.

You have received: Draw one of Manison's ability (talent/skill)

Tip: Manison is a Virtual Mechanic, and your Class is completely compatible with his. You will be able to draw any of his abilities. If you draw an ability that you have, you can strengthen your ability to a certain extent.

Randomizing… complete.

Please select one from the five options below as the reward:

Blueprint—Emperor Mechanic's Sacred Trident - Skill: A Universal Treasure Class melee weapon dedicated for the Mechanical Deity's usage. Manison has combined a lot of weapon technology to develop this fine piece of work. The specific parameters are as follows… (Expand/Collapse). Minimum Manufacturing Requirements: Character Level 310, 20,000 INT, [Ultimate Mechanical Engineering Lv.5], [Endless Material Science Lv.5], [Eternal Power Source Lv.4]…

Perfect Mechanical Sense - Talent: x1.4 bonus coefficient to Machinery Affinity. Grade of Mechanic equipment that receive Mechanical Force bonuses are temporarily increased by 1 – 2 tiers (highest quality will not exceed Pink Grade), +4 to all Mechanic Skills.

Blueprint—Punisher - Skill: Manison's self-developed advanced mechanical soldiers, powerful war weapons made possible through Biological Transformation and Biochemical Machinery. A living Super is needed as raw material, and the stronger the Super, the higher the performance will be after transformation. The specific parameters are as follows… (Expand/Collapse).

Note: To transform a Beyond Grade A living Super into a Punisher, the minimum requirements are: Character Level 340, 32,000 INT, and possess [Endless Material Science Lv5], [Mechanical Life Tinder Lv5], [Eternal Power Source Lv5], [Virtual Creator Lv5]…

The Ancient Ones - Talent: A long life gives you a wealth of experience, which is precious spiritual wealth. +20% INT, +10% MYS, +2 to all Skill levels.

100 Million Mechanic Empire—Manison - Talent: +15% INT, +1.2x Machinery Affinity Coefficient, +2 to all Mechanic Class Skills. In addition, +6 to [Machinery Fusion], [Emperor's Gift], [King's Mentor], [Tinder Awakening], [Apostle Life Creation], [Dimension Factory], [Apostle Evolution], [Mechanical Proliferation Growth], [Strengthened Machinery Civilization]… +5,000% for machinery production efficiency and +10% – 40% for the quality of mechanic artifacts produced. Furthermore, +36% in abilities relating to the research and manufacturing of ordinary blueprints, and +12% in abilities relating to the research and manufacturing for Golden blueprints.

When battling against any other machinery, you will obtain a bonus of +10% to all Attributes, -15% to damage received, and +10% to damage dealt to the other party. Your energy and stamina consumption are also reduced by 25%.

Remarks: You're the owner of hundreds of millions of machines. You are the Mechanic Emperor!

Gulp. Han Xiao was a little dazed, swallowing unconsciously. Is the Goddess of Luck finally willing to hold onto my pants…

Chapter 1120: Snatching Manison's Treasure

The quality of this wave of extraction was just too scary!

Han Xiao was unprepared for this and was stunned for a while before ecstasy surged in his heart.

Because both of their classes were perfectly matched, any skill or expertise could be drawn, so the thousands of blueprints Manison had would lower the possibility of him drawing anything good.

Han Xiao's original goal was to at best extract a Molding Talent, but he did not expect to draw out Manison's treasured baby!

[100 Million Mechanic Empire—Manison], a Unique Talent!

Just look at the effect! Woah, the difference in template level! And it's even top notch among the templates!

This was definitely the reason behind Manison's strength!

The Unique Talents of most characters stemmed from their own experience, which also carried a strong personal touch.

Generally speaking, the talent formed after becoming strong would definitely be more powerful compared to the earlier ones, and the [100 Million Mechanic Empire] was obviously the specialty borne after Manison had been famous for a long time. Its conditions for forming were extremely harsh, and it was the summation of his lifetime of experience.

To put it in layman's terms, this talent was equivalent to the old man's 'inner core'. It contained the essence of his life!

And right now, the old man's lifetime of work was unfortunately extracted by him…

It was as though one had gone down to the river to fish, and immediately caught a protected animal in one go!

The richness of this harvest completely outstripped our Great Mechanic Han's expectation, and he was so excited that he wanted to gorge on his nutrition fluid as a reward.

I f*cking earned big this time!

One's character indeed needs to be accumulated. Harrison has stored so many years of luck with him, and I probably wiped it all clean in one go.

Han Xiao was full of excitement.

Forgetting the [100 Million Mechanic Empire], the overall quality of this extraction was also surprisingly high, with two Molding Talent level abilities and even [Perfect Mechanical Sense].

Fortunately, he had long obtained the [Perfect Mechanical Sense] template by bullying Nero, and even if he chose it again, he would only obtain a minor upgrade to the skill. The price to performance ratio was too limited, otherwise he would have had trouble deciding.

The other options were also quite good. The Emperor Mechanic's Sacred Trident was the weapon that Manison had used in the battle against him, which was a Universal Treasure stronger than the Celestial Punishment Edge. The blueprint [Punisher] was a special living weapon modification technology that was even applicable to the Beyond Grade A levels. Most likely, all the Beyond Grade As 'collected' by Manison were transformed into advanced weaponry in this manner.

[The Ancient Ones] was also a high-level talent, which Han Xiao had used before through the Character Summon Card. If he did not draw the [100 Million Mechanic Empire] talent, then this ability would have been good to solidify himself.

Since the other abilities paled in comparison in front of Manison's Unique Talent, Han Xiao did not need to hesitate.

Tonight, we are all Manison!

You have received a new talent: 100 Million Mechanic Empire—Manison!

An unexplainable change occurred in his body, different from the pain experienced during the sublimation of life level. Han Xiao only felt as though he was flying, the unknown shackles binding him having been broken off.

His vision rippled, and scenes flashed quickly in front of him.

He saw the fast-forwarded process from a baby's birth to when he became a teenager. Obscure books on machinery theory were being read as children's books, casually flipped through.

He saw the first Mechanical Force of the boy being born, the first book he read, the first machine made, the first blueprint refined, the first enemy killed…

As the stars shifted, countless messy and fuzzy pictures flashed by, and the person in the illusion finally turned into an old man dressed in a silver robe, with his eyes flickering with lightning. Behind him stood a mighty mechanical army, boundless and as numerous as the stars in the galaxy, occupying every inch of Han Xiao's sight.

The illusion ended there, and Han Xiao opened his eyes in revelation.

This must be Old Man Manison's life story. It seems as though obtaining the Unique Talent of a person will allow me to see the general outline of said person's life… But hey, that old bugger is still alive, so why does it seem like they're celebrating his life?

The illusion was fuzzy most of the time and lacked detail. It only showcased the more important nodes of Manison's life.

Han Xiao did not receive any intelligence despite viewing the whole thing, at most only having a better outlook over Manison's life.

He was a proud son of heaven, talented in many ways, and had always been the outstanding one from a young age.

The stereotypical child-next-door. Han Xiao grimaced.

The only special thing worth noting was that despite Manison being so dazzling since childhood, he seemed to have no interest in material enjoyment, nor did he have any interest in passing down his genes. All he wanted was to stay in his workshop and tinker with machinery.

This is a little similar to me. We're all craftsmen that are focused on our own crafts…

Han Xiao shook his head, putting this illusion to the back of his mind before carefully scrutinizing the effects of [100 Million Mechanic Empire—Manison]. While the talent was now his, the suffix of 'Manison' had not disappeared. This would always display the origin of the skill.

One of the most exaggerated bonuses within would be the 5,000% increase in production efficiency. Most likely, the nickname of Mechanic Emperor for Manison was derived because of this, as his speed of creating machinery was frightening.

While this was awe inspiring, fifty times the production efficiency also meant fifty times the speed of money burnt!

Manison had been continuously expanding his organization all the while. Other than ambition, it was because he needed to support his own expenses. With the expenses he incurred in his own class, he spent the money he earned fast.

The biggest difference between me and Manison now is our accumulation. With this bonus, the speed at which I accumulate my foundation will increase sharply. While it will not shorten the gap, it will not allow Manison to open up the gap between us even more… Han Xiao stroked his chin as he thought. It's just that my money will be spent too quickly… Luckily, I'm not short on cash.

The Black Star Army was at a huge scale now, with huge cash flows and terrifying profits daily. Furthermore, there was the cornucopia in the form of the Evolution Totems. His own personal finances were now full enough to have permanently crossed out the term 'lack of money' from his dictionary.

The bonus awarded to his blueprint manufacturing and R&D was also large, which could be around the range of dozens of stacks from the [Spirit Instrument] buff. The best would be the twelve percent bonus to Gold Grade blueprints. Manison's specialty was the research and development of various Universal Treasures, and this should be affected by his expertise.

This will make things easier when I study Universal Treasures myself in the future. Han Xiao was overjoyed.

As for the buffs that would take effect when facing off against other machinery, this was the best when having a battle against other Mechanics. This was one of the reasons Manison was so powerful when facing other Mechanics.

The next time he faced off against Manison, he would also obtain the same targeted increase.

The bonus given to me by the [100 Million Mechanic Empire] is equivalent to two [Perfect Mechanical Sense] talents stacked together. The Unique Talents of the best are actually so terrifying…

Han Xiao was satisfied as though he had managed to eat a full meal. The gap between him and the Mechanic Emperor was already greatly reduced now.

What I said earlier still stands. Manison is indeed a good person.

Every time I argue and fight with him, I obtain such a huge gift. What sort of attitude is this? Returning grievances with virtue!

If it were not for his fear of angering the other party, he would send a pennant over to Manison, with the words "The Timely Assistance for Galaxy, Hero Manison!"

It seems like I need to fight more with Manison. My ability to obtain a fortune depends on him now.

Han Xiao secretly clenched his fists.

Closing the skill interface, he looked at the other mission rewards.

Directly challenging Manison was an extremely difficult mission, and the experience awarded was even greater than the first time, giving him close to a hundred billion. His stock, which was basically used up to exchange for Awakening Points, was now filled up again.

As for the Character Summon Card awarded, it was an ability known as [Vigor Resonance]. The effect reduced energy consumption as well as strengthened his attributes. When converted to Mechanical Force, it increased the coverage of Mechanical Force bonuses given. At the same time, as long as his energy value did not reach zero, his energy bonuses would always remain at the maximum.

Perhaps due to him using up all his luck, the effect of the Character Summon Card was quite ordinary. With his own HP to Energy exchange, this Character Summon Card was quite useless to him.

However, Han Xiao was not discouraged. With Manison's core talent in his hands, he was already very satisfied.

After doing some statistics, Han Xiao closed the interface, thinking about the impact of his actions.

I've changed the trend of the plotline, as the virus core was directly eliminated by me. The Intelligent Plague will no longer sweep through the universe like in my previous life, and the losses have been reduced by more than ninety-five percent. The explored universe has survived this disaster without any risk, and more people have been saved in this life.

With the work I've done, I should obtain the highest Mission Rating this time. Other than the mission reward, the three Universal Civilizations will also give me a second wave of remuneration. When the news is released, I can once again obtain a third wave of rewards from the feedback given by the galactic society.

It's a pity that this Domino Virus cannot be used to deal with the World Tree. However, since the virus was not used in my previous life, the impact should not be too huge. Actually, if the World Tree managed to crack this technology and turn it against us, that would be bad. The negative impact of this virus on us is far greater than that of the World Tree, so eliminating this variable might not be a bad thing.

The possibility of the Mechanic Emperor retaliating against me is low, since he'll have to deal with the suppression from the three Universal Civilizations. Even if he really wishes to mess with me, I'm now full of abilities and will not be too afraid of him.

Since we've made our contradictions clear, the Mechanic Emperor and I will definitely fight in the development union. The Beyond Grade A Mechanics are not on the side of the Mechanic Emperor, so they are equivalent to my hidden supporters. My speaking rights in the union should increase.

Han Xiao calculated the pros and cons silently, discovering that his gains this time were huge, with the only disadvantage being that he had offended Manison.

In the past, it was likely that Manison had obtained the virus core, becoming the greatest beneficiary of the Intelligent Plague.

Now, it was the other way around. In this operation, the Old Man Manison became the only one that lost out.

It seems like I did him a good number this time… Han Xiao scratched his head. Bah, what does it have to do with me? It's not that I'm bad; you're just too sly.

Chapter 1121: Special Consultant

Han Xiao left the virtual brainwave amplifier, returning to the command center. As the spaceship landed and Han Xiao stepped out from the hatch, he immediately saw Sidreun and the other inspectors waiting for him on the platform.

Sidreun took two steps forward before bowing slightly. His attitude showed a lot more reverence than before.

"Your Excellency Black Star, the three heads are waiting online for you."

Han Xiao's actions in destroying the virus core had won him over.

"Alright, I'll head over now." Han Xiao smiled as he nodded. He was not surprised and had long expected the three Universal Civilizations to approach him.

He swept the area with a glance, realizing that the other Beyond Grade A avatars were not present.

"The others?"

"They have yet to descend at the moment, but all their missions have been completed, so we are enough to wrap up the backend."

With the virus core eradicated, the Virtual Mutiny Virus was thus stopped at the first generation. With the three sets of antivirus kits, the three Universal Civilizations' original plan to cleanse the virus could now continue. Since the next step did not require the Beyond Grade As, their missions could be said to have been completed.

The Mechanic Emperor was even more unlikely to come back, or else it would be awkward if they saw each other, not knowing if they should fight.

Han Xiao followed the trio to a remote conference room on the top floor of the headquarters. Walking into the room, he glanced to see three huge virtual screens standing in front of them. They were the remote projections of Urranrell, Bader, and the Pope.

Sidreun and the others nodded to show their respect before retreating and closing the door. Only Han Xiao was left in the room.

Urranrell was the first to speak.

"Black Star, you've achieved a great merit this time, pinpointing the real danger of the Intelligent Plague for us. Without your intel, countless people would have been killed and injured in this disaster. We're grateful for you for your contribution on behalf of the universe."

"Maintaining the order of society is everyone's responsibility," Han Xiao replied perfunctorily as he looked at the three of them.

This was still the first time he had spoken to all three heads of the Universal Civilizations. He had practically reached the very forefront of Galaxy, as few had such an honor in the universe, with those receiving this treatment being the most dazzling great people of each age.

Speaking of which, he was only familiar with Urranrell and had not had much contact with either Bader or the Pope.

The three of them took turns to speak, praising Han Xiao for his contribution but did not say much about his act of destroying the virus core.

After listening to their praise, Han Xiao then finally heard the Pope move onto the main topic.

"For such an achievement, we will definitely not be stingy with the reward…"

Han Xiao secretly rolled his eyes. He knew that the three leaders had definitely reached a consensus before speaking to him.

Not out of his expectations, the three of them coincided with each other, introducing the reward. Among them, resources and policy support counted for the majority. The federation and the church expressed their willingness to help the Black Star Army in the Star Fields outside the Shattered Star Ring and the Flickering World, allowing them to expand their businesses and sphere of influence.

The development of the Black Star Army in the other Star Fields had been relatively difficult, as their hands could not stretch too far at the moment. With the joint support of the three Universal Civilizations, the development would be much smoother.

Han Xiao understood the meaning behind this—it was to allow him to catch up with the Mechanic Emperor's organizations, allowing the two of them to better compete with each other. At the same time, this support would mean that the three Universal Civilizations were sharing their own interests with him, so as to deepen their relationship and avoid any conflict with him like what happened between them and Manison.

Furthermore, the three Universal Civilizations promised to open a portion of the Universal Treasure blueprint library to Han Xiao, which would allow him to purchase a portion of the Gold Grade blueprints using money and his Contribution Points.

Originally, most of these blueprints were not for sale. However, during his conflict against the Mechanic Emperor, the three Universal Civilizations saw the gap in strength between the two parties, so they were willing to provide some benefits to aid Black Star in reducing the gap. Generally speaking, such privileges were only awarded to those of their direct line. These treatments could be regarded as a manifestation of their trust in Han Xiao.

Of course, support still had its limits, and they would not give everything away for free.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled, and he was unexpectedly surprised.

If this was the case, other than his own research and Awakening Point methods, he now had a new channel to purchase Universal Treasures. Because of his [Spirit Instrument] skills, there were additional benefits to this reward for him, and in his opinion, this was better compared to those business support they would provide him.

At this moment, Urranrell slowly said, "We've also jointly decided to hire you as a Special Safety Consultant for the Federation of Light, the Crimson Dynasty, and the Arcane Church."

Han Xiao was stunned.

A Special Safety Consultant for the three Universal Civilizations‽

This was new to him.

If that was the case, then he would also form a relationship with both the federation and the church, turning from an ally of the dynasty into a cross-faction character.

It seemed like there was no Beyond Grade A who had been given such an honor before in history. He might be the first and likely only one.

After thinking about it, Han Xiao could guess the intentions of the three Universal Civilizations.

Firstly, they wanted to build his momentum, and the second reason was that the other two wished to earn money through investing in him just like advertising sponsors. Black Star would carry a part of their labels with him. The third intention would be for the development union, which would mean that the three Universal Civilizations were currently adjusting their attitudes toward the Beyond Grade A development union.

Why does this feel like in the martial arts novels that I read in my previous life, about how the court would secretly support one of their own in order to become the Master of the Martial Community, thus allowing them to control the pugilists? I'm becoming more and more like a villain, Han Xiao grumbled in his heart.

While he thought this way, he did not refuse the position of the Special Safety Consultant and politely nodded.

"I'm honored to be offered this position."

For the Mechanic Emperor to engage in rebellion, it was not just because of the methods employed against them but also contained his own selfish will. Han Xiao did not have that idea; for him, there was more than one way to protect the Beyond Grade As. In his opinion, no one could truly be alone in the universe. The right way was to seek cooperation amid their struggles.

Furthermore, the three Universal Civilizations would be the main force in dealing with the World Tree Civilization. What he wanted was to make their cooperative relationship equal, not to backstab the three Universal Civilizations.

The majority of people in the Beyond Grade A Association also thought the same way. His position as a Special Security Consultant for the three Universal Civilizations would now act as a halo, which could attract members with the same idea. This would further separate him from Manison.

Thinking of this, Han Xiao once again had a fresh perspective.

Why does it feel like we're Professor X and Magneto?

While he had become a Special Consultant, his roots were still as a pillar of the dynasty, and his relationship with the other two civilizations was a lot more superficial.

"These are the general rewards. Black Star, do you have any specific needs?"

Han Xiao thought for a while before saying, "I hope that I can purchase the Ultimate Knowledges of other systems and be able to pass it on to others."

The moment he spoke, the eyes of the trio changed, and silence fell.

This was a sensitive issue and one that the Development Union had been negotiating with the three Universal Civilizations.

The issue of lifting the monopoly on Knowledge.

There were so many Beyond Grade As, and if they gathered together, they would definitely be able to gather all the Ultimate Knowledges of every Class. The key lay in their right to disseminate the knowledge, as the three Universal Civilizations prohibited any sort of private teaching.

Now, Han Xiao wished for them to release their grips on this issue, which was in line with the requests of the Beyond Grade As. However, it would harm the interest of the three Universal Civilizations.

Seeing their expressions, Han Xiao said, "Hila is still serving as my Deputy Army Commander. I have to help her gather knowledge of her Esper System, and there are also people with extraordinary potential under me that I hope can master some Ultimate Knowledge to improve their combat power."

The three of them exchanged glances, and after being silent for a long time, Urranrell finally spoke.

"You may exchange three Ultimate Knowledges for Hila, but you are only limited to passing one Ultimate Knowledge per person for others. At the same time, you have to submit a list for filing and limit the number of people who are able to learn this."

The three Universal Civilizations finally made some concessions on this issue, but this was only limited to Black Star himself, while others did not have this treatment.

After the various deals were negotiated, the three Universal Civilizations' leaders went offline, and Han Xiao left the meeting room, stopping by to greet Sidreun before returning to his territory.

Just as he walked into his exclusive office area, he saw Harrison nervously standing at the door, waiting for him.

Han Xiao did not stop, however, instead walking on.

Harrison immediately rushed up, stammering, "Your… Your Excellency Black Star, I have something to ask…"

"Speak."

"I would like to ask, what are we going to do after the Intelligent Plague is over?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao turned to glance at him, only to see Harrison's expression of anxiety. He immediately knew what was on the latter's mind.

"What, are you afraid you'll go back behind bars?"

"Yes, that's right." Harrison appeared a little frazzled. While he had followed Han Xiao for a few months, he was still guilty. This charge had not been lifted, so he was afraid he would have to continue sitting behind bars and had come to ask Han Xiao for help.

"Relax, you've made a great contribution this time, and I won't leave you in the lurch." Han Xiao patted his shoulder.

Harrison was flattered, but at the same time, he was a little dazed.

I made a great contribution?

Why didn't I hear anything about it?

"Then… what will happen to me in the future?"

"I will ask the three Universal Civilizations to withdraw the charges against you and restore the freedom of you and your companions, but you can no longer be scavengers."

"Thank you very much!" Harrison had an expression of gratitude.

It was nice to regain his freedom. It did not matter if he could not be a scavenger. After unearthing the Virtual Mutiny Virus, Harrison was already traumatized and planned to go back and inherit his family fortune.

"Don't rejoice too early. I'm not saving you for nothing. You'll need to continue your current job scope and do exploration under the funding and surveillance of the Black Star Army."

"This…" Harrison hesitated.

"Not willing?" Han Xiao stared at him. "Then I hope you'll get used to your prison life as soon as possible."

"No, no, no!" Harrison immediately grabbed Han Xiao and helplessly replied, "We can do it."

Black Star was their last hope, so he had no other choice. Besides, obtaining financial aid from a behemoth such as the Black Star Army would mean that they did not have to worry about everything like before.

Han Xiao hummed in agreement, but he was smiling in his heart.

Want to go back and inherit the family business? Dream on!

Once you enter my leek field, don't even think of running away. Just work hard for me!

Chapter 1122: Changes and Announcements

After the three Universal Civilizations completed the operation, they notified the various organizations in the Ancient Star Desert to reopen their quantum networks. The quantum network was only disconnected for half a day, yet it brought about huge economic losses to the entire Star Field. The various organizations were all wondering what the three Universal Civilizations had done during the period when their quantum network was disconnected.

Through intelligence gathered from all walks of life, they quickly found out that a group of Beyond Grade As had gathered for an operation, and they all were dumbfounded.

The Super Star Cluster Civilizations were all suffering from PTSD from the three Universal Civilizations, and thus, they were always on the lookout about this turmoil. Upon learning of this matter, the upper echelons held another meeting.

"It turns out that the Virtual Mutiny Virus had such a mechanism. If it was leaked out, it's unknown how many people would have been killed or injured… It's a pity that we were kept in the dark, and the core has now been destroyed by Black Star."

Many of the upper echelons displayed fear and regret.

They were afraid of the threat of the Virtual Mutiny Virus itself. They thought that the three Universal Civilizations had controlled the situation, but they did not expect it to be just an illusion. If they did not manage to find the virus core, then disaster would have swept across the entire universe.

What they regretted was that they did not know the goals of the three Universal Civilizations in advance, and in order to cooperate, they developed a wait-and-see attitude, finally resulting in the virus core being handled by the three Universal Civilizations. The Virtual Mutiny Virus thus became a disappearing voice.

Because the ship had already sailed, the three Universal Civilizations no longer concealed the information, so the Super Star Cluster Alliance discovered this matter.

One of the executives sighed in relief. "Luckily, Black Star destroyed the virus core. If we'd let the three Universal Civilizations obtain such weaponized information technology, then our situation would have been much worse."

"You're wrong. Black Star destroying the virus core does us more harm than good. Even if the technology was obtained by the three Universal Civilizations, they would only use it in order to maintain order. But for us, this sort of technology would be enough to allow us to threaten them, and it would allow us to shorten the gap between us and them. Now that this technology has disappeared, we have lost this opportunity forever," someone retorted.

"It would have been good if the Mechanic Emperor had succeeded…"

Many of them sighed.

They had hoped that Manison would succeed, as there was a high chance the Mechanic Emperor would ally with their Super Star Cluster Alliance in order to maintain his competitive advantage in hoarding profitable goods. In this manner, they would also have had an opportunity to find ways to obtain the virus technology through him.

However, this hope of turning the tables was now destroyed by Black Star, and they could not help but greatly regret it.

"Black Star, this fellow, really…" One of the superiors paused, not knowing how to describe Han Xiao, before finally speaking dejectedly. "He's too wasteful."

Glancing at the other upper echelons with varied expressions, the Star Arc Civilization's leaders solemnly said, "The results cannot be changed. What we need to think about is how to deal with the current situation."

"In the Flickering World, the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance will definitely have a battle. What we lack now is preparation time. Originally, the Intelligent Plague would have taken up all the energy of the three Universal Civilizations. The longer they are held up, the better. But now that the disaster is about to disappear, the three Universal Civilizations will soon be free to deal with us."

"The virus core was discovered by Black Star, and it was also eliminated by him. Because of his actions, the time for the three Universal Civilizations to solve the Intelligent Plague was greatly reduced… Hey, it's Black Star again!"

Most of the upper echelons were very dissatisfied. The exposure of Traveler before was due to Black Star, and now he had once again disrupted their plans.

But while they were angry, they could not do anything. They hoped to be low-key at this point to avoid trouble, so why would they go and provoke Black Star?

The leader of the Star Arc Civilization looked through the intelligence and suddenly exclaimed, "Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor had a disagreement on the issue of dealing with the virus core. The two of them had a fight and officially turned against each other. What do you think about this?"

"The battle report shows that Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor reached a tie…" An intelligence department's chief frowned. "If Black Star arrived in his main body, it is still possible, but both sides were using avatars. Our artificial intelligence has constructed countless models and analyzed the results, showing that in the case of this battle, Black Star's win rate was as low as 0.0027%. He is not yet an opponent of the Mechanic Emperor. The tie was because the other Beyond Grade As forcibly interfered, which meant that they were instructed to do so. Thus, we can judge that the three Universal Civilizations hope to create an equivalent character to compete against the Mechanic Emperor."

The leader of the Star Arc Civilization narrowed his eyes. "This means that after this battle, Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor will part ways, and the Beyond Grade As will be divided into two factions. One faction will support Black Star, and the other, the Mechanic Emperor. There might be an opportunity in this…"

"You mean…"

"After operating his business for so many years, the Mechanic Emperor is already considered a semi-independent state, almost rid of the three Universal Civilizations control," the leader of the Star Arc Civilization said. "However, against the three Universal Civilizations, he will still require some external help, and that help… can be offered by us."

Everyone's eyes lit up, and they nodded.

Everyone would have a time when they sorely needed help. The Mechanic Emperor was such a powerful figure, so if the Super Star Cluster Alliance helped him right now when he was in a difficult position and not trusted by the three Universal Civilizations, they might have a chance to become his secret partner.

In this way, to a certain extent, they can prevent the Beyond Grade A union from reaching a new cooperative relationship with the three Universal Civilizations, and they would also add obstacles to Black Star, who often caused them trouble.

On a desolate planet in the Primeval Star River, there was a hidden base underground.

Electricity arced in the darkness, and a pair of eyes emitting sparks opened, reflecting a silhouette sitting on the ground. This figure stood up, his robe rustling in the silence of the room. The next moment, he turned on the light, revealing his appearance, which was the true body of Manison.

After the battle, he had released his Lord's Descent and had not been in contact with others for quite a while. During this time, he had been secretly operating his organizations in the various Star Fields, ready to deal with the suppression of the three Universal Civilizations.

Manison knew better than anyone what sort of measures the three Universal Civilizations would take against him.

"This day has arrived a lot sooner than I expected…"

Manison let out a sigh of relief before his tone turned a little unpleasant as he snarled.

"That kid, Black Star, spoiling my plan!"

If it were not for Black Star, releasing news about the virus core, he would not have had to take the risk to try and obtain it.

Manison had also found clues about the virus core and concealed his tracks without reporting it to the three Universal Civilizations, all so that he would have the opportunity to swallow the Virtual Mutiny Virus, secretly obtain this technology, and make a fortune.

In his opinion, Black Star also had this opportunity, with even more clues than he had, but in order to reduce the damage of the disaster, he sought out the three Universal Civilizations to share his intelligence!

If not for this, he would not have had to compete against the three Universal Civilizations in full view. If he had missed out on this opportunity, then he would never have obtained the chance to get the Virtual Mutiny Virus technology.

Everything was due to Black Star!

He had taken the risk, but Black Star had actually destroyed the virus core in the end, making everyone fight for nothing.

Manison could still recall the moment Han Xiao crushed the virus core, and this made his heart ache.

Since he dared run the risk of offending the three Universal Civilizations to rob the virus core, it was naturally because the item was worth it.

As a top-notch Virtual Mechanic, with an AI civilization under him, if he obtained the full Virtual Mutiny Virus dataset and improved on it, there would be a violent chemical reaction. Coupled with his own strength, it would be enough to create a new version of the universe!

Apart from this, as long as he placed the core in his own artificial intelligence incubation room, cultivating generations of viruses in advance and placing them out to penetrate the universe, he would be everywhere at once!

At that time, the Intelligent Plague would be a toddler compared to him!

Even if the three Universal Civilizations obtained the technology, there was still a chance. Manison could still hack in and steal the technology at the risk of being discovered.

But now, the opportunity for him to reach the apex had been ruined by Black Star. Manison could not help but want to deem Black Star as a 'criminal' on the spot.

Manison shook his head. With things as they were, there was no use dwelling on it. It was better to deal with the matters in the present.

After this matter, the relationship I have with the federation will become even more strained. The three Universal Civilizations will scheme to cut off my wings, but fortunately, I've managed to get rid of as many attachments as I could over the years. I've also obtained independent channels and cultivated a large number of hidden forces. Many of my businesses can easily be transferred into hidden ones…

Since a long time ago, Manison felt that there would come a day where he would turn independent, and thus prepared for a rainy day. He dared to take the risk today because he was not afraid of falling out with the three Universal Civilizations.

Moreover, given the current situation, neither side would be completely opposed to the other, since the three Universal Civilizations still had some restraining fear toward him.

Manison had calculated his risks before he acted, thus taking the opportunity to reveal a few of his cards. The tens of millions of Lord's Avatars that he revealed were enough to make the three Universal Civilizations hesitate in dealing with him, fearing the repercussions of their actions on the innocents. As long as they could not find his body, he could always appear once more.

The three Universal Civilizations will want to support Black Star to compete with me. I guess I'll lose my funding from the federation, and I'll now have to make new friends…

Manison narrowed his eyes, deep in thought.

After the virus core was eradicated, the disaster relief efficiency of the three Universal Civilizations was rapidly accelerated, and the anti-virus kit was re-promoted as part of the anti-virus plans.

Without the virus core, the first generation of the Virtual Mutiny Virus had no leader and lost all coordination. The three Universal Civilizations just had to scan and lock down each node before clearing them at the same time. They would then go online immediately with a dedicated firewall. The viruses in the Ancient Star Desert were solved quickly, and the damage done by the Intelligent Plague was quickly rectified.

It had been several months since the outbreak of the Intelligent Plague, and the Star Field had been blocked out of signal for the whole time, leading the universe to be concerned about the status quo of the Ancient Star Desert. As the news was blocked for a long time, more and more rumors started circulating in the universe, spreading faint panic.

Now that the disaster was under control, the three Universal Civilizations finally issued an announcement to the entire universe to reassure the citizens of Galaxy.

In the announcement, the three Universal Civilizations specifically shared the entire experience of hunting down the virus core.

As soon as the official news bulletin was released, it immediately attracted the attention of countless organizations within the explored universe.

Han Xiao's deeds were also propagated around the universe following the deliberate announcements by the three Universal Civilizations, causing a huge uproar!

Chapter 1123: Damaged Blueprint

Following the development of the Star Field, more galactic residents had begun pouring into the Flickering World. The various industries had been rapidly improved, and a large number of planets were transformed into transit stations or tourist destinations.

As the entrance of the territory of the Black Star Army and the gateway toward one of the top ten stargate traffic routes in the Flickering World, Planet Black Gate had an amazing number of daily visitors. Numerous entertainment facilities had been built on the planet's surface, confusing day and night and causing the place to be constantly noisy. Every moment was extraordinary, as one could see visitors from all Star Fields and races present.

Murica Street was a famed entertainment street, with casinos, pubs, shops, and departmental stores present. The area was full of feasting and pleasure seeking, with people constantly coming and going without rest.

"It's been a while since I last came here, and it's getting more and more prosperous."

Maple Moon dragged Frenzied Sword along as they walked through the bustling street, looking curiously around at the strange passersby.

Seeing their emblems, showing them to be high-ranking warriors from the Black Star Army, everyone showed varying degrees of awe in their eyes, giving way to them. On the bustling street, there seemed to be an invisible wall around them.

"Stop browsing. We're here to submit our mission." Frenzied Sword could only speak helplessly.

At this moment, the giant screen on the wall of a building in the distance lit up, showing a news screen.

"Now, we'll broadcast an urgent piece of news. The Federation of Light, the Crimson Dynasty, and the Arcane Church are jointly issuing an announcement to report on the progress of the Intelligent Plague to the entire universe…"

Hearing the first official news about the Ancient Star Desert in days, the pedestrians on the street stopped suddenly, as though someone had pressed a 'freeze' button. They all looked up at the screen and stopped to watch.

Frenzied Sword and Maple Moon both stopped as well, curiously looking at the screen.

They saw the scene of a diplomatic press conference on the giant screen. The spokespersons of the three Universal Civilizations all stood side by side and read out the announcement.

"The Intelligent Plague has troubled us for several months. We contained the disaster within the Ancient Star Desert and carried out a special disaster relief operation. Because this matter concerned the security of the entire universe, it attracted great attention from all walks of life. Thus, we're hereby making a special report today to announce the progress of our tripartite governance of the Intelligent Plague."

"The Virtual Mutiny Virus is a highly dangerous information data virus that can rewrite the underlying logic of any artificial intelligence, turning machinery into an exterminating organism. The virus has an amazing permeability, spread, and threat, and it is an information warfare weapon that has been lost in time. We thought that the threat came from the virus itself, but it was only recently discovered that the virus core was the true threat…"

The representatives described the mechanisms of the virus core, highlighting the danger of its self-evolution adaptability, using exaggerated words to describe the consequences of the disasters.

Hearing this, the people listening on the streets shuddered involuntarily.

Because of the news blockade, the galactic residents had little understanding of the Virtual Mutiny Virus. Now that they understood the real horror behind the virus, they could not help feeling a panic in their hearts, frightened by the lethality of the virus.

At this moment, the spokesperson changed the conversation, saying, "If Black Star had not discovered the threat of the virus core, we would still be in the dark. According to our artificial intelligence's simulation, the anti-virus plan we made without the knowledge of the virus core would have had a success rate of no more than 0.1%. It is very likely that the virus would have leaked out in the end, leading to disasters sweeping across the entire universe. Countless creatures would have died in the disaster, and the interstellar era would have regressed catastrophically.

"This discovery by Black Star allowed us to avoid this result, so his merits are huge, as he has indirectly saved countless people."

Many of them breathed out a sigh of relief, still feeling the jitters at the thought of their escape from disaster, and thanked Black Star for changing their fates.

The representative then continued. "Because of Black Star's intelligence, we planned an operation, and the entire Star Field was disconnected from the network to chase down the core of the virus. Everything was going well. However, when the virus core was captured, some twists and turns occurred…"

"The virus core was captured by the Mechanic Emperor Manison, but he refused to turn it in regardless of the safety of the universe, in an attempt to reverse-engineer the complete technology. In order to maintain the peace of the universe, Black Star seized the virus core, destroying it and completely eliminating this technology. He eliminated the possibility of a re-emergence of this Virtual Mutiny Virus so that the whole universe would always be out of the shadow of this disaster.

"But the Mechanic Emperor was unwilling to fail like this. Thus, he attacked Black Star, and the two of them fought to a tie. He was finally driven back by Black Star."

Frenzied Sword and Maple Moon could hear the commotion of the people around them on the street.

This speech first raised the issue of the operation, triggering the anxiety of the population, then made a comparison between both the Mechanic Emperor and Black Star, distinguishing between them. It deliberately promoted Han Xiao's actions protecting the galactic residents, implanting an image of Black Star with boundless love for the residents, making the galactic residents thank him for his contribution.

In contrast, the Mechanic Emperor was portrayed as a selfish careerist who disregarded the overall situation. Because he ignored the interests of the galactic residents, he was regarded as a villain, and his image discredited.

The representative summarized the entire happenings at the end.

"Today, the management of the Intelligent Plague is now in its final stages. The disaster is under control, and the virus will be completely eliminated in the next few days. The blockade surrounding the Ancient Star Desert will be lifted. In this incident, the merits that Black Star has rendered are irreplaceable, and thus, the three Universal Civilizations have decided to jointly award the title of Special Safety Consultant for the three Universal Civilizations to Black Star as a reward."

Special Security Consultant to the three Universal Civilizations?

Frenzied Sword and Maple Moon looked at each other, surprised.

Didn't the federation and the church have something against our Black Star Army? They've now turned their status as enemies into friends. Were they 'taken down' by the Army Commander?

Then, won't we have two more strong and sturdy thighs to hug?

The news ended, but the enthusiasm of the people had just been aroused. They fervently discussed the topic, creating a buzzing in the streets.

"Thanks God for His Excellency Black Star. He's really a great person."

"Among all of the Beyond Grade As, only Black Star is working for the welfare of our ordinary people. Just like the previous Holy Light Emissary cultivation plan, he's given us ordinary people a chance, an opportunity to turn someone into a Super. Now he is determined to destroy this virus technology because of our safety. For this reason, he even went to war with the Mechanic Emperor. If I were a woman, I'd definitely fall in love with him."

"Sigh, I never expected the Mechanic Emperor Manison to be that sort of person. To think I used to worship him."

"For such a great merit, no wonder the three Universal Civilizations invited Black Star to be a Special Security Consultant. It seems like no one has ever been awarded such an honor, right?"

"Frankly speaking, other than Black Star, I cannot think of anyone who would be more qualified for this position."

At this moment, from the opposite street came out a wave of cheers. Someone ran over and exclaimed, "Hurry, there are a few wealthy merchants who've bought the entire bar's stock. They said that they were thankful for Black Star's accomplishments and are offering free drinks to everyone!"

Hearing this, the people on the street swarmed over, and when they passed Frenzied Sword and Maple Moon, they no longer avoided them. Rather, they enthusiastically greeted them, using all kinds of weird etiquette to show respect to the people of the Black Star Army.

Feeling the warm atmosphere, Frenzied Sword and Maple Moon felt a sense of pride flowing in their hearts. They strongly felt the sense of camp identity.

The two of them hurriedly went to the forums, and the forums had already exploded as the news swept across the board.

Their Army Commander had only disappeared for a few months, but he immediately made such big news as soon as he appeared. The three Universal Civilizations exaggerated the whole thing, making it seem as though Black Star was their savior, leaving the players extremely excited.

Glorious Tomahawk: Damn, so we were in the frontal camp?

Cloud Dragon Li: Second Battalion Commander, take out my spaghetti to let Black Star try[1]!

Intelligent Cold Monarch: Be reasonable, this time, the Army Commander can be described as… handsome!

Gallery Sister: Black Star is still Black Star. He never lets us down!

Fawkes: Where's 'Galaxy Times'? Come out to get beaten up. You said that it's gonna be a mission, so why did it become a cutscene instead?

Daydreamer: Am I the only one that cares about how the Army Commander and the Mechanic Emperor tied?

Throughout the posts on the screen, there was basically a wave of praise. Some of the older players gave the newbies a run down on the deeds that Black Star had done, such as solving the Mutation Disaster, destroying the DarkStar organization, and so on.

Even after several versions, Han Xiao's image in the eyes of the players was still magnificent, and this time, his merits once again raised the players' perception of him, giving birth to a consensus.

Black Star is really a noble man!

In addition to faction interests, if the leader of a faction had a charming personality, the players would also have a sense of identity.

…

As soon as the public announcement was released, everyone that was concerned about the progress of the Intelligent Plague was relieved.

This achievement allowed Han Xiao's reputation to rise to the top for a while, whereas Manison's reputation was struck down by the deliberate suppression.

At the same time, Han Xiao's fleet had just passed through the dynasty's military stargate, leaving the Ancient Star Desert. He also saw the official announcement of the three Universal Civilizations.

"Tsk, the three Universal Civilizations' representatives are really skilled in the act of raising one while kicking down another."

Han Xiao read the news happily. He just loved it when people praised him.

At that moment, he suddenly had a thought and opened his interface to take a look.

With the three Universal Civilizations basically completing the elimination of the first-generation Virtual Mutiny Virus, only an unsuspecting ending was left. Thus, when the announcement was made, the Intelligent Plague mission finally changed to 'Completed'.

The mission can finally be turned in.

Han Xiao turned his head to look at Harrison, whom he had brought onto the spaceship, rubbing him before choosing to accept the mission completion reward.

S-Ranked Mission: Intelligent Plague has been completed!

Mission Rating: S+ (Perfect)

You have obtained 300 billion experience, x8 Random Rewards, +35,000 Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points, +15,000 Federation of Light Contribution Points, and +15,000 Arcane Church Contribution Points.

You have gained x2 Political Assets (The Crimson Dynasty), x1 Political Asset (Federation of Light), and x1 Political Asset (Arcane Church).

You have obtained x4 Legendary Points.

Star Field Legendary Point (Ancient Star Desert): [Black Market's Giant Croc] - Through various means and methods, you temporarily unified the black market organizations of the Ancient Star Desert, leaving behind a frightening legend.

Universe Legendary Point: [Intelligent Plague's Curer] - The Intelligent Plague is a universe level disaster on the level of complete annihilation. You accepted the invites from the three Universal Civilizations to treat the disaster and finally made a unique contribution to successfully solve the disaster. The whole universe will remember your achievements and contributions!

Universe Legendary Point: [Galaxy's Guardian] - You had to choose between selfish desires or righteousness. For choosing the latter, your choice has maintained the peace of the universe and affected the evolution of the entire universe. Perhaps this is a turning point in your destiny. You are always watching and guarding Galaxy, and the people all know it.

Universe Legendary Point: [Special Security Consultant for the Three Universal Civilizations] - You have been invited to become a special consultant for the three Universal Civilizations. This is unprecedented, and no matter how the situation evolves, you will leave behind a rich and colorful stroke in history.

Dungeon Copy Created: Intelligent Plague (Simulated Disaster)

Han Xiao nodded.

The rewards up to this point were still within his calculations.

After all, this was an S-level mission, and he had even achieved a perfect evaluation. The rewards were bound to be huge.

It was just that Han Xiao got stunned the moment he continued reading.

Given that your mission rating has achieved S, you have received extra reward

You have received a new skill: Blueprint - Domino Virus (Damaged)!

You have completed the special mission requirement: Personally destroying the virus core

Generating a related specialty… generation complete.

You have received a new talent, [Virtual Purification—Restore]!

"What‽"

Han Xiao's eyes widened, staring blankly at the reward of [Blueprint: Domino Virus (Damaged)].

This was not an extra reward for the completion of the special mission requirements but a normal reward obtained when the S ranked mission reached the highest rating. This meant that only those who had made great contributions in disaster relief could obtain this reward.

After toiling so hard to resolve the intelligent plague, the mission actually gave me a damaged blueprint of the virus technology, allowing me to recreate it…

He suddenly felt a great wave of irony.

I didn't expect that, after so many twists and turns, this virus technology was actually not destroyed and has landed in my hands… even though it's a damaged remnant.

Looking at the content of this blueprint, Han Xiao's expression was conflicted. He did not know if he should be happy.

[1] [Annotation text missing] Back

Chapter 1124: Spy

The mission reward was the incomplete version of the Domino Virus blueprint, so a lot of key content was missing. A lot of deduction had to be done to put the blueprint into production, and the results of those deductions might not be the same as the original version.

It's very troublesome to deduce complete blueprints at this level from the incomplete version. Sure, I can use Awakening Points to speed it up, but that seems a bit wasteful. I'll be better off slowly working my way through it.

Fate was really unpredictable. He had thought that the Domino Virus was destroyed, but the technology still ended up in his hands. The entire outside world thought that he had destroyed the Domino Virus, so there was no way Han Xiao could just expose the fact that he had this technology. Otherwise, the results would definitely be the exact opposite of the treatment he was receiving now.

Furthermore, the core material of it was a thousand mutated artificial intelligence lives, which was not easy to find. Manison had a lot of them, but it was certainly not realistic for him to purchase any from him right after having a fight with him. Plus, Manison might notice something even if he could purchase any from him.

Therefore, this technology could not be shown to the world for a very long time. He might only use it when facing enemies like the World Tree civilization.

Now that I think about it, it seems logical for Mechanic Emperor not to use the Domino Virus during the World Tree war in the previous life.

Han Xiao suddenly figured it out.

Unless the situation of the war was totally one-sided and unwinnable, even if he could obtain the upper hand with this kind of weapon, he would still be surrounded by trouble after victory.

Perhaps, in his previous life, the Mechanic Emperor saw the Domino Virus as something similar to the Hand of Death System. When the three Universal Civilizations really had no way of winning the war, only then might he release the Domino Virus. He would then use his tons of Lord's Avatars and mechanical armies to utilize guerrilla warfare tactics against the World Tree Civilization.

Han Xiao recalled something else. In his previous life, having considered the possibility of losing the war, the three Universal Civilizations executed the 'Tinder Operation'. They sent a large group of wandering fleets out and far away from the explored universe. At the same time, they built tons of refugee shelters deep inside the secondary dimensions, which stored intelligent life forms, crops, and flora and fauna samples, ensuring that the civilization could be rebuilt after losing the war.

He wondered if the Mechanic Emperor had his eyes on those refugees. Could his plan have been to start anew after losing the war, escape faraway, and build a world in which he was the god of creation?

If his final goal was to rule the entire world, this might really seem like the most feasible path.

Han Xiao let his imagination run wild for a while before focusing on the matter at hand again. He closed the introduction of [Blueprint: Domino Virus (Incomplete)] and looked at the related talent he had just obtained.

[Virtual Purification—Restore] could purify the artificial intelligence target that was infected by viruses. The Virtual Mutiny Virus, for example, rewrote the fundamental logic of machines into killing organic life forms, and this talent's effect would clear that modification and restore the target's normal fundamental logic.

Simply put, if those artificial intelligences were considered hypnotized when their fundamental logic was modified, this ability would wake them up.

At the same time, this ability was not limited to the Domino Virus; it could restore any type of virtual virus.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. This is going to be very useful in virtual battles. The Mechanic Emperor is probably going to cry when facing this.

If his control of the mechanical army was taken away, he could just use this talent and directly regain control from the enemy.

However, given his current strength, there was almost no one who could take away his control of his mechanical troops. The only one Han Xiao could think of was the Mechanic Emperor.

Speaking of which, Manison controls his artificial intelligence civilization through rewriting their fundamental logic too, like what the ancestor of that civilization, Finette, is experiencing. This talent is going to give him a huge problem.

Han Xiao scratched his head and thought of the [Reboot] series mission that had been collecting dust for a very long time at the bottom of his mission list.

It looks like I just got the key to liberate that artificial intelligence civilization.

If I find an opportunity to use this on Manison's AI civilization, his Indestructible Mechanic Empire might totally go out of control.

Also, since a portion of Manison's elite forces were created by transforming living bodies, he might have used virtual means to twist their minds, so [Virtual Purification—Restore] might be effective on them too. When a certain level was reached, virtual methods that could be used on living things would actually have a lot of similarities to soul-related spells.

To take it one step further, this might even be effective on the World Tree, even more so than the Domino Virus…

Recalling how the World Tree operated, Han Xiao pondered.

The blueprint and the talent were the biggest rewards he had obtained. Universal Grade S missions sure gave generous reward.

He also received a total of four Political Assets that came from all the three Universal Civilizations. This meant that after this incident, his words would carry weight even in the federation and the church. At the same time, the EXP bonus he received increased once again.

Han Xiao glanced at the [Intelligent Plague (Disaster Simulation)] Dungeon. This was a special type of Dungeon. It no longer worked through intercepting a part of this incident but through selecting a certain area, and the dungeon would simulate what happened in this area during the Intelligent Plague outbreak. The difficulty depended on the area.

For example, if the selected area was the Black Star Army headquarters, the difficulty would almost be impossible. If the area was a normal colonial planet of a normal Star System civilization, the difficulty would be around Grade B or Grade C. If the area was a sealed battleship, it might turn into a horror movie.

This Dungeon should have a good market, especially for the Mechanics. Han Xiao saw quite a good business future.

Also, the large amount of EXP awarded to him filled up his empty wallet, and the total 65,000 Contribution Points for the three Universal Civilizations could not only be used to exchange for Ultimate Knowledges but also Gold blueprints. The three Universal Civilizations had already opened this option up to him.

Speaking of Gold blueprints, Han Xiao suddenly thought of the Holy Accord and the federation. These two were making deals with him, but it was put aside temporarily because the Intelligent Plague suddenly erupted.

There was no need to worry about the federation; they definitely would not forget about it. What he was mainly concerned about was the Holy Accord organization. The date they previously agreed on was voided, and Oathkeeper did not leave any means of contact, so he could only wait for Oathkeeper to come looking for him.

After going through the rewards, Han Xiao closed the interface and contacted the headquarters.

The fleet had already left the Ancient Star Desert and could now communicate with the outside world freely. He had been out for a few months, so he wanted to know what was going on in the army.

The communication got picked up very soon. Sylvia's projection appeared before him, wearing exquisite makeup on her elegant face and a simple work uniform that highlighted her exceptional curves. She seemed to be in the middle of a meeting, and she was surprised to see Han Xiao.

"Teacher, you finally got released?"

"Erm, yeah." Han Xiao gave her a weird expression. Why did you say it in a way that sounds like I just got out of prison?

"I've seen the news. The decision you made was marvelous." Sylvia praised him. "The entire army is now praising your virtue, and the army is more united than ever. The director from that time wants to sign the contract for five more follow up movies. Since you're not here, I didn't reply to him."

"Tell him yes, and Feidin will still be the lead, so he has something to do."

Han Xiao waved his hand. Suddenly, he realized that Sylvia was wearing a pair of frameless spectacles, adding a well-educated lady vibe to her, so he asked, "Why are you wearing spectacles?"

Sylvia blushed a little. She took off the spectacles and showed them to him. On the inside of the glass was a single-sided screen. Embarrassed, she said, "Meetings are sometimes boring, so I use these to watch shows…"

"… Have you gotten close with Lagi recently?"

"Nonsense, I hate him the most!" Sylvia firmly denied it.

Han Xiao did not want to make a fuss about his subordinates slacking at work, so he changed the topic and asked, "By the way, how's the Black Star Cup going?"

"Well, due to the impact of the Intelligent Plague, the audience rating of the Black Star Cup decreased somewhat, but it's maintained its popularity. At this point of time, most of the secondary competitions are already finished. The army's elites in various areas have already been selected… er, the card players don't count." Sylvia paused momentarily. "Currently, only the finals of a few important items are left. They're the battles of the various Grades…"

Han Xiao listened to Sylvia's report while nodding and saying, "Not bad, not bad."

He did not have many forms of entertainment in the Ancient Star Desert, so he was looking at the forums every day and paying attention to the Black Star Cup. As the competition carried on, the only ones left were the elites of elites. The players had made a name for themselves among the NPCs, so they felt a strong sense of achievement and became very passionate about the event. The popularity of Black Star Cup remained high and comparable to the official Pro League.

Him not being present did not impact the Black Star Cup at all, only causing disappointment to some people who wanted to produce his Character Summon Card when facing crucial matches.

"Teacher, the closing ceremony of the Black Star Cup needs you to make a speech, don't forget. Will you make it back in time?"

"Hmm, definitely." Han Xiao then changed the topic and asked, "Has anything major happened in the army recently? How's the situation in the Flickering World?"

"There are more and more people entering the new Star Field, the explored area of the free competition zone has already extended to the center of the various Star Clusters, and the territory of the Super Star Cluster Alliance has been increasing. Other than that, there are no other changes. Deputy Army Commander Hila is also slowly exploring with the fleet… By the way, she took leave some time ago, saying she had to go to the secondary dimensions, and told me to inform you."

"Got it." Han Xiao nodded. Ever since Hila inherited the Underworld dimension, she had been going there every few days.

Now that a few months had passed, the Underworld dimension had probably stabilized. He wondered if Hila was sucked dry.

As Hila was brought up, Han Xiao was reminded of another matter.

"How's the Holy Light Emissary plan going?"

"Very smoothly. Other than recruiting ordinary people, we've also recruited many people to cultivate the Holy Light Seeds and let Aurora harvest them after the seeds mature. These people have already signed contracts before starting work, so there won't be any problems."

"Very good, increase the number of cultivators as much as possible," Han Xiao said. He was hoping Aurora could grow fast by harvesting leeks, so of course, the bigger the leek field, the better.

Then, he paused and said, "I've made a huge contribution this time. The three Universal Civilizations have decided to work with me and provide heavy support in multiple major Star Fields…"

Han Xiao explained the details of the support the three Universal Civilizations were about to provide, and Sylvia soon turned moody.

"So, my workload has increased again?"

"Tsk, buddy, your resolve isn't strong enough." Han Xiao criticized her with a serious tone. "You need to have a more positive mindset. Having a wider work scope and heavier workload means you now have more power in your hands, right?"

As if I'd believe you! Sylvia chuckled with absolutely zero emotion.

Hearing her laughter, Han Xiao nodded with satisfaction. Just look at how happy she is, her face is basically covered with joy.

He then glanced at Sylvia's hairline and was relieved.

After his many years of experience, the hairline of his subordinates was equivalent to their durability. It looked like this student of his could still last quite a long time.

The two of them chattered for a while, and Sylvia suddenly thought of something.

"By the way, yesterday, there was a political talk show that wanted to invite you as their guest to discuss this Intelligent Plague incident. Do you want to go?"

"What show?"

"That 'Ruden's Show' that's quite popular."

"No, no." Han Xiao waved his hand.

With the three Universal Civilizations helping him to promote himself, he did not have to do it personally. Keeping a certain amount of mystery and distance would be more beneficial for his reputation.

"Alright, I'll refuse him then."

Han Xiao gave Sylvia a few words before hanging up.

The Intelligent Plague was a sudden incident. Without it, the three Universal Civilizations would definitely be preparing to deal with the Super Star Cluster Alliance. Now, this had been postponed. The Intelligent Plague had given the Super Star Cluster Alliance time to catch their breath.

After the three Universal Civilizations were done with the Intelligent Plague completely, they would then start fighting with the Super Star Cluster Alliance like they did in his previous life. This time, the Super Star Cluster Alliance was more prepared, so the fight would definitely be more intense. The results of that would decide the path the universe took.

As a semi-independent force, his fight with the Mechanic Emperor in the development union would definitely be dragged into this storm too. He had to prepare early.

Hu!

While he was thinking about this matter, the sound of the air moving abnormally suddenly appeared beside him.

Han Xiao looked up and saw clusters of black flames appearing out of nowhere, forming a man wearing a black coat whose face could not be seen clearly, which suddenly appeared before him. It was indeed the Holy Accord's Oathkeeper's spiritual projection.

Han Xiao looked around and saw that all the crew in the bridge command room including Harrison did not react to Oathkeeper at all, as if they could not see him.

"We meet again, Black Star," Oathkeeper said. His voice sounded right in Han Xiao's mind. They had formed a mind link.

"You're on time, coming here right after I've left the Ancient Star Desert." Han Xiao caressed his chin and asked through the mind link, "Speaking of which, why can you use your spiritual projection on me directly? Do you know my whereabouts?"

"This is the specialty of my Esper Ability," Oathkeeper said slowly. "There are no two exactly the same souls in the world, especially strong individuals. Souls are very easy to identify. As long as I record the characteristics of your soul, I can trace the target in a higher dimension and use spiritual projection on you right away. Of course, it's only limited to that. I can't figure out where the target is in the real world."

Han Xiao was not surprised.

The Beyond Grade A leader of a mysterious organization that had stayed hidden for so many years definitely had some tricks up his sleeves.

"You contacted me to continue our trade previously, right? Trading a part of two Primal Esper Abilities and two Universal Treasure blueprints for a part of the Holy Light Particle."

"That's right," Oathkeeper replied with a deep voice.

Due to the Intelligent Plague, the deal was postponed for a few months, which he was actually happy about. He had used these few months to focus on finding the spy in the Holy Accord.

Sadly, the act of looking for a spy made everyone in the organization uneasy and worried, but he did not even find the slightest trace of a spy.

It was either that the spy hid too well, or Black Star's information did not come from a spy.

Day by day, Oathkeeper became more suspicious about whether a spy really existed. Hence, he temporarily stopped the investigation.

"Then let's decide on another date…" Han Xiao suddenly thought of something and asked casually, "By the way, you guys have a long history, so you should know about a lot of secret information, right?"

"Depends."

"Then… have you guys heard about the Sanctum?"

"…" Oathkeeper was totally unprepared and was startled by this question. His mind was filled with shock.

This is a test, right? This must be a test!

Didn't you say you don't know our purpose the last time‽

Liar!

His initially shaken resolve became extremely firm once again.

There's definitely a spy!

Find him! Find him no matter what!

Chapter 1125: Information About the Sanctum

Oathkeeper tried his best to suppress the shock in his mind and keep his mind frequency stable, so Han Xiao would not find out he panicked.

He observed Han Xiao's expression and mind frequency, but he could not see any mockery from him, only curiosity.

Did Black Star ask about the Sanctum because he knew the Holy Accord's plans, or did he hear about this name somewhere else? There were not that many people who knew about the Sanctum throughout the entire universe.

Oathkeeper's emotions were like a tiny boat in the raging sea. He maintained his cool as much as possible. He acted casual and asked, "Where did you hear about the Sanctum?"

"Someone told me." Han Xiao casually lied—no way he was going to tell the truth.

"Who?" Oathkeeper continued asking. "There are very, very few people in the entire universe that know about the existence of the Sanctum. Even advanced civilizations might not."

Since Black Star had mentioned the name 'Sanctum', Oathkeeper knew that Black Star definitely had some kind of knowledge about it. If he acted like he did not know about the Sanctum, he might lose out on the opportunity of finding out how much Han Xiao actually knew.

"Well… if I say it's intuition, will you believe me?"

Han Xiao had no choice but to use the jack of all trades of excuses. Although it was not very convincing, he did not plan to convince Oathkeeper anyway.

However, to his surprise, Oathkeeper nodded softly and did not continue asking any more questions. It was as if this was the right answer. Oathkeeper then said, "This is indeed a simple way of sensing the Sanctum, but it's not within one's control, and it's very blurry. Only individuals who reached a certain level in the hierarchy of life can maybe, somehow, possibly build an extremely weak link with the Sanctum, occasionally witnessing its blurry outline when connected with the universe. However, your senses are countless dimensions apart from it, and you will never come into contact with it. The most you'll experience will only be mumbling beside your ears in the ancient language…"

Han Xiao was stunned.

Excuse me, what's going on buddy? What's with this theology explanation?

Hearing what Oathkeeper was saying, Han Xiao did not know if he should believe him. He really did have no idea of what the Sanctum was, and he had only brought it up today with the attitude of trying his luck. However, it looked like the Holy Accord really did know about the Sanctum.

"Stop the nonsense. Can you say something that I can understand?"

Han Xiao could not take it anymore and interrupted.

Oathkeeper went silent for a moment, seemingly hesitating over whether he should expose any information. After contemplating, he decided that sharing some basic information would not hurt, so he slowly said, "The Sanctum… is an ancient existence. No one knows when it appeared. It might be even more ancient than the three Universal Civilizations. One can only sense or even come into contact with it during special timings using specific methods."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

He had finally met someone who knew anything about the Sanctum, so he was not going to give up the opportunity.

"Then, what is the Sanctum? Where is it?"

Hearing this, Oathkeeper looked at Han Xiao with a strange expression. Seeing that Han Xiao did not look like he was faking it, he asked, "You don't know?"

"Why would I ask you if I did?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

What he knew about the Holy Accord was limited only to the surface; he really did not know about the Holy Accord and the Sanctum's connection. Therefore, he had no idea that he coincidentally asked the right question and horrified Oathkeeper.

Hearing this, Oathkeeper finally was relieved and glad.

It seems like Black Star really doesn't know about our plan. Did I misunderstand? Could there be no spies and Black Star got the information from somewhere else?

While thinking that, Oathkeeper continued speaking. "The Sanctum is not in the material world, nor is it in the secondary dimensions. In fact, it does not have a geographical location. I don't know how to define the Sanctum either, but I think it's more like a phenomenon."

"A phenomenon?" Han Xiao asked curiously.

"Yes, a phenomenon."

Han Xiao waited for Oathkeeper to carry on, but Oathkeeper had no intention to.

The two of them looked at each other, and the conversation got cut off.

Seeing this, Han Xiao knew that Oathkeeper was not willing to continue on this topic, so he changed the question and asked, "So, what's inside the sanctum?"

"…"

The two of them continued to look at each other.

"How many Sanctums are there in total?"

This time, Oathkeeper replied. "Six."

Han Xiao was a little stunned. This answer was not what he expected.

He asked a few more questions such as how to find the Sanctums, how to open the Sanctums, and so on. Without exception, Oathkeeper said nothing about any of that.

This guy definitely knows more, but he's just not willing to share any key information. Hence, the Sanctums are definitely something very important… although I still don't know what their uses are.

This thought flashed past his mind. Seeing that he could not obtain any more information from Oathkeeper, Han Xiao ended the Sanctum topic and went back to their deal. They decided on a new date, location, and method of the deal and agreed on it.

Having achieved what he had come for, Oathkeeper's silhouette exploded, turned into flowers of black flame, and dissipated.

Han Xiao sensed around, made sure that Oathkeeper had left, then caressed his chin and started pondering.

The Holy Accord organization seems to know about a lot of secrets. I might have to think of a way to get more information from them. The only way of contacting them now is when Oathkeeper contacts me, so I'm a little passive in this respect. During the deal, I can try tracing their emissary… By the way, there are six Sanctums?

Han Xiao was confused. This was different from what he had guessed. He originally thought there were only five Sanctums. Why six?

However, Oathkeeper was very ambiguous on this matter and was not willing to share any more information.

He had an idea.

After the deal is done, I can consider bringing up their intention to revive the Primordial Ones. Maybe I can use that in exchange for information about the Sanctums, counting it as the price for keeping my mouth shut.

…

Inside the secret temple in the Holy Accord organization base, Oathkeeper, who was floating in midair with his legs crossed, deactivated his spiritual projection. The clusters of flames floating around him went back into his body.

"How did it go?"

Law and Fay were waiting below and looking up at their boss.

"Black Star was friendly. The deal has been reestablished," Oathkeeper said slowly. "Prepare our chips. The method of the deal remains the same as planned, so we won't be tracked by Black Star."

"Understood." The two of them nodded.

Oathkeeper nodded and said with a tone that was a little grave but had some anticipation in it, "Due to the information state disturbance Destiny's Child talked about, the promised day has been brought forward. After we acquire the Holy Light Particle, we'll prepare to activate the Third Sanctum and the awakening ceremony. Thousand Shadows' Esper Ability is the foundation of the fusion. We have no time to wait for him to completely transform, so we'll have to start finishing it."

While speaking, Oathkeeper's eyes looked like they were staring deep into the universe.

"It's time to fulfill my promise and welcome the return of history."

"The spy…" The two of them brought the matter up at possibly the worst timing.

Oathkeeper's emotions were interrupted. He ground his teeth and said with frustration, "Humph, stop looking for one. I might have been mistaken."

…

In the Underworld dimension, the shattered black floating islands had assembled together into a black land. It looked like a flowing desert, sometimes with tall mountains, sometimes with deep cliffs. Its terrain kept changing.

In the sky, heavy black clouds covered the sky, some darker and some lighter. A pale white sphere of light floated in the middle of the sky like a moon. Its gently silver light penetrated the clouds, illuminating the land. The atmosphere was calm and peaceful.

More than half a year had passed since Hila started to refill the dimension's core energy. The broken space walls there were already repaired, and the chaotic space streams were blocked out. It was no longer in a horrible and heavily damaged state. This was what the Underworld dimension should really look like.

At the heart of the Underworld was a red lake. There was no wind, only high tides. When looking at it more closely, this was made of highly condensed and almost liquid formed energy. It was indeed Hila's death energy.

At this time, the piercing bright red had tints of faint black. This came from the Underworld and was applied on Hila through the Mark of the Underworld. Her connection with the Underworld enhanced the strength of her Esper Ability tremendously.

This was the inheritance of the former death energy Esper, which was given to Hila and made her much stronger.

Above the bright red lake, Hila was floating in midair with her legs crossed. She was surrounded by faint red energy, her eyes were closed tight, and her eyelashes were shaking. She was releasing her energy and giving it to the Underworld.

At this time, Onicelu appeared beside Hila.

"Your connection with me is stronger."

Hila opened her eyes and said with an expressionless face, "How much have you recovered after absorbing my energy for a few months?"

"About three percent, more than enough to fight against the chaotic space streams of the secondary dimensions."

"So little?" Hila frowned.

"After all, the energy of the Underworld comes from two Esper Abilities. If the vital energy Esper reaches Beyond Grade A and feeds the Underworld energy together with you, it will cause resonance and increase the speed of the Underworld's recovery tremendously. You're the only one now, so of course, it won't be as efficient," Onicelu said with a smile.

"I see…" Hila suddenly thought of something and asked, "By the way, since the Underworld is stable now, can the souls of the Hero Spirits be released?"

"Well, they can be, but it's too early, so I don't suggest you do that." Onicelu shook her head. "This is the graveyard of Hero Spirits. There are a lot of souls here. Their activities will consume the energy of the Underworld. The stronger the Hero Spirits were when they were alive, the more energy they will consume, which will decrease the speed of the Underworld's recovery even further. Before the Underworld recovers to thirty percent and the stable way of putting them to sleep is recovered, it's best to keep them sleeping."

"So, you're saying there's not enough power output now?"

"You can say that."

Hila sighed. Although the Underworld was powerful, there was a long way to go till it reached its peak, so it would take a very long time before she could summon Hero Spirit warriors like the founders.

This time, Hila suddenly got curious and asked, "Speaking of which, the Underworld can let the souls of the past temporarily awaken and let them come to this world again, so are there any other ways to let dead people appear in this world again?"

Hearing this, Onicelu searched her memories for a while then said with uncertainty, "When Nerkese and Eros, the two old masters, were still alive, I seem to recall hearing them speak about a special phenomenon related to the dead reviving."

"Really? What's that?" Hila asked.

"It's something called the Sanctum, I think… The two masters had an argument because of it once, and they hardly brought it up after that. It seems like someone invited them on a mission related to the Sanctum. I don't know the details, but they rejected it."

"So, what is the Sanctum? Is it similar to the Underworld?"

"No idea. I don't know much about it. I only overheard their conversation. However, from what I've heard, the Sanctum is very powerful, and reviving the dead is only one of its functions." Onicelu shook her head.

"I see…"

Hila shook her head. She was only casually asking, so she was not too concerned.

However, Onicelu thought about it for a while and said, "If you're very curious, there are some Hero Spirits of Primordial Ones in the Underworld. They might know something. However, if you wake them up, you won't be able to force them to go back to sleep."

"Never mind then. I'll think about it when they can go back to sleep after being woken up. There's no hurry."

Hila shook her head.

She memorized the information about the Sanctum and planned to share it with Black Star to discuss it.

Chapter 1126: Stuarts Peace Prize

The three Universal Civilizations' official announcement quickly spread across all the Star Fields and resolved the panic and unease of the galactic society brought by the Intelligent Plague.

Although most civilizations and races were displeased with how the three Universal Civilizations did some things, they still had strong trust in the three Universal Civilizations when it came to matters that involved the safety of the entire explored universe. They could always make people feel assured.

Before the impact of the announcement was gone, the three Universal Civilizations officially opened up the Ancient Star Desert in less than a month, connecting this Star Field with the galactic society once again.

The first-generation Virtual Mutiny Virus was mostly wiped out. The three Universal Civilizations installed special firewalls in various Star Fields. Without the virus core, these viruses could no longer cause a problem. They would completely disappear with time, so the threat was already defused.

Word from the Ancient Star Desert got out along with it, revealing many more details than in the three Universal Civilizations' announcement. The passion and interest of the galactic residents rose once again.

Han Xiao paid attention to the public opinion of the galactic society on the way back. It was almost all compliments of the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Mechanics with him at the top of it, mixed with criticism of 'Mechanic Emperor' Manison and complaints about the order of the area.

During the Intelligent Plague, the various Star Fields were not peaceful. Most problems were caused by local rebellious forces attempting to incite panic but were all stopped by merciless methods. As for those mercenaries who tried to smuggle the virus out of the Ancient Star Desert, most of them entered the prisons of the three Universal Civilizations, while the rest all became wanted criminals.

Public opinion was going in an excellent direction. There were not many negative opinions, or the negative opinions were censored.

Like sharks that smelled blood, the galactic media groups of the various areas swarmed to the Ancient Star Desert and visited the various planets, digging for more detailed information about what happened during the pandemic. In a short time, they produced a large number of themed shows to compete for attention, which was approved by the three Universal Civilizations behind the curtains.

Their power came from obedience. The three Universal Civilizations had just done something great and heroic—this was the time the media's compliments and discussions were needed so that their positions as the rulers would be firmer and receive more recognition.

The Black Star Army fleet carrying Han Xiao and the others had only arrived at the Shattered Star Ring through the dynasty's military stargates when the dynasty sent someone to contact Han Xiao right away.

"An award ceremony?"

Han Xiao heard this from the dynasty's exploration marshal, Tarrokov.

"That's right. Led by the three Universal Civilizations, the explored universe has once again defused a universal disaster. This will undoubtedly be written in the history books. As for the heroes who aided in defusing the disaster, we'll be hosting a large-scale award ceremony to emphasize what they've done and reward them. Of course, you're on the invitation list."

Han Xiao was not unfamiliar with this. Although he felt this was a rather formal event, he knew that events like this had to be held.

"Okay, where will the award ceremony be held? When? I'm not going to have to make a trip to the Central Galaxy, am I? I've only just returned to my headquarters."

"The three Universal Civilizations will be hosting the award ceremony together, so to keep up with the times and make it more convenient for all the Beyond Grade As to attend, it's been decided that it'll be held in the new Star Field, the Flickering World. The date is in three months, so there's plenty of time."

"Convenient, indeed." Han Xiao nodded. Suddenly, he kept his voice down and asked with a mysterious tone, "Tell me, have you guys finished preparing to target the Super Star Cluster Alliance? When are you guys going to do it?"

"I don't think this is a suitable time to talk about that…" Tarrokov coughed. He also kept his voice down and said, "Anyway, the three Universal Civilizations will only consider redistributing the Super Star Cluster Alliance's territories after the fourth phase of the free competition zone's exploration finishes, not taking them back but sharing them with free organizations and other civilizations… Maybe an excuse similar to the 'New Star Field Anti-Monopolization Exploration Regulations' will be made as the reason."

Pot calling the kettle black… Han Xiao curled his lips. This was what happened in his previous life, so he was not surprised.

"Speaking of which, before you opened up the Ancient Star Desert, did you guys do anything to the Super Star Cluster civilizations there?"

"We really didn't this time, and you understand why… However, although we did not make an attempt on them, we left a lot of eyes and ears behind, closely monitoring the whereabouts of the military and resources of civilizations like the Star Arc Civilization, all to prepare for the conflict that might occur soon," Tarrokov explained.

"Tsk, evil," Han Xiao joked.

"You're one to talk." Tarrokov rolled his eyes. "Don't think I don't know. I heard quite a lot of rumors from the intelligence department that you left quite a lot of things in the Ancient Star Desert's black market."

"You and I both." Han Xiao did not mind.

The two of them were already old friends who had known each other for many years. They joked around for a while and prepared to end the communication.

This time, Tarrokov suddenly thought of something and said, "If you have the time, you can go and watch this show. My colleagues in the public opinion management department seem to have sent some of your information over."

After the call ended, Han Xiao received a link from Tarrokov.

An episode of a political talk show appeared on the virtual screen. It seemed quite recent. This was a show similar to Ruden's Show, but it was more authentic and official. It was called Focus Talk, targeted at people with higher positions in society.

This episode was about the Intelligent Plague. It analyzed the impact the Intelligent Plague had on the Ancient Star Desert. Han Xiao fast-forwarded for a while and finally saw his name.

A well-dressed Godoran was speaking fluently on the show. The subtitles below said this was an advanced researcher of galactic society, a scholar.

"… Before Black Star left Planet Aquamarine, the Godoran Civilization had already heard of him. With our very own eyes, we saw this powerful neighbor, the Black Star Army, rise step by step. We even fought alongside them. The Black Star Army has gotten past the growing stage, and it's not difficult to notice they're trying hard to take on more responsibility in society from the recent Black Star Cup, the Holy Light Emissary project, and the Intelligent Plague.

"Although Black Star is a universe-level warlord, his principles are different from the others. Currently, he controls a large number of resources, and instead of simply keeping all of them to himself, he seems more passionate about using these resources to maintain and improve the environment of the universe. The other Beyond Grade A warlords make us feel afraid and fearful, but toward Black Star, we mostly feel admiration and reverence. He gives us a completely different image, reducing the instinctive fear the galactic residents have toward those strongest individuals in the universe. Perhaps this is this source of his extraordinary affinity…"

While Han Xiao was enjoying his compliments, the images changed, and his deeds flashed past the screen one after another, accompanied by a serious narrator summarizing the events. It sounded quite like an official news segment.

Very soon, the recent events were brought up. This show was able to get their hands on the exclusive first-hand video footage of the confrontation on Planet Magnetic Cloud and played it to the entire universe.

So, this was the promotional material the dynasty sent.

The video captured him fighting Manison in a third-person view. He heard himself saying that sentence again, and it got a close-up.

"…This universe has an end no matter how enormous it is, but ambition has no limits."

Han Xiao stared at the screen and smirked.

He had to admit that at this instant, he looked very handsome in the video.

The dynasty probably sent this video out because they felt that this scene was beneficial to improving his public image.

The next moment, the narration ended, and the scene changed to a grand office. The interviewer changed into someone very famous too. The subtitles showed that this person was the president of the Stuarts Committee.

Kraber Peterhius, a tenured professor of the Federation of Light's Advanced Supreme Science and Technology Institute, principal of the Truth Academy, winner of 'Stars' and Heller's Eye medals… There were so many titles that the subtitles had to keep rolling down to display all of them.

The Stuarts Committee was not some little organization but had an extremely long history and superior position. Its founder was the founder of the Energy Rank theory, Professor Stuarts Ona, traditionally known as the 'Father of Supers'.

In his late years, he founded an award under his name. It was used to reward professionals who had made a huge achievement in various areas. The committee was the organization that managed and assessed the award. It was similar to the Nobel Prize in Han Xiao's past life, but this was even more impressive and had been going on for thousands of years.

Every year, the three Universal Civilizations and the advanced civilizations would provide sponsorships. The Stuarts Award maintained absolutely neutral. The assessment of their award was affected by any political or economic factors. The award was given out once every three years. It could not really be considered the most anticipated event, but it was very prestigious.

Kraber stroked his neatly combed gray braided beard, smiled at the camera, and said, "Black Star is an extremely powerful individual, as well as a respectable scientist. Not mentioning his capabilities, I also respect his philosophy. I'm a scientist, too, and I know very well of the overflowing desire and curiosity we scientists have about the unknown. No one knows better than me how much perseverance it takes to personally destroy unknown technology. I admire Black Star, and I believe he deserves to be the first shared Special Safety Consultant of the three Universal Civilizations more than anyone.

"I can let you guys know a little bit of information from behind the curtains. The Stuarts Committee has already received a lot of members' nominations for Black Star's Peace Prize. As a nominee of this year's Stuarts Peace Prize, Black Star has received a lot of support. From my personal perspective, I have high hopes for him. He's made a huge contribution to the universe."

Kraber did not hide his admiration for Han Xiao at all. At the end of the interview, he made a brief summary.

"In the future, when we look back and study this history, we might see the choice Black Star made today as the turning point of this era. He might have affected the path of the entire world."

Han Xiao let out a deep breath.

He had heard of the Stuarts Award, but something so high class, of course, had nothing to do with the players in his previous life.

If I win the Stuarts Peace Prize of this year, it'll probably be another Universe Legendary Point. The dynasty really isn't holding back on promoting me.

Han Xiao chuckled in his mind. He was very satisfied with how the three Universal Civilizations promoted him.

With so many honors gifted to him, they could be seen as a defensive aura that could deflect damage. If anyone attacked him, that person would certainly become a public enemy and lose a lot of reputation. Even if the federation and the church wanted to do something to him again, they would have to first dirty his image, otherwise even they would have to think twice about if the reputation drop was worth it.

Beep beep…

At this time, he received a communication request.

Han Xiao looked at it, and to his surprise, it was a call from Ames.

As he picked it up, the projection of the beautiful Ames, who was wearing a black dress, appeared before him. Her arms were crossed, and her lips were slightly lifted.

"I saw the video. You copied me."

"Haha, just suddenly thought of it."

"Looks like you paid attention to what I said." Ames narrowed her eyes with overflowing happiness in them. Clearly, she was in a very good mood.

"I remember most of the things you said."

"You really are getting better at talking…" Ames then chuckled softly and said, "I'm not doing anything at home. Have time to visit me?"

"Missed me?"

"Are you coming or not?" Ames slightly raised her brows.

"You've already invited me. How can I possibly not go? Wait for me to arrange my schedule. It's on the way too."

"Hmm, I'll wait for you at home."

Ames stepped forward and raised her hand to touch Han Xiao's cheeks. Sadly, it was just a projection. She then smiled and ended the communication as her projection disappeared.

Han Xiao touched his face and shook his head with a smile.

"It's not good to go empty-handed. I should take some gifts…"

It just so happened that the three Universal Civilizations had opened up more resources to him, so he could acquire an Esper Ultimate Knowledge and give it to Ames.

He could then give it to Hila afterward too, killing two birds with one stone.

Also, he had something he had to ask Aesop too. Maybe that knowledgeable old man knew something about the Sanctum, Holy Accord, Oathkeeper, or Manison.

Furthermore, Han Xiao had a feeling.

He felt that if he went to see Ames now, he might receive something surprising.

While thinking of that, Han Xiao looked outside the window, and Harrison just happened to walk by.

Chapter 1127: Prophecy

Dark blue tail flames extended from the deep cosmic space and brought light to the dark universe. The trail stopped at the dock of the Floating Dragon Island, which was orbiting Planet Aquamarine.

Although they had a lazy leader, Floating Dragon still expanded to having five islands and close to a hundred million residents. Most came from Planet Aquamarine. Staying on Planet Aquamarine's surface meant they had to be ruled by the Aquamarine Federation, but Floating Dragon was a neutral island with no regime, so it was freer. Plus, they could experience galactic society while still being close to their home, so it was a good holiday destination, which was why the tourism industry of Floating Dragon was booming.

The Black Star Army fleet parked on the main dock and immediately attracted the attention of countless people. When Han Xiao walked out from the cabin with a group of subordinates in the Black Star Army uniform, people instantly swarmed over with excitement.

"It really is Black Star!"

"You make us proud!"

"Can you give me an autograph? My grandfather loves you!"

Han Xiao was surrounded by the crowd and could hardly move.

Hearing the noisy yells and feeling the passion from everyone, Han Xiao used his classic smile, which was quite effective and made the crowd even more thrilled.

Most of the people there were born on Planet Aquamarine. They were taught about Black Star from a young age and were almost all admirers of Black Star. Lately, due to the three Universal Civilizations' promotion, his reputation had become extremely positive. He was almost worshipped by Planet Aquamarine's people as an almighty God.

This time, the Floating Dragon soldiers who had been waiting for quite some time walked over, split up the crowd, and opened a path.

Jenny approached with an expressionless face. She then said in a tone that completely lacked any emotion or sincerity, "Welcome to Floating Dragon, Your Excellency Black Star."

"You don't sound like I'm that welcomed," Han Xiao joked.

"No, I'm thrilled." With her eyes opened wide, she moved aside and made a 'please' gesture. "Follow me."

The two of them left with their subordinates, leaving the crowd on the dock watching them disappear in their sights. Quite a number of people shot knowing looks at each other.

Gossip about Black Star and Ames had been passing around in the Shattered Star Ring for decades, and that was even more so on Planet Aquamarine. Almost everyone knew about it.

There was a reason it started in the first place. Black Star frequently visited Floating Dragon, and Dragon Emperor moved her base to Black Star's home planet. If someone were to say there was nothing between the two of them, not a single person from Planet Aquamarine would believe it.

Han Xiao and Jenny walked at the front and led the others through one street after another, receiving thrilled looks from countless passersby and chatting here and there.

Han Xiao glanced at her. "You seem to be in a good mood today."

"Why do you say so?" Jenny wondered.

"Your attitude to me isn't as bad as before."

"…Humph." Jenny snorted softly. "If you liked it, I can go back to that."

She had never liked Black Star, partly because he gave her tons of work and partly because of Ames. However, after watching the recent news, although Jenny never mentioned it, she actually did admire Black Star somewhat. If she continued to be so cold to Black Star, she would not feel good about it.

"Tsk." Han Xiao shook his head. "I liked you more when you were defiant."

Jenny secretly rolled her eyes and did not bother responding to Han Xiao.

At this time, they arrived at a junction and heard the sound of dense footsteps, as well as the clear and loud sound of metal rubbing against metal.

They looked over and saw a group of Floating Dragon warriors in dark gold heavy armor pushing several creatures from different races that had their heads covered in black cloth. They hastily passed by on the street not far away from them.

The pedestrians around quickly stepped out of their way like they were horrified.

These warriors were covered by armor from head to toe, including their faces. They gave off a cold-blooded merciless vibe while walking. There were two symbols on their chest armor. One was Floating Dragon's symbol, and the other was a symbol Han Xiao had never seen before.

"Who are those people? I don't recall seeing them the last time I was here." Han Xiao was curious.

"They're the Hunters. They recently split from Wilsander's law enforcement team and became an independent division," Jenny explained briefly.

Harrison saw that the creatures that were being escorted had dried blood marks on their clothes, so he asked, "What are they going to do to those people?"

As soon as he asked that, Han Xiao and Jenny both turned and glanced at him with a strange expression.

"Wh—What?" Harrison was a little terrified and nervous from being looked at by the two of them.

Jenny did not bother about him but looked at Han Xiao. "Black Star, where did you get this newbie from again? He doesn't seem to know when to speak."

"Don't say that. Harrison is a great kid. He's helped me a lot." Han Xiao did not mind it and smiled. "I like it when you're being mean. It just feels right."

"Humph." Jenny sized Harrison up, waved her hand, and said, "Since you're so curious, why don't we go and take a look? It's not that far anyway."

"Er… can we?" Harrison looked at Han Xiao.

"Go take a look then." Han Xiao nodded. Although he was Harrison's boss now, he would still try to satisfy the tiny requests of someone with Advanced Luck Glow.

The group of them followed after the Hunters and came to the edge of Floating Dragon Island. The translucent light gold protective shield separated them from the vacuum of space right outside.

A large crowd had already formed around, but the Hunters did not mind it at all. They did not chase the bystanders away and focused on their tasks. They lined up the people blinded by black cloth in a row and made them kneel down. They then opened up a small part of the light gold protective shield.

As an opening was created on the gold shield, the group of people who had no armor got sucked out instantly. They were exposed to the cosmic space and started to struggle in agony, like fish jumping around on the cutting board.

Very soon, these people struggled less and less. A layer of white snow appeared on all of them, and their bodily functions were destroyed by the vacuum. Their faces were hidden under the black cloth, or their twisted facial expressions would have shown as well.

The next moment, the Hunters raised the firearms in their hands and fired simultaneously.

Green beams shot out from their guns, shattering those people who were about to turn into ice sculptures into pieces that drifted out into cosmic space.

"Is this an execution?" Harrison opened his eyes wide. "What crime did they commit? Isn't this too cruel?"

Although he had never come to the Shattered Star Ring, he did some slight research about Floating Dragon when he heard their schedule had changed.

As the Black Star Army's galactic pirate happy little house was too famous, the galactic pirates in the Shattered Star Ring all transferred their business elsewhere. Floating Dragon, too, stopped letting galactic pirates in. This place had become an orderly safe and free city.

He had expected the atmosphere in Floating Dragon to be very positive, but to his surprise, Floating Dragon shockingly carried out death sentences right before countless spectators. This was not something that would happen in an orderly city at all. Furthermore, open execution was a special trait of places that were ruled by terror. He did not expect to see something so violent here at all.

"Cruel? Look around you," Jenny said with a displeased tone. "Which one of them thinks it's cruel?"

Harrison turned and looked around. To his absolute shock, all the people around looked happy, and some were even clapping.

Jenny looked at Han Xiao and snorted. "One's enemies increase with one's fame. In recent years, there have been multiple infiltration cases on Planet Aquamarine. These culprits are spies and rebels of different organizations. They have advanced technology, and their goal is to infiltrate Planet Aquamarine, through messing up your mother planet, causing damage to you… Some had their eyes on Floating Dragon and attempted to build secret strongholds here or make use of the geographical location of Floating Dragon to launch destructive weapons at Planet Aquamarine. Hence, we formed the Hunters, who exclusively clear out these spies… Black Star, we've helped you block quite a lot of pressure."

Hearing this, Harrison finally understood. Most people around were from Planet Aquamarine. No wonder they were so glad. These people were criminals who were planning to attack their mother planet, so not only was publicly executing them not cruel but even beneficial to making the people feel assured.

"Thanks." Han Xiao smiled. Ames had moved Floating Dragon there because she wanted to help him stop these evil people.

"Just a thanks?"

Han Xiao thought for a moment and said, "I'll bring you some special magic potions that stimulate hair growth for you next time as a present then."

"… Go find Ames yourself!" Jenny's face turned green. She suppressed her impulse of yelling at Han Xiao right on the spot and left straight away.

Seeing this, confused, Harrison mumbled on the side, "Your Excellency Black Star, you stand at the top of the universe. Why is this woman so disrespectful toward you?"

"I've known her for decades, and we've always been like this. There's no point making the difference in positions so clear between friends." Han Xiao waved.

"I see, you're really generous…" Harrison praised Han Xiao subtly and asked, "What's her name then?"

"You don't know? Jenny is the Chief Administrator of Floating Dragon. She's the Dragon Emperor's sister and good friend. You should know that from your internet research."

"I didn't go to so much detail… but I see, her name is Jenny. I think she's quite pretty…"

"… When did you go blind?" Han Xiao suddenly stopped in place, sized him up, and said with a surprised tone, "Have you fallen in love with her?"

Harrison slightly blushed and reluctantly said, "I wouldn't call it love. I've only met her once, after all…"

"Oh, got it, you lust for her body."

Harrison was speechless and did not know what to say.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. He did not know much about Jenny's private life in his previous life, but he knew that Harrison remained single all the way till he sacrificed himself during the World Tree Civilization war.

Although Jenny might be more than a hundred years older than Harrison, she maintained herself very well and looked like she was just thirty.

Furthermore, age was just a number; love was what mattered. This was a win-win.

This might work out!

Having thought of that, Han Xiao patted Harrison's shoulder and giggled.

"Go for it if you like her. I'll be your shield. Quickly conquer her and adjust her personality. I don't mind her personality because we're old friends, but with the way she is, she'll definitely get beaten up often if she ever goes out."

Harrison blushed even more. "What should I do? I have no experience…"

"Hmm? You're the second-generation owner of a big financial group, but you have never been in a relationship?"

"I liked reading books more back then…"

"Shameful!" Han Xiao was hurt. "You've wasted being born with a silver spoon!"

While the two of them chatted about nonsense, they arrived before Ames' palace. Han Xiao told Harrison and the rest of his subordinates to wait at the stronghold while he tidied up his clothes and stepped into Ames' palace.

He walked all the way to the garden filled with rare greenery. Ames was lying sideways on the long bed in the middle of the garden. Her black dress looked like a blossoming black flower. She was using her force field to play with the revive token that Hila had given to her by making it fly around the garden. The table beside her was filled with food and drinks.

Hearing footsteps, Ames retrieved the coin, turned to look at Han Xiao, smiled, and patted on the mattress.

"You're here. Quick, come and sit. I've waited a long time for you."

Han Xiao walked forward, grabbed a crystal blue wine glass on the way that was filled with wine, sat at the edge of the mattress, and took a sip. "Old Man Aesop made this again?"

As soon as he said that, he felt a pair of white arms above his shoulders.

Ames placed her chin on his shoulders from behind and asked curiously, "What did you do in the Ancient Star Desert? The news has little detail. I want to hear it from you."

Han Xiao was not surprised by her intimate actions. During the trip to the secondary dimensions, the two of them had spent months with each other alone. Their relationship had become much closer. Although Ames hated to have any physical contact with others, he was an exception.

"Forget that for now. I've brought you a present."

Han Xiao snapped his fingers. A virtual screen popped up and displayed a list of the Esper class Ultimate Knowledges.

"The three Universal Civilizations have allowed me to acquire Ultimate Knowledges and teach them to others, but there's a limit. Pick one you want. I'll get it for you."

"So nice?" Ames blinked. "Let me guess, you're not just giving this to me exclusively. You'll also teach this knowledge to other Espers, such as Hila, right?"

"Of course." Han Xiao nodded.

"Now that sounds like you more," Ames smirked slightly. She looked at the screen and pointed at one item with her long finger.

Han Xiao glanced at it. "This doesn't seem like the most suitable one for you."

"Didn't you say there's a limit to the number of knowledges you can exchange? Never mind me, as long as it's suitable for Hila and Aurora." Ames smiled.

"You're too concerned about them." Han Xiao sighed.

"They're my only students. They're like my children. Who else will I care for if not them?" Ames casually slammed Han Xiao's chest, making a loud 'bang' sound like beating on a drum. "Quick, tell me stories. I want to hear them."

Han Xiao finished up the wine. He casually picked up the crystal blue fruits on the table and tossed them in his mouth. He then started to talk about every detail of his experience in the Ancient Star Desert.

After telling stories for more than half a day, Ames finally let Han Xiao go with satisfaction and made him promise to continue tomorrow.

Han Xiao left the palace and was about to look for Aesop, but Aesop had already surprisingly come looking for him at the army stronghold.

Han Xiao returned to the stronghold and saw Aesop sitting in the hall right away, accompanied by Harrison and the others.

"Old man, I was just about to look for you. Did you foresee something again, so you came to find me?"

Han Xiao sat opposite Aesop and joked with him.

"Stop messing around. I'm here to speak about something serious with you today." Aesop put down the glass in his hands. His tone was rather serious.

"How rare." Han Xiao was a little curious. "What do you want to speak with me about?"

"Lately, my passive foresight has been triggering very frequently. I think it's better to tell you some of the things."

Aesop raised one finger and said with a deep voice, "First, I saw a special existence landing on Planet Aquamarine, and I've seen his appearance clearly."

"Since you know what he looks like, why not just go tell Bennett and let him cross-reference it with the planet surveillance to find this person?"

"That's the problem…" Aesop frowned. "I've looked all over Planet Aquamarine. There's no record of this person anywhere. There are no witness reports of this person too… It's like this person doesn't exist."

"Is your prophecy wrong?"

"No, I've never felt as strongly about a prophecy. I can't exactly explain why, but I can say with full certainty that this prophecy is reliable."

"Then what else is special about this person you saw?"

Hearing this, Aesop glanced at Han Xiao.

"According to my prophecy… you seem to have already crossed paths with him very long ago."

Chapter 1128: No Such Person Found

"Crossed paths? Show me what he looks like."

Han Xiao was curious.

Aesop took out the communicator and showed a 3D portrait.

This was a pale-skinned man who looked like he was from Planet Aquamarine. Han Xiao sized him up for quite some time but did not seem to find this person in his memories.

"That's weird, I've never seen this person before. Anyway, I'll let people look for this person on Planet Aquamarine."

Since he was part of Aesop's prophecy, this person was definitely involved in something important. He did not know if it was a good thing or not that this person had arrived on Planet Aquamarine. After all, Planet Aquamarine was his mother planet, so he had to worry about its safety.

"What you just said was the first thing. What's the second?"

"I've foreseen history repeating itself." Aesop frowned slightly, a little confused.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. "You're saying…"

"In my visions, many people who died long ago reappeared in the world. I even saw some of the Primordial Ones."

Could it be the event of the Holy Accord reviving Beyond Grade As? If Aesop felt this future too, then the trigger of that would most likely be his deal with Oathkeeper.

"Hmm? You don't seem surprised about this prophecy?" Aesop wondered.

"I have some knowledge about this." Han Xiao rubbed his chin and asked, "By the way, do you know about…"

He briefly asked Aesop about the Holy Accord, Oathkeeper, the Sanctums, and all those related matters, hoping that an Eternal like Aesop who traveled around would know something others did not.

Sadly, Aesop shook his head and expressed that he had not heard about those things.

However, when mentioning Oathkeeper, he seemed to recall something.

"This higher dimension spiritual projection ability that completely ignores distance you've mentioned is not common. It might sound easy, but it's extremely difficult to do. Most spirit-related Esper and Psychics Abilities won't be able to achieve it. If this is not his own Esper Ability, then it's quite similar to a legendary Primal Esper Ability Entity—Soul Flame."

Having heard the term Primal Esper Ability, Han Xiao knew this was probably the case, so he asked, "What else do you know?"

"Soul Flame is one of the Super High Risk Esper Abilities. There have been no witness reports of it for many years… Oh, but you should already know that, so I won't go over that. Tell you something you don't know, in my early years wandering the universe, I seem to recall that I once had a prophecy. That prophecy warned me that if I did this one thing, a person who used the Soul Flame would suddenly appear and try to control me, making me help him search for something. Hence, thanks to that prophecy, I avoided that thing and stopped it from happening. That guy might be the Oathkeeper you spoke of, and this is the only information I have about him."

After communication for a while, Han Xiao realized that this was all Aesop knew about Oathkeeper, so he stopped asking him and remembered the name 'Soul Flame'. He planned to go back and ask the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and Holy Light Particle. They were both members of the Primal Esper Ability family, so they might know more.

Furthermore, Primal Esper Ability Entities had existed for a very long time. If the two of them knew whose hands Soul Flame last ended up in, he might find out more about the Holy Accord organization.

"Since you have some knowledge about this, I won't say too much." Aesop pointed a third finger and said with a serious tone, "There's one last prophecy. I saw that a universal-level disaster is now brewing somewhere we can't see."

"Are you talking about the Intelligent Plague? Then your prophecy might have expired."

"Do I look like I'm kidding?" Aesop asked. "I saw wormholes that were millions of miles large opening in cosmic space one after another, countless fleets swarming out from within, and the occurrence of a galactic war comparable to the exploration era. No one will be able to avoid it."

Han Xiao's eyes turned solemn.

That sounds like the invasion of the World Tree Civilization.

Prophecies occurred for a reason. There were definitely some causes or changes that caused Aesop to have this prophecy. This meant that the World Tree storyline had progressed.

Han Xiao immediately thought of the wormhole coordinates from the past, which was outrageously difficult to pin down and required absolute accuracy.

He had made limited progress, so was the dynasty able to find something?

Looks like I'll have to find the time to ask around about it. Back when EsGod accidentally obtained the wormhole coordinates, I already knew that the World Tree storyline would change… Han Xiao shook his head.

Aesop stood up, stretched his waist, and casually said, "I've delivered the prophecies to you, so I'll leave the rest to you. I'll also notify you if there are any new prophecies."

He deliberately told these prophecies to Han Xiao but not Ames because it would not make a difference even if Ames knew; she would only see it as a story. Only Black Star would do something about it.

Han Xiao was about to send Aesop out the door, but Aesop waved and told him there was no need to. However, he suddenly stopped at the doorstep, as if he had thought of something, turned around, and said, "By the way, I've got to tell you something. While I was waiting for you, I did some prophecies on your subordinates to kill time. This kid called Harrison has quite a bright future. His string of fate is very thick, and it's deviated from its original path."

Then, Aesop opened the door and left. Han Xiao turned to look at Harrison, who was completely at a loss. Han Xiao was not surprised.

He had dragged Harrison with him, so of course, his string of fate had deviated. The World Tree war would very likely erupt earlier, and it was uncertain if Harrison would sacrifice himself like he did in Han Xiao's previous life.

Han Xiao committed the three prophecies to memory. Although they were all quite blurry, Aesop did indirectly provide some key information to him, so he had more clues.

Currently, the best thing to do was to look for that person Aesop spoke of first. Han Xiao gave the portrait of the target to Phillip and told him to monitor the entire planet. He then summoned the Black Star Army members who were stationed on Planet Aquamarine and sent them out to search all over the planet.

With his power on Planet Aquamarine, he could find even a tiny mouse if he wanted to, not to mention a person.

…

My name is Rody Anchor, 48 years old, a citizen of Ice Forest City, Maple County, Planet Aquamarine. My house is on No.107 Morning Light Street, Block B 1511. My ID is 77054591A62H. I'm currently working at the Fero Organization Subdivision three streets away. I'm the vice-manager of the operation department.

My parents are survivors of the old era. They died during a riot caused by the Mutation Disaster. Back then, I was just an ignorant child. The disaster caused the majority of the city's residents to flee. The shops were robbed clean, and burnt cars were everywhere on the roads. I lived a few weeks in a waste of a city like this and was finally found by the Black Star Army's rescue team. Thanks to that, I was brought to life in the Sanctuary.

After that, His Excellency Black Star got rid of the Mutation Disaster, and I was sent to Public Orphanage No.87. After receiving therapy from Ms. Martha for six years, I finally got over my childhood trauma. My social anxiety, depression, and other illnesses were cured.

After that, my life felt like it was fast-forwarding. Went to school, graduated, entered society, participated in rebuilding Planet Aquamarine, kept changing jobs, kept moving houses, had one girlfriend after another, experienced two failed marriages… The tides of the fast-developing times dragged me along with its extremely quick pace. Like everyone in the same era as me, I worked hard to contribute to society and the new era. With my very own eyes, I witnessed the unbelievably quick development progress of Planet Aquamarine after it connected with the galactic society.

However, as I grew older, my ambition started to shrink. Instead, I started to miss my parents more and more. Five years ago, I decided to quit my job in a large company in Black Star City and returned to my parents' home, Ice Forest City.

My home city had finished being rebuilt. I bought a house in this city, found a new job, and started living here.

The new job is very relaxing. The intensely competitive environment I experienced in the capital does not exist here. Life is like a quiet lake. I meet the same people every day. I'm old now, and I have noticed I've grown a liking for a slow life. Very quickly, I fell in love with this peaceful life.

Galaxy Calendar Year 731 July 16th, I can still vividly recall that sunny morning. I woke up early and washed up, as usual, preparing to take out the leftover dinner from the previous day and heat it up as breakfast.

However, when I was brushing my teeth, I suddenly realized that I could not see myself in the mirror!

Horror gripped my heart. I had no idea what happened. I cowered in the corner of the washroom and looked around anxiously as if a monster was going to jump out any minute. I spent more than a minute in that state, shivering in the corner. Then, I finally found the courage to sprint out of the washroom. Without even having the guts to put my shoes on, I hastily grabbed my keys and rushed out of my house, pressing the elevator button rapidly like a mad man.

I lived in a condominium that's thirty-three floors high. It had four elevators. At the morning peak period, the elevators always automatically went up to the top floor before slowly descending, stopping on almost every floor. Usually, I would watch the morning news while waiting for the elevator, but seconds felt like years at that time. I almost wanted to pry the elevator door open and pull the elevator down.

Finally, the lift arrived at where I lived, floor fifteen. The door opened, and it was completely filled with people. Usually, when I came across something like this, I would always greet my neighbors inside with a smile and wait for the next lift. However, I completely threw all that aside at that time. I grabbed onto the door and screamed at them, describing what had just happened to me.

However, I quickly realized no one was looking at me. No one was listening to me. It was as if I did not exist!

As I was drowning in panic and fear, the people inside noticed that the lift door was not closing, so the person standing by the buttons rapidly pressed on the closing button impatiently. Someone even reached out and tried to slap the door, and that person's hand just happened to land on my arm.

Something happened that made me even more horrified—this person's hand easily passed through my arm like I was just an illusion.

Before my brain could even react to it, my sight started to ripple, and I saw an illusion. A lady in the lift did not hold on to the communicator in her hand properly, and it dropped onto the floor.

At this instant, an immense pain erupted in my body. I lost control of my body, fell onto the floor, and started twitching all over. My sight quickly turned blurry, and a powerful sense of drowsiness rushed up to my brain.

The moment before I passed out, I faintly saw a communicator that was exactly the same as the one I saw in the illusion earlier, and I saw it drop onto the floor inside the lift.

The next second, I lost consciousness.

When I woke up again, it was already night, and I was still lying on the floor outside the lift. A sense of overwhelming weakness pervaded my body as if I hadn't eaten or slept for two whole days.

The extremely strong sense of hunger seemed to have chased away my fear. I dragged myself back home and ate up almost everything in my fridge, finally regaining some strength. During which, I tried using the metal cutlery and the camera to see my reflection, but everything failed without exception.

After that, I tried my best and barely calmed down. After multiple tests, I've realized that I'm non-existence to everyone, and I can't touch anyone either. However, I can influence some objects that are not in contact with any form of life.

Therefore, I tried driving, stealing, creating accidents, and so on. Most of my actions that will have a direct influence on others will be interrupted by me suddenly passing out. However, many of my attempts at stealing worked, and no one noticed. It's only thanks to that was I able to live till now, or I would've starved to death long ago.

The illusion that causes me to faint happens frequently. I've realized that I seem to be able to see a certain period of time into the future, but I can't activate or deactivate that power. When this power activates, I faint and feel weak after. I'm guessing that the cost of using this power is my stamina.

I thought of the Mutation Disaster. My body has definitely gone through some kind of terrifying mutation.

I've lived for about three months in this state. Initially, I was terrified, but then, for some time, I felt happy, and after that, I felt lost and alone. I can't interact with people in real life, so I tried communicating with people online.

However, no matter what method I use to leave a message, it all still seems to get ignored by others. I've sent messages to my friends, but I never get a reply. No one from my company has even called to ask why I haven't been going to work. It's like everyone has lived with the fact that I've just simply evaporated. I don't understand why.

Therefore, I've written this diary, hoping that someone sees it and comes to help me. My address is Maple County, Ice Forest City, No.107 Morning Light Street, Block B 1511. I'll be waiting at home for you.

Planet Aquamarine Public Announcement Channel, post 'Help! I've disappeared!'

Views: 0

…

One day later, on Floating Dragon Island…

"No such person has been found?"

Han Xiao received the search report from Phillip and the various army members, frowning.

"Master, hum… Not only are there no traces of this person in the surveillance footage, I even crossed referenced the photo with all ID photos of the residents registered in the Aquamarine Federation. Still, no match found."

"We've scanned the entire planet using all kinds of vital sign detection devices, including every spot, and we could not find the target either," the army warrior who was in charge of the field search said. "Is this person really on Planet Aquamarine?"

Han Xiao tapped on the table, turned to Harrison, and asked, "What do you think?"

"Me?" Harrison pointed at himself with surprise and said with some hesitance, "How about we make a search notice?"

"Alright." Han Xiao nodded. Initially, he did not know anything about this person in Aesop's prophecy, so he did not want to alert him. However, since they could not find him now, making it public would not hurt. Anyway, he was right there, so he was not worried about anyone causing any problems.

He had to see what connection he had with this stranger.

Chapter 1129: High Dimensional Information Form

Four days passed very quickly, but the search notice sent through the Aquamarine Federation's official news did not receive any response. Either no one saw the target, or the target saw it but decided not to come. There were also no witnesses.

Left with no choice, Han Xiao could only have his subordinates continue searching. He also used [Bold Explorer] on the portrait Aesop had provided, only to see some images, but he had no idea what they were supposed to represent—a bunch of string crossing cosmic space.

After another round of searching, spaceships returned to the Floating Dragon's dock one after another. Many Black Star Army members walked out the hatch unhappily.

After searching for so many days and still not finding the target, continuously repeating a task that had a 'result' long ago would make anyone frustrated and annoyed. The army warriors were not exceptions.

Harrison was in the crowd too. Suddenly, he caught sight of Jenny. His heart skipped a beat. He hesitated for a moment, walked over, and found the courage to finally speak with her.

"Jenny, I'm Harrison. We meet again."

Jenny was dealing with a group of financial group investors. Hearing someone call her name, she turned, casually nodded, and said, "It's you. What is it?"

A few days ago, Han Xiao and Ames had hosted a small party that all the important officers attended. Han Xiao had introduced Harrison to her back then, but she did not have a very good impression of him. She only remembered that this was a talkative, curious, and immature kid.

"Ca-can I speak with you?" Harrison stuttered.

"Now?" Jenny frowned slightly, waved, and said in a displeased tone, "I'm very busy now. Can't you see I have guests to attend to?"

Then, she looked away from Harrison and left with the investors. She was distant and cold.

Harrison opened his mouth but did not dare disturb her more. Dejected, he followed the others and headed to Dragon Emperor's palace to report to Han Xiao.

However, when he was about to leave the dock, he suddenly saw that someone was lying on the floor not far away. This person's clothes were ragged, and Harrison could not see his face. The pedestrians around did not notice him, as if they could not see him.

"That's odd. Is that person sleeping on the floor? Why isn't anyone doing anything about it?"

Harrison was curious.

The Black Star Army warrior beside him heard his question and looked over in the direction he was looking. He then said with a confused tone, "Where?"

"Right there… can't you see?" Harrison was stunned.

The army warriors around all stopped and looked over. They stared in that direction for a few seconds before turning around and looking at Harrison with the same weird expression.

"Buddy, better go have your eyes looked at."

Harrison was lost. His overflowing curiosity instantly started burning. He left the crowd and quickly approached the person lying on the floor. He hesitated for a moment before giving this person a light push.

"Wake up."

This person did not react at all as if he had fainted.

Unable to hold back his curiosity, Harrison turned this person over.

The instant he saw the look of this person, his eyes widened with shock.

"You're saying that… this is the person we're looking for?"

Half an hour later, Han Xiao rushed back to the base from the Dragon Emperor's palace, came to a secret interrogation room, and looked across the table with a strange expression.

"Yes, I found him on the dock. He seems to have fainted and still hasn't woken up." Harrison stood by the side and pointed at the seat on the other side of the table.

Han Xiao looked at the empty seat with a frown. He then said with a serious tone, "You're not pulling my leg, are you? There's no one here."

Harrison scratched his head and said with a confused tone, "I don't understand why either. It seems like I'm the only person who can see him, and no one else can. But I can assure you, he looks exactly the same as the target we're looking for."

"Where did you find him?" Han Xiao wondered.

"You might not believe me but…" Harrison shrunk his neck and said, "I picked him up on the streets."

"…"

Han Xiao was speechless.

What else can I say?

If not because Harrison happened to see this person, even if he was standing right in front of me, I would not have seen him.

No wonder you became an explorer. This is what talent is, able to find good stuff anywhere you go!

Doubtful, Han Xiao pondered for a moment and sent a message to Aesop and asked him to come over. Then, he told Harrison to describe what this person looked like.

Harrison took a step forward and looked down at what seemed to be empty space in Han Xiao's eyes. "He looks very weak. He's so skinny that there's basically only skin and bones. His clothes are ragged and torn, and there's a lot of dust on his body like he hasn't cleaned himself for many days…"

Han Xiao told Phillip to draw out the appearance of this person according to Harrison. In comparison, what he described was much thinner than the portrait Aesop provided. One would not even be able to tell they were the same person if the two portraits were not placed side by side.

Aesop soon arrived. As soon as he entered, he looked at the empty seat, smiled, and said, "You guys are quite efficient to have found him this soon."

Han Xiao was frustrated.

Why am I the only one who can't see him? How does this even work?

If not because he knew Harrison's personality, he might have thought that these two were working together to trick him.

Thinking of that, Han Xiao reached out and waved at the space in front of him. He could not sense that he had touched anything at all.

"Army Commander, your hand passed through his body…" While Harrison was explaining, he suddenly said with surprise, "Wait, he's suddenly twitching, like you're electrocuting him."

"Quickly wake him up."

Han Xiao pulled his hands back, frowned, and brought up the surveillance footage of the room. He realized that no type of detection device could detect the existence of this person.

Clearly, he was not simply invisible. It seemed like only some people were able to see and touch this person.

What similarities did Aesop and Harrison have? If he really had to say, it seemed like both of them were quite lucky… Could it be that only those whose Luck was high enough could see this guy‽

Then I'd better wash up and go to sleep.

While he was making guesses, Harrison suddenly yelled, "He's awake!"

Han Xiao regained focus and forced himself to talk to the seat. "Tell me who you are."

The atmosphere became silent. Han Xiao did not receive a response even after a few seconds, but he did see Harrison and Aesop listening closely to something.

"Did he speak? Looks like I can't hear him either." Han Xiao sighed. "Tell me, what did he say?"

Harrison scratched his head and repeated, "He said his name is Rody Anchor, born on Planet Aquamarine…"

Hearing this, Han Xiao quickly connected to the Aquamarine Federation's database and did a precise search of documents under this name. However, the result was still that no such person existed.

"Now this doesn't make sense at all. Since he's a resident of Planet Aquamarine, there's no way there aren't any documents at all about him. Either they were wiped by some kind of abnormal power, or something is stopping me from finding out his identity. Could it be that anyone who can't see him won't be able to find out any information about him in any form? But I can still hear what Harrison is saying about him…"

Han Xiao searched through his memories. Suddenly, he thought of a special form of existence.

This situation looked like the traits of a High Dimensional Information Form!

The explored universe had limited knowledge of the term 'information form'. Their theories remained unproven and unclear. It was said that any and all individuals carried various forms of information such as height, weight, smell, mass, and so on. These forms of information fused into the conditions that made the individuals detectable.

'High Dimensional Information Form' represented a specific form of existence, where physical attributes of something were removed and only the 'concept' of this information was left. These 'concepts' formed a certain kind of existence, similar to physical life forms, energy life forms, and so on, becoming a new form of existence… Whether it existed or not depended on the observer.

To those special groups of people who could sense and observe this cluster of information, it would be something that had a physical form and could be touched. However, to those who could not observe it, they could not obtain any information on High Dimensional Information Forms through any channels, as if it did not exist. Like spirits that roamed the world, they would not be able to have any information exchange with each other. There were many names for this phenomenon, such as 'Information Closure', 'Information Isolation', and 'Unobservable Entity'.

At the same time, 'Information Closure' was not limited to the senses of life forms. It was also effective on technological and magical methods of observations. This was why some documents that were supposed to exist could not be found.

This was because, including Virtual Technology, all these detection devices were also carriers of information, tools to obtain and save information. At their roots, they were no different from life forms using their organs to sense the world. 'Information Closure' worked on both life forms and these tools… This was also the reason it had the 'High Dimensional' prefix.

However, after those people who could observe High Dimensional Information Forms obtained the information, the information they obtained would become their own information, so they could describe the existence of High Dimensional Information Forms to others. This was the only form of information flow. However, even if others obtained this information, they would still not be able to sense the High Dimensional Information Forms.

Looks like he's still not a complete High Dimensional Information Form, or he would not have to consume food…

His situation feels like he's only half transformed, causing the information he carries to mutate and his 'existence' to be wiped. However, he has yet to completely become a High Dimensional Information Form, which is why he can still interact with some objects… These traits are more similar to him awakening a related Esper Ability but temporarily being unable to control it.

Why would a totally normal person suddenly become like this?

There has to be a cause, and maybe that's why Aesop saw him in his prophecy!

Han Xiao tapped the table and said with a deep voice, "Tell him to tell me everything that happened."

For now, the only thing he could do was have Harrison and Aesop relay Rody's situation. Han Xiao understood the situation very quickly and explained what had happened to this person with the Information Form Theory.

This person's name was Rody Anchor. He had always lived on Planet Aquamarine. Some time ago, he mutated and gained some traits of a High Dimensional Information Form. He tried to communicate with others in many ways, but everything failed, so he had no choice but to do nothing for a few months.

A few days ago, he had seen the search notice that the Black Star Army had put up. Overjoyed, he had sent countless messages to the army's mailbox but never received any replies. He had no choice but to board a spaceship and come to Floating Dragon, hoping to find Han Xiao.

Every time a life form passed through his Semi High Dimensional Information Form body, he would passively read part of the information of that life form, bringing the illusions that felt like foresight, which led to him fainting. With his current body, if he wanted to do anything to someone, it would be equivalent to him trying to rewrite someone else's 'form of existence' on the information level, interfering with reality using information state disturbance, which required more energy than he could afford. Hence, he would faint halfway every time. It was a self-protection mechanism.

Therefore, he dodged all passersby on the way there. However, when he arrived at the Floating Dragon's dock, even without coming into contact with anyone, he suddenly had foresight visions again, so he passed out. This was how he appeared in Floating Dragon and was coincidentally discovered by Harrison.

Han Xiao captured the key information and pondered.

"He awakened foresight… Maybe his information form mutation came from his sudden ability to see the future?"

"Maybe," Aesop said with a deep voice. "The ability to see the future can be seen as the ability to sense, process, and deduce information. The terms us foreseers use are strings of fate, cause and effect, and so on. This is because foresight ability requires one to connect with a lot of strings of fate, so it's not impossible for it to cause someone to undergo Information Form mutation."

Now, this is the blindspot of my knowledge… Han Xiao had a slight headache. "Old man, your prophecy says I crossed paths with him long ago. Is this referring to me saving his life because I resolved the Mutation Disaster?"

According to Rody's past, Han Xiao thought of this possibility.

"How would I know?" Aesop shrugged. "If prophecies were that accurate, do you think I'd have been caught by you in the past?"

Han Xiao was hesitant.

He did have an idea regarding how to find out what was going on with Rody, which was to activate the combat information, but he first had to be able to touch this person.

In order for a normal person to observe a High Dimensional Information Form, it looks like one has to have a strong information connection with the target… He seems to be able to touch dead objects. So, it's not as impossible as real High Dimensional Information Forms… Hmm, I can't see the clothes he's wearing either, which means his clothes are assimilated too. Maybe I can start from there…

After some pondering, Han Xiao took out a mechanical suit, linked with it using Mechanical Force, and tried touching Rody.

However, Rody passed through it without any difficulty. Since this mechanical suit was connected with Han Xiao through Mechanical Force, it was like Han Xiao was touching it, so it could not touch Rody.

Han Xiao then deactivated the Mechanical Force link and let Rody try to touch it again, but it still failed.

"Artificial intelligences are observers too," Aesop hinted.

Han Xiao then pulled out the artificial intelligence controlling the mechanical suit too. After several experiments, when all connections including the virtual links, fundamental authority, and everything else were removed, Rody finally successfully wore the mechanical suit.

The next moment, the mechanical suit disappeared right under Han Xiao's nose.

Seeing this, Han Xiao tried finding the mechanical suit using methods such as Mechanical Force, Virtual Technology, and so on, but everything failed. This mechanical suit just disappeared into thin air.

Then, Han Xiao told Rody to take off the mechanical suit, and it appeared on the floor again.

After running a few more tests, Han Xiao sighed and said, "He's basically an information black hole… I'm almost out of ideas."

Aesop crossed his arms, frowned, and asked, "Are there really no other ways?"

"It's too difficult to find a flaw." Han Xiao was a little frustrated.

Those who could not observe Rody had no way of creating any information link with him. Combat was a form of information exchange too, but even if he attacked him, he would probably still be completely unharmed.

He would only take damage from a weapon that was completely unaffected by any observer, a 'neutral' weapon.

If not because this guy can't influence any other life forms who aren't able to observe him, he'd be a terrifying infiltrator…

Han Xiao clenched his teeth, looked at Harrison, and gave it his last try.

"Ask him, does he have anything that he wants me to help him do?"

Harrison nodded, listened to Rody for a while, and said, "Your Excellency Black Star, he hopes you can help him to get out of this state."

The moment he said that, Han Xiao's heart skipped a beat.

A notification popped up on the interface.

You have triggered the mission [Destiny's Child—Sub-body Transformation]!

Mission Introduction: Rody Anchor, an ordinary man who lived an ordinary life, has undergone a unique mutation. He hopes you can help him to deal with this problem…

Mission Requirements: Solve Rody's mutation and find the root cause of it.

Reward: 2 Random Rewards, +80 Rody Favorability, 2 Character Summon Cards.

Before he could take a closer look at the mission, a skinny and weak middle-aged man appeared in Han Xiao's sights, sitting on his chair and looking at him with a face filled with hope.

It was indeed Rody, and he appeared all of a sudden.

It-it worked?

Han Xiao was surprised.

He did not have much hope initially and did not expect this method to really work.

Being able to see Rody meant that he now had an official information connection with him, and the source of that was definitely not just Rody's request.

Han Xiao was absolutely certain that if a mission was not triggered on the interface, even if he knew about Rody's request, he would still not have been able to see him.

Therefore, the interface became their connection!

However, this was not what shocked Han Xiao the most. It was the name of the mission.

Destiny's Child!

Isn't this one of the trump cards of the Germinal Organization in Version 1.0‽ Although I've never seen it, I once got his Character Summon Card.

How is this related to Destiny's Child? Isn't that guy dead‽

So, this is what Aesop meant when he said we crossed paths before!

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. Thousands of words were at the tip of his tongue, but they all became one word.

"…Damn!"

Chapter 1130: Questioning and Information

Shock and doubt appeared in his mind.

Decades had already passed, but Han Xiao still had vivid memories about it. He used to think Destiny's Child was just simply a Foreseer who ended up dead due to the Germinal Organization's explosion, turning into dust.

Now, however, it looked like Destiny's Child had more unknown secrets. Not only did it play an important role in Planet Aquamarine, but now it was related to the High Dimensional Information Forms.

Initially, he felt that having him, Hila, and Aurora, three outrageously talented members, was already the limit. To his absolute shock, Destiny's Child, who had died long ago, was not as simple as he thought! The Germinal Organization was filled with mad talent!

If the Germinal Organization leader suddenly revived and appeared right in front of him, he probably would not even be surprised.

What in the world is the Destiny's Child?

Han Xiao was stunned. He could not stop worrying without finding out the truth.

"… Army Commander?" Harrison suddenly prompted.

Han Xiao regained focus.

Aesop shook his head. He thought he understood why Han Xiao was silent and explained, "Even the three Universal Civilizations don't know much about the Information Form Theory, so I understand that this request might be too difficult for you."

Rody was instantly frustrated and said with despair, "Then what should I do? If even His Excellency Black Star can't help me, who can? Please, help me to convince His Excellency Black Star. I-I really don't know what to do!"

Hearing this, Han Xiao waved and said, "Don't worry, I'll try to help you."

"That's great. Thank you, Your Excel… Hmm‽" Rody showed appreciation subconsciously, but he was suddenly stunned halfway. He stared at Han Xiao with his eyes widened with shock.

Aesop and Harrison were startled too. They looked at Han Xiao with surprise.

"Army Commander, you can see him now‽"

"Hmm, I can."

"But earlier you… have you found a solution? But you didn't do anything!" Aesop could not understand why.

Han Xiao coughed and lied, "Real High Dimensional Information Forms can choose who can observe them. Maybe his strong will triggered that trait, so he actively created an information link with me… To put it simply, he removed me from his blacklist."

Harrison's eyes were filled with confusion.

How does that work?

Aesop thought about it for a while before accepting it. "That actually makes some sense. He might have inherited that trait, only he can't control it freely, but subconsciously, he might be able to…"

Han Xiao looked at him with a smile and supported the old man in his mind.

That's it. Please keep guessing. Help me convince you yourself.

Like a drowning man holding onto the last straw, Rody suddenly pressed on the table with both hands. He stood up and said while his entire body was shivering from excitement, "Thank you so much! You're really just like what they say in the news. Not only a great man of Planet Aquamarine but a great man of the entire universe! You're so noble! To be frank, in my forty-eight years alive, there's only one person I ever admired, and that person is you! You've been my role model from a young age, the light of my life, the motivation of my advance, encouraging me to grow…"

Han Xiao uncontrollably smiled with recognition. He loved to hear people say these facts about him.

However, very soon, he wiped off the smile on his face and signaled for Rody to calm down.

"You don't have to be so appreciative. Honestly, I'm only helping you because I'm interested in your mutation and want to study it. As for whether I can cure you, I can't make any promises."

"I understand. I don't have anything else I can repay you with. I'll do my absolute best to cooperate with your studies." Rody nodded rapidly.

Han Xiao nodded with satisfaction.

There were no free meals, and Rody knew that, which made things easier.

He stood up, circled around Rody, sizing him up closely, and suddenly thought of something.

That's right. I've already established an information connection with him, so I should be able to sting him now.

As this thought appeared, Han Xiao immediately acted.

He raised his finger. Electrical sparks flashed, and nanoparticles formed into a tiny metal needle.

Then, he cautiously stung Rody's arm with the needle, using as little force as a normal person would use to pick up an ant, afraid of using too much strength and squeezing the ant to death.

Then, Han Xiao looked at the interface right away. As expected, combat information appeared, and he could see all of Rody's attributes.

The target was just an ordinary person, so there was little information. All of Rody's abilities were ordinary people abilities. There were only about two lines of information, completely different from how Supers had pages and pages of information.

Only one abnormal piece of information attracted Han Xiao's attention. There was a special status in Rody's status bar, and it had the exact same name as the name of the mission.

_____________________

[Destiny's Child—Sub-body Transformation]: The Primal Esper Ability Entity Destiny's Child has caused an information state disturbance, creating all kinds of 'sub-bodies' randomly in the entire universe. You're one of the chosen ones. A mutation is going to occur to your body. The traits of Information Forms will gradually develop in you, and you'll randomly obtain part of Destiny's Child's abilities. During the transformation, not only will your body change, but your personality will too. When this process ends, you might lose the majority of your desires and emotions, you might lose your memories, or you might believe in made-up life experience. A brand-new personality will be born in your body.

Current Transformation Progress: 37.1%

_____________________

Han Xiao's eyes opened wide. He had captured the key information.

"Destiny's Child is a Primal Esper Ability Entity? Randomly creating sub-bodies all over the universe‽"

This was surprising for him. On the Super High Risk Esper Ability list, Destiny's Child was not included. In his previous life, no players obtained any related information about it. Could this be an undiscovered or unpublicized Primal Esper Ability?

Looking at the introduction on the interface, Han Xiao had a lot of thoughts.

If that's how Destiny's Child's works, what was in the Germinal Organization back in Version 1.0 should have been a sub-body, not the Primal Esper Ability Entity itself…

Rody has yet to completely transform. Once he fully becomes a Destiny's Child sub-body, his personality will be replaced. Maybe that's another form of death.

Although Han Xiao now knew that Destiny's Child's true identity was a Primal Esper Ability Entity, there were still a lot of unsolved mysteries. Perhaps, Ah Ho and Ah K, who were also Primal Esper Ability Entities, would know something.

Han Xiao told the few of them to wait a while in the room while he went to another room, closed the door, and opened up the secondary dimensional army box, summoning the Mysterious Energy Host. At the same time, he sent Aurora a communication request and contacted the Holy Light Particle too.

"Black Star! How have you been? We have to chat more if you haven't been busy!"

The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy looked very happy. He did not have a master, and he was dying of boredom being inside a metal carrier that had no soul.

"I have something I'd like to ask you guys," Han Xiao said. "Do you guys know about a Primal Esper Ability Entity called Destiny's Child?"

Considering that there might be different names, Han Xiao even described part of Destiny's Child's characteristics, which he deduced from the interface.

Hearing this, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and Holy Light Particle suddenly became silent for quite a while.

"This guy… I seem to have seen him before?"

"Odd, did I sleep too much? I feel like I know him, but I just can't recall…"

It felt like the feeling of suddenly realizing someone looked familiar, but they just could not recall who it was.

"According to the information I have, Destiny's Child is heavily related to Information Forms. Maybe that's why you two can't recall it." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and made a guess.

The two of them tried recalling for a while longer, then Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy said hesitantly, "You might be right. We can't recall any more information about it. All we can recall is that there seems to be a Primal Esper Ability Entity in our memories who can switch between a physical form and High Dimensional Information Form. It has the ability to foresee the future, interfere with reality, and so on. It might be the Destiny's Child you're talking about."

Looks like I can't get more information from the two of them…

Han Xiao then changed the topic and asked, "Then, do you guys know about Soul Flame? It's a Primal Esper Ability Entity too."

"I know this one!" The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy quickly responded as if worried the Holy Light Particle would take away its chance to speak. "This guy is sneaky. I haven't met him many times, and the last time I heard about him was during the exploration era. He seems to have chosen a Primordial One as a master. After that, he disappeared for many years."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

According to Aesop's intelligence, Oathkeeper might very well be the master of Soul Flame. He might even be the Primordial One whom Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy mentioned. As long as he knew Oathkeeper's identity, he would be able to expose him.

"Do you remember who that Primordial One was?" Han Xiao quickly asked.

"I only remember his nickname, [Soul Emperor] if I'm not wrong, a powerful spiritual Esper… but he should've died in battle."

Tsk, this nickname doesn't sound like someone who's easy to mess with.

Han Xiao noted it in his mind and planned to ask the dynasty for information about this 'Soul Emperor'.

As for something as mysterious as Destiny's Child, the dynasty might not have records of it.

Since Destiny's Child is a Primal Esper Ability Entity, and the Holy Accord organization is the professional at studying Primal Esper Abilities… asking them might be a good choice.

Han Xiao nodded in his mind. He decided that after his deal with the Holy Accord was complete, he would ask Oathkeeper about Destiny's Child. Maybe he could get some information from him.

Speaking of which, could Destiny's Child be in the Holy Accord organization's hands? Hmm, it's possible but not very likely. Destiny's Child can trigger disturbances, meaning it should be free and not locked up… Hehe, no point thinking so much. It won't hurt if I only ask Oathkeeper.

Han Xiao smirked.

As for whether Oathkeeper will be able to take it…

Hmm, I think his mind should be quite strong.

As he had already asked everything he wanted to, he was about to hang up the communication when he suddenly thought of something and said to the Holy Light Particle, "By the way, I'll have to cut off a part of your body after some time and use it to make a deal with someone. I'm telling you first so you can be mentally prepared."

The Holy Light Particle suddenly stopped in midair and was stunned.

The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was stunned for a minute too. He then suddenly started gloating and laughing loudly. "This day has finally come for you! Who asked you to laugh at me? You can't escape the same fate, hahaha!"

The Holy Light Particle did not respond out loud. I'm so tired. I feel like I won't believe in love anymore.

Chapter 1131: I'm Leaving Her to You

Once Han Xiao had digested the information he had just obtained for a while, he pushed open the door and returned to the interrogation room. Aesop, Harrison, and Rody all looked over.

"Your Excellency Black Star, I…"

Rody hastily wanted to ask, but Han Xiao raised his hand and stopped him.

"I already know about your situation. Come with me for the time being. I'll try to solve your issue."

Han Xiao pondered over what to do about Rody.

Rody was now only a work in progress; he had yet to complete transforming, so he could not control his abilities. He might only become like the Germinal Organization's Destiny's Child after completely transforming.

However, once the transformation was complete, Rody's personality would be taken over by a brand-new personality, so he could be considered dead by then in some senses.

A stable and controllable Foreseer would be much more useful than this half-assed Foreseer who fainted occasionally. However, since he had accepted the mission, he did not want to just let the transformation happen. Hence, Han Xiao decided to think of ways to prevent Rody's transformation as much as he could… And if he could not prevent it, he would not mind getting a new Destiny's Child.

Judging from Rody's current state, controlling his whereabouts was a necessity.

Han Xiao told Phillip to empty a new private lab on the spaceship and told Harrison to take Rody there, put him into a restoration cabin, and inject hypnosis drugs into him so that studying him would be easier. Rody had no choice but to hold on tight to his only hope and cooperate fully.

After the two of them left, Han Xiao and Aesop were the only ones left in the room. They looked at each other.

"I saw you left for a while earlier. Have you already discovered something?" Aesop asked with curiosity.

"The source of this guy's mutation might be because he was affected by a certain special Primal Esper Ability…"

Han Xiao briefly talked about Destiny's Child's information and his experience in the Germinal Organization.

"Destiny's Child… never heard of it," Aesop murmured.

"That's normal. I don't know much either."

Aesop coughed and said, "I don't know much about your past experience, but assuming that the Destiny's Child you met in the past is also a random product of the Primal Esper Ability Entity like Rody, why would two sub-bodies appear on Planet Aquamarine? If it's really random over the universe, do you think this is really coincidental?"

That's nothing. I've seen things that are more coincidental…

This thought flashed past Han Xiao's mind, but he did not show it on his face and agreed. "It is very coincidental indeed."

"Following this logic, if the mutation occurs on the information level, I think that Planet Aquamarine might be special in some way. Maybe it has a special string of fate or something… I'm not saying this out of the blue. I've seen many people who are born with a different string of fate to others…"

Midsentence, Aesop stopped, sized Han Xiao up, and said, "… That's right, someone like you came out of Planet Aquamarine, as well as Hila, another Beyond Grade A. The rise of the two of you caused your mother planet to be unique. Maybe that's the reason."

Han Xiao wanted to say something, but he did not say anything in the end, only patting Aesop's shoulders.

Smart people are indeed easy to trick. You convinced yourself before I said anything.

"Thanks. Without your prophecy, I would have never noticed this."

Jokes aside, Han Xiao was quite appreciative of Aesop's warning.

"You don't have to thank me. Floating Dragon and Planet Aquamarine are neighbors now. I'm just ensuring the safety of the surrounding residential environment. Plus, among the people I know, my prophecies will have the most impact in your hands. I believe in your abilities and morals." Aesop waved his hand.

Hearing this, Han Xiao could not help but realize how much things had changed.

In the past, Han Xiao really envied Aesop's powerful connections. However, as he continued to rise, without him realizing, he already now had the highest position among the people Aesop knew.

Aesop was willing to discuss anything with him. He had become reliable in his eyes.

Aesop sighed and said, "I've lived so long, and I consider myself to be knowledgeable. Yet, you're still the most shocking person I've ever met in my long life. I've never seen anyone as magical as you. The first time I saw you, although I felt that you had a bright future, I would never have expected you to reach heights countless people are never able to reach in just a few decades. History might forget me, but it'll never forget you."

"… Why the sudden compliments? You're flattering me," Han Xiao joked but revealed an expression that said, 'Don't stop.'

"Maybe it's because I'm getting older, so I like to say these things more and more." Aesop sighed and earnestly said, "Thank you for helping Floating Dragon all these years."

Seeing this, Han Xiao wiped off the smile on his face and slowly said, "My achievement cannot be separated from the help I've received from Floating Dragon. Without Ames' protection in the past, things would not have gone so smoothly for me. Therefore, you don't have to thank me. Anything I've done for Floating Dragon is what I should do as repayment."

Just like creating a business, having sponsors would be much easier than starting with nothing. When he was weak, Floating Dragon had helped him a great lot. Therefore, even though his position in the universe was far superior to Floating Dragon, he still held respect for the people of Floating Dragon and never considered himself superior when speaking with them. Plus, he had never stopped helping them.

"Having the opportunity to help someone like you might just be Floating Dragon's luck." Aesop's expression was complicated. He said with a low tone, "Ames is like my daughter, but as you know, the only thing I can do is foresee. I'm not powerful like you guys; you can protect her better than me now…

"I've lived for many years, and I've never asked for anything from anyone, but I'm asking you today, protect Ames. I'm leaving her to you. I hope that even after hundreds and thousands of years, you'll still remember what I said today."

Then, he gave Han Xiao a meaningful look, pushed the door open, and walked out the room. His slightly bent back disappeared at the end of the corridor.

"Old man…"

Han Xiao watched him leave and exhaled slightly. He understood what Aesop meant.

Although Aesop was an Eternal, he was getting old, and he hardly had any combat capability. Even though he could see the future, what he could do was limited. He was far from being almighty.

He foresaw the storms that might occur in the future, and the disaster he saw made him feel worried, something he had not felt in a very long time. He was afraid that he was not capable of protecting Ames, so he planned ahead and was willing to put down his pride to privately ask Black Star to always be the protector of Floating Dragon. This was a form of insurance. In Aesop's eyes, Black Star was the only one who had both the capability and motive to protect Ames, so he was the best candidate he could find.

Ames would absolutely never say these things, so Ames knew only he could say it, and he had to say it.

This was why the old man came to him first unlike before—he got scared by his own prophecy.

"The old man suppressed his nature of looking for thrills and stayed for decades in such a boring place, Floating Dragon. Although he's grounded by Ames on paper, if he wanted to leave, he definitely could. And now, because he's worried about Ames' future, he ignored his pride and came to ask me for something…"

Han Xiao smiled.

In his previous life, Ames caused Floating Dragon to be destroyed for the sake of revenge. Looking at it now, Aesop was certainly worth it.

However, this time, I'm here. I won't let the same thing happen to Floating Dragon.

…

Tidying up his emotions, Han Xiao returned to the office and summoned Phillip.

He still remembered about searching for where Soul Flame ended up in. Using his authority, he found the information about the Primordial One 'Soul Emperor' and quickly browsed through it.

Soul Emperor's real name was Rovell Sissock. He also had other nicknames such as the King of Souls and Master of Secrets. He was a Primordial One. Before becoming the master of Soul Flame, he was already a powerful Beyond Grade A spiritual Esper.

This person was born in an advanced civilization that was already a powerful civilization in the exploration era.

Back then, Beyond Grade As had only just appeared. Compared to other abilities, spiritual Esper Abilities were more difficult to deal with. The technology at that time could not give birth to any spiritual barrier devices that could stop Soul Emperor, so he could easily penetrate the shields and armor to kill or control the people in spaceships. He made a name for himself in the exploration era war very quickly.

After obtaining Soul Flame, like a tiger growing wings, he won countless battles for his civilization in the war using his individual strength and received countless honors and medals. He was seen as the hero and protector of the entire civilization.

However, as all the advanced civilizations started to study the Beyond Grade As, the era when the Primordial Ones were invincible quickly passed. Battles became tougher, and Beyond Grade A casualties started to appear.

Soul Emperor was no exception. Although he was still powerful even among the Beyond Grade As and he was still one of the strongest forces in galactic battles, since he would be targeted every time he appeared, it became tough for him to contribute as much as he did before. He could no longer decide a battle on his own.

Plus, his civilization suffered multiple losses in other battles. The civilization's overall strategy was heavily affected, and the situation gradually grew worse.

Because of that, Soul Emperor's fighting style became aggressive. Sometimes, even if it meant he had to suffer heavy injuries, he would still try to turn the battle around. Although it was not enough, this showed how much he wanted to contribute to his civilization and how loyal he was.

The Primordial Ones back then were unlike the Beyond Grade As now. Most of them did not have the mindset of putting themselves first. In the exploration era war, the fate of individuals was almost totally tied with the fate of civilizations.

Over the long years of war, the turning point quickly came. The civilization Soul Emperor belonged to faced multiple enemies on the main battlefield, which spanned two Star Systems. The civilization dispatched a large number of military forces, and a decisive battle began.

Countless fleets fought intensely on many battlefronts. The situation changed every second. At the peak of the battle, this civilization was faced with a choice…

Soul Emperor was being targeted and surrounded. He was exhausted and needed reinforcements urgently. Meanwhile, an extremely crucial battlefront also requested immediate backup.

If the fight on this battlefront was lost, it would cause chain reactions and might cause the entire war to slip into the abyss of defeat. However, if they were able to win on this battlefront, they would obtain a huge strategic advantage and have much higher chances of winning. This was also the reason the enemies kept sending troops into this battlefield.

At this point of time, this civilization had already dispatched most of its forces into the battlefield and had very few fleets that were available to be deployed. They knew that if they sent reinforcements to both sides, there might be a chance they could save Soul Emperor, but they would definitely not be able to guard the crucial battlefront.

That was where the choice lay… which side they should send their reinforcements to.

To the civilization, this choice did not seem difficult at all.

They abandoned Soul Emperor and decided to put all the reinforcements into that crucial battlefront. The results were just as they expected. They successfully won the fight on that battlefront, obtained a decisive advantage, gradually forced the enemies to retreat, and finally won this war.

Soul Emperor was sacrificed. This civilization said he fought to his last moment and that his death was what led to their victory. The entire civilization mourned for him and paid their respects, hosted his funeral in the highest regards, and gave him the 'Valverde Golden Tower' medal, which represented the highest honor of the civilization. The civilization then also built the Soul Emperor's hero monument on its mother planet to remember him.

However, in the exploration era war, one thing that was never in shortage was enemies. The crucial victory this civilization acquired could not be their amulet forever.

In the end, this civilization never became a winner of the exploration era. It was destroyed by a stronger civilization, its race was almost extinct, and it became a loser that was eliminated.

That was the brief life of Soul Emperor. He was marked as 'Killed In Action' in the documents.

All this happened too long ago, and the exploration era was a chaotic time, so the three Universal Civilizations' database only had rough data of Soul Emperor, nothing too detailed. As Soul Emperor's civilization was eliminated, a lot of information about him was buried by history.

After seeing the documents, Han Xiao started pondering. He was not surprised about how the civilization treated Soul Emperor. He was used to it. He was now only interested in the whereabouts of Soul Flame.

"Soul Emperor is the last Soul Flame master known by the world. Is this guy Oathkeeper? Either Soul Emperor faked his death, or Oathkeeper is someone else who took Soul Flame away from Soul Emperor. If that's the case, there's a chance he's one of the Beyond Grade A enemies of Soul Emperor in that battle, but there's also a possibility it's someone else…"

This time, Han Xiao suddenly thought of the Primordial Ones who got revived in his previous life. They did not seem to include Soul Emperor. Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

"It seems that there's quite a high chance Soul Emperor faked his death…"

Han Xiao pondered.

Quite a number of Primordial Ones were revived in his previous life. If he waited for those people to be revived, he could ask someone who knew about it…

However, at this time, Han Xiao suddenly thought of something and was instantly stunned.

Wait a minute!

People who know about it… are not only those Primordial Ones revived by the Holy Accord!

The Underworld dimension Hila inherited is also storing the Hero Spirits of Primordial Ones!

Now this is excellent…

Han Xiao's eyes widened.

Is this fate?

Or has collecting people who have Luck Glow really changed my luck too‽